<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | Google Cloud on Provision and manage any cloud provider resource using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | Google Cloud on Provision and manage any cloud provider resource using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AppEngineApplication</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/appengineapplication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/appengineapplication/</guid><description>AppEngineApplication Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppEngineApplication metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppEngineApplicationSpec status AppEngineApplicationStatus AppEngineApplicationSpec (Appears on:AppEngineApplication, AppEngineApplicationStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string authDomain string (Optional) codeBucket string (Optional) defaultBucket string (Optional) defaultHostname string (Optional) featureSettings []AppEngineApplicationSpecFeatureSettings (Optional) gcrDomain string (Optional) locationID string name string (Optional) project string (Optional) servingStatus string (Optional) urlDispatchRule []AppEngineApplicationSpecUrlDispatchRule (Optional) AppEngineApplicationSpecFeatureSettings (Appears on:AppEngineApplicationSpec) Field Type Description splitHealthChecks bool (Optional) AppEngineApplicationSpecUrlDispatchRule (Appears on:AppEngineApplicationSpec) Field Type Description domain string (Optional) path string (Optional) service string (Optional) AppEngineApplicationStatus (Appears on:AppEngineApplication) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BigqueryDataset</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerydataset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerydataset/</guid><description>BigqueryDataset Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigqueryDataset metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigqueryDatasetSpec status BigqueryDatasetStatus BigqueryDatasetSpec (Appears on:BigqueryDataset, BigqueryDatasetStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string access []BigqueryDatasetSpecAccess (Optional) creationTime int (Optional) datasetID string defaultTableExpirationMs int (Optional) description string (Optional) etag string (Optional) friendlyName string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lastModifiedTime int (Optional) location string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) BigqueryDatasetSpecAccess (Appears on:BigqueryDatasetSpec) Field Type Description domain string (Optional) groupByEmail string (Optional) role string (Optional) specialGroup string (Optional) userByEmail string (Optional) view []BigqueryDatasetSpecAccessView (Optional) BigqueryDatasetSpecAccessView (Appears on:BigqueryDatasetSpecAccess) Field Type Description datasetID string projectID string tableID string BigqueryDatasetStatus (Appears on:BigqueryDataset) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BigqueryTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerytable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerytable/</guid><description>BigqueryTable Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigqueryTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigqueryTableSpec status BigqueryTableStatus BigqueryTableSpec (Appears on:BigqueryTable, BigqueryTableStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTime int (Optional) datasetID string description string (Optional) etag string (Optional) expirationTime int (Optional) friendlyName string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lastModifiedTime int (Optional) location string (Optional) numBytes int (Optional) numLongTermBytes int (Optional) numRows int (Optional) project string (Optional) schema string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) tableID string timePartitioning []BigqueryTableSpecTimePartitioning (Optional) type string (Optional) view []BigqueryTableSpecView (Optional) BigqueryTableSpecTimePartitioning (Appears on:BigqueryTableSpec) Field Type Description expirationMs int (Optional) field string (Optional) type string BigqueryTableSpecView (Appears on:BigqueryTableSpec) Field Type Description query string useLegacySQL bool (Optional) BigqueryTableStatus (Appears on:BigqueryTable) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BigtableInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstance/</guid><description>BigtableInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableInstanceSpec status BigtableInstanceStatus BigtableInstanceSpec (Appears on:BigtableInstance, BigtableInstanceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cluster []BigtableInstanceSpecCluster (Optional) clusterID string (Optional) Deprecated displayName string (Optional) instanceType string (Optional) name string numNodes int (Optional) Deprecated project string (Optional) storageType string (Optional) Deprecated zone string (Optional) Deprecated BigtableInstanceSpecCluster (Appears on:BigtableInstanceSpec) Field Type Description clusterID string (Optional) numNodes int (Optional) storageType string (Optional) zone string (Optional) BigtableInstanceStatus (Appears on:BigtableInstance) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BigtableTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtabletable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtabletable/</guid><description>BigtableTable Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableTableSpec status BigtableTableStatus BigtableTableSpec (Appears on:BigtableTable, BigtableTableStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string instanceName string name string project string (Optional) splitKeys []string (Optional) BigtableTableStatus (Appears on:BigtableTable) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BillingAccountIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiambinding/</guid><description>BillingAccountIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BillingAccountIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BillingAccountIamBindingSpec status BillingAccountIamBindingStatus BillingAccountIamBindingSpec (Appears on:BillingAccountIamBinding, BillingAccountIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccountID string etag string (Optional) members []string role string BillingAccountIamBindingStatus (Appears on:BillingAccountIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BillingAccountIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiammember/</guid><description>BillingAccountIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BillingAccountIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BillingAccountIamMemberSpec status BillingAccountIamMemberStatus BillingAccountIamMemberSpec (Appears on:BillingAccountIamMember, BillingAccountIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccountID string etag string (Optional) member string role string BillingAccountIamMemberStatus (Appears on:BillingAccountIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BillingAccountIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiampolicy/</guid><description>BillingAccountIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BillingAccountIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BillingAccountIamPolicySpec status BillingAccountIamPolicyStatus BillingAccountIamPolicySpec (Appears on:BillingAccountIamPolicy, BillingAccountIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccountID string etag string (Optional) policyData string BillingAccountIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:BillingAccountIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BinaryAuthorizationAttestor</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestor/</guid><description>BinaryAuthorizationAttestor Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BinaryAuthorizationAttestor metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpec status BinaryAuthorizationAttestorStatus BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpec (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestor, BinaryAuthorizationAttestorStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string attestationAuthorityNote []BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpecAttestationAuthorityNote description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpecAttestationAuthorityNote (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpec) Field Type Description delegationServiceAccountEmail string (Optional) noteReference string publicKeys []BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpecAttestationAuthorityNotePublicKeys (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpecAttestationAuthorityNotePublicKeys (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpecAttestationAuthorityNote) Field Type Description asciiArmoredPgpPublicKey string comment string (Optional) ID string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationAttestorStatus (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestor) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>BinaryAuthorizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationpolicy/</guid><description>BinaryAuthorizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BinaryAuthorizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec status BinaryAuthorizationPolicyStatus BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationPolicy, BinaryAuthorizationPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string admissionWhitelistPatterns []BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecAdmissionWhitelistPatterns (Optional) clusterAdmissionRules []BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecClusterAdmissionRules (Optional) defaultAdmissionRule []BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecDefaultAdmissionRule description string (Optional) project string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecAdmissionWhitelistPatterns (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description namePattern string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecClusterAdmissionRules (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description cluster string enforcementMode string (Optional) evaluationMode string (Optional) requireAttestationsBy []string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecDefaultAdmissionRule (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description enforcementMode string evaluationMode string requireAttestationsBy []string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationPolicyStatus (Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>CloudbuildTrigger</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudbuildtrigger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudbuildtrigger/</guid><description>CloudbuildTrigger Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudbuildTrigger metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudbuildTriggerSpec status CloudbuildTriggerStatus CloudbuildTriggerSpec (Appears on:CloudbuildTrigger, CloudbuildTriggerStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string build []CloudbuildTriggerSpecBuild (Optional) Contents of the build template.</description></item><item><title>CloudfunctionsFunction</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunction/</guid><description>CloudfunctionsFunction Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudfunctionsFunction metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudfunctionsFunctionSpec status CloudfunctionsFunctionStatus CloudfunctionsFunctionSpec (Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunction, CloudfunctionsFunctionStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string availableMemoryMb int (Optional) description string (Optional) entryPoint string (Optional) environmentVariables map[string]string (Optional) eventTrigger []CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecEventTrigger (Optional) httpsTriggerURL string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) retryOnFailure bool (Optional) Deprecated runtime string (Optional) sourceArchiveBucket string sourceArchiveObject string timeout int (Optional) triggerBucket string (Optional) Deprecated triggerHTTP bool (Optional) triggerTopic string (Optional) Deprecated CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecEventTrigger (Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionSpec) Field Type Description eventType string failurePolicy []CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecEventTriggerFailurePolicy (Optional) resource string CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecEventTriggerFailurePolicy (Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecEventTrigger) Field Type Description retry bool CloudfunctionsFunctionStatus (Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunction) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>CloudiotRegistry</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudiotregistry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudiotregistry/</guid><description>CloudiotRegistry Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudiotRegistry metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudiotRegistrySpec status CloudiotRegistryStatus CloudiotRegistrySpec (Appears on:CloudiotRegistry, CloudiotRegistryStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string credentials []CloudiotRegistrySpecCredentials (Optional) eventNotificationConfig map[string]kubeform.</description></item><item><title>ComposerEnvironment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/composerenvironment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/composerenvironment/</guid><description>ComposerEnvironment Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComposerEnvironment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComposerEnvironmentSpec status ComposerEnvironmentStatus ComposerEnvironmentSpec (Appears on:ComposerEnvironment, ComposerEnvironmentStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string config []ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfig (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfig (Appears on:ComposerEnvironmentSpec) Field Type Description airflowURI string (Optional) dagGcsPrefix string (Optional) gkeCluster string (Optional) nodeConfig []ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfigNodeConfig (Optional) nodeCount int (Optional) softwareConfig []ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfigSoftwareConfig (Optional) ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfigNodeConfig (Appears on:ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfig) Field Type Description diskSizeGb int (Optional) machineType string (Optional) network string (Optional) oauthScopes []string (Optional) serviceAccount string (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) tags []string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfigSoftwareConfig (Appears on:ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfig) Field Type Description airflowConfigOverrides map[string]string (Optional) envVariables map[string]string (Optional) imageVersion string (Optional) pypiPackages map[string]string (Optional) ComposerEnvironmentStatus (Appears on:ComposerEnvironment) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeAddress</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeaddress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeaddress/</guid><description>ComputeAddress Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeAddress metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeAddressSpec status ComputeAddressStatus ComputeAddressSpec (Appears on:ComputeAddress, ComputeAddressStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string address string (Optional) addressType string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) Deprecated labels map[string]string (Optional) Deprecated name string networkTier string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) users []string (Optional) ComputeAddressStatus (Appears on:ComputeAddress) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeAttachedDisk</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeattacheddisk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeattacheddisk/</guid><description>ComputeAttachedDisk Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeAttachedDisk metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeAttachedDiskSpec status ComputeAttachedDiskStatus ComputeAttachedDiskSpec (Appears on:ComputeAttachedDisk, ComputeAttachedDiskStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string deviceName string (Optional) disk string instance string mode string (Optional) project string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeAttachedDiskStatus (Appears on:ComputeAttachedDisk) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeAutoscaler</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeautoscaler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeautoscaler/</guid><description>ComputeAutoscaler Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeAutoscaler metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeAutoscalerSpec status ComputeAutoscalerStatus ComputeAutoscalerSpec (Appears on:ComputeAutoscaler, ComputeAutoscalerStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoscalingPolicy []ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) target string zone string (Optional) ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy (Appears on:ComputeAutoscalerSpec) Field Type Description cooldownPeriod int (Optional) cpuUtilization []ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyCpuUtilization (Optional) loadBalancingUtilization []ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyLoadBalancingUtilization (Optional) maxReplicas int metric []ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyMetric (Optional) minReplicas int ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyCpuUtilization (Appears on:ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy) Field Type Description target encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>ComputeBackendBucket</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendbucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendbucket/</guid><description>ComputeBackendBucket Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeBackendBucket metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeBackendBucketSpec status ComputeBackendBucketStatus ComputeBackendBucketSpec (Appears on:ComputeBackendBucket, ComputeBackendBucketStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucketName string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) enableCdn bool (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeBackendBucketStatus (Appears on:ComputeBackendBucket) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeBackendService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendservice/</guid><description>ComputeBackendService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeBackendService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeBackendServiceSpec status ComputeBackendServiceStatus ComputeBackendServiceSpec (Appears on:ComputeBackendService, ComputeBackendServiceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeDisk</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computedisk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computedisk/</guid><description>ComputeDisk Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeDisk metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeDiskSpec status ComputeDiskStatus ComputeDiskSpec (Appears on:ComputeDisk, ComputeDiskStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeFirewall</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computefirewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computefirewall/</guid><description>ComputeFirewall Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeFirewall metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeFirewallSpec status ComputeFirewallStatus ComputeFirewallSpec (Appears on:ComputeFirewall, ComputeFirewallStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string allow []ComputeFirewallSpecAllow (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) deny []ComputeFirewallSpecDeny (Optional) description string (Optional) destinationRanges []string (Optional) direction string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) enableLogging bool (Optional) Deprecated name string network string priority int (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sourceRanges []string (Optional) sourceServiceAccounts []string (Optional) sourceTags []string (Optional) targetServiceAccounts []string (Optional) targetTags []string (Optional) ComputeFirewallSpecAllow (Appears on:ComputeFirewallSpec) Field Type Description ports []string (Optional) protocol string ComputeFirewallSpecDeny (Appears on:ComputeFirewallSpec) Field Type Description ports []string (Optional) protocol string ComputeFirewallStatus (Appears on:ComputeFirewall) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeForwardingRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeforwardingrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeforwardingrule/</guid><description>ComputeForwardingRule Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeForwardingRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeForwardingRuleSpec status ComputeForwardingRuleStatus ComputeForwardingRuleSpec (Appears on:ComputeForwardingRule, ComputeForwardingRuleStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendService string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) ipAddress string (Optional) ipProtocol string (Optional) ipVersion string (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) Deprecated loadBalancingScheme string (Optional) name string network string (Optional) networkTier string (Optional) portRange string (Optional) ports []string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) serviceLabel string (Optional) Deprecated serviceName string (Optional) Deprecated subnetwork string (Optional) target string (Optional) ComputeForwardingRuleStatus (Appears on:ComputeForwardingRule) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeGlobalAddress</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobaladdress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobaladdress/</guid><description>ComputeGlobalAddress Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeGlobalAddress metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeGlobalAddressSpec status ComputeGlobalAddressStatus ComputeGlobalAddressSpec (Appears on:ComputeGlobalAddress, ComputeGlobalAddressStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string address string (Optional) addressType string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) ipVersion string (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) Deprecated name string network string (Optional) Deprecated prefixLength int (Optional) Deprecated project string (Optional) purpose string (Optional) Deprecated selfLink string (Optional) ComputeGlobalAddressStatus (Appears on:ComputeGlobalAddress) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeGlobalForwardingRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobalforwardingrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobalforwardingrule/</guid><description>ComputeGlobalForwardingRule Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeGlobalForwardingRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleSpec status ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleStatus ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleSpec (Appears on:ComputeGlobalForwardingRule, ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) ipAddress string (Optional) ipProtocol string (Optional) ipVersion string (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) Deprecated name string portRange string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) target string ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleStatus (Appears on:ComputeGlobalForwardingRule) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeHealthCheck</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehealthcheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehealthcheck/</guid><description>ComputeHealthCheck Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeHealthCheck metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeHealthCheckSpec status ComputeHealthCheckStatus ComputeHealthCheckSpec (Appears on:ComputeHealthCheck, ComputeHealthCheckStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string checkIntervalSec int (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) healthyThreshold int (Optional) httpHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttpHealthCheck (Optional) httpsHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttpsHealthCheck (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sslHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecSslHealthCheck (Optional) tcpHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecTcpHealthCheck (Optional) timeoutSec int (Optional) type string (Optional) unhealthyThreshold int (Optional) ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttpHealthCheck (Appears on:ComputeHealthCheckSpec) Field Type Description host string (Optional) port int (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) requestPath string (Optional) response string (Optional) ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttpsHealthCheck (Appears on:ComputeHealthCheckSpec) Field Type Description host string (Optional) port int (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) requestPath string (Optional) response string (Optional) ComputeHealthCheckSpecSslHealthCheck (Appears on:ComputeHealthCheckSpec) Field Type Description port int (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) request string (Optional) response string (Optional) ComputeHealthCheckSpecTcpHealthCheck (Appears on:ComputeHealthCheckSpec) Field Type Description port int (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) request string (Optional) response string (Optional) ComputeHealthCheckStatus (Appears on:ComputeHealthCheck) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeHTTPHealthCheck</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttphealthcheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttphealthcheck/</guid><description>ComputeHTTPHealthCheck Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeHTTPHealthCheck metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeHTTPHealthCheckSpec status ComputeHTTPHealthCheckStatus ComputeHTTPHealthCheckSpec (Appears on:ComputeHTTPHealthCheck, ComputeHTTPHealthCheckStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string checkIntervalSec int (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) healthyThreshold int (Optional) host string (Optional) name string port int (Optional) project string (Optional) requestPath string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) timeoutSec int (Optional) unhealthyThreshold int (Optional) ComputeHTTPHealthCheckStatus (Appears on:ComputeHTTPHealthCheck) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttpshealthcheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttpshealthcheck/</guid><description>ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckSpec status ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckStatus ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckSpec (Appears on:ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck, ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string checkIntervalSec int (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) healthyThreshold int (Optional) host string (Optional) name string port int (Optional) project string (Optional) requestPath string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) timeoutSec int (Optional) unhealthyThreshold int (Optional) ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckStatus (Appears on:ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeImage</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeimage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeimage/</guid><description>ComputeImage Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeImage metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeImageSpec status ComputeImageStatus ComputeImageSpec (Appears on:ComputeImage, ComputeImageStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTimeout int (Optional) Deprecated description string (Optional) family string (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) licenses []string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) rawDisk []ComputeImageSpecRawDisk (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sourceDisk string (Optional) ComputeImageSpecRawDisk (Appears on:ComputeImageSpec) Field Type Description containerType string (Optional) sha1 string (Optional) source string ComputeImageStatus (Appears on:ComputeImage) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstance/</guid><description>ComputeInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceSpec status ComputeInstanceStatus ComputeInstanceSpec (Appears on:ComputeInstance, ComputeInstanceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceFromTemplate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancefromtemplate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancefromtemplate/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceFromTemplate Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceFromTemplate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceFromTemplateSpec status ComputeInstanceFromTemplateStatus ComputeInstanceFromTemplateSpec (Appears on:ComputeInstanceFromTemplate, ComputeInstanceFromTemplateStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroup/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceGroupSpec status ComputeInstanceGroupStatus ComputeInstanceGroupSpec (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroup, ComputeInstanceGroupStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) instances []string (Optional) name string namedPort []ComputeInstanceGroupSpecNamedPort (Optional) network string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) size int (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeInstanceGroupSpecNamedPort (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupSpec) Field Type Description name string port int ComputeInstanceGroupStatus (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroup) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceGroupManager</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroupmanager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroupmanager/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceGroupManager Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceGroupManager metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec status ComputeInstanceGroupManagerStatus ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManager, ComputeInstanceGroupManagerStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoHealingPolicies []ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecAutoHealingPolicies (Optional) Deprecated baseInstanceName string description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) instanceGroup string (Optional) instanceTemplate string (Optional) name string namedPort []ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort (Optional) project string (Optional) rollingUpdatePolicy []ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecRollingUpdatePolicy (Optional) Deprecated selfLink string (Optional) targetPools []string (Optional) targetSize int (Optional) updateStrategy string (Optional) version []ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersion (Optional) Deprecated waitForInstances bool (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecAutoHealingPolicies (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description healthCheck string initialDelaySec int ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description name string port int ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecRollingUpdatePolicy (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description maxSurgeFixed int (Optional) maxSurgePercent int (Optional) maxUnavailableFixed int (Optional) maxUnavailablePercent int (Optional) minReadySec int (Optional) minimalAction string type string ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersion (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description instanceTemplate string name string targetSize []ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersionTargetSize (Optional) ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersionTargetSize (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersion) Field Type Description fixed int (Optional) percent int (Optional) ComputeInstanceGroupManagerStatus (Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManager) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceTemplate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancetemplate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancetemplate/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceTemplate Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceTemplate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec status ComputeInstanceTemplateStatus ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplate, ComputeInstanceTemplateStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string canIPForward bool (Optional) description string (Optional) disk []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecDisk guestAccelerator []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecGuestAccelerator (Optional) instanceDescription string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) machineType string metadata map[string]string (Optional) metadataFingerprint string (Optional) metadataStartupScript string (Optional) minCPUPlatform string (Optional) name string (Optional) namePrefix string (Optional) networkInterface []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterface (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) scheduling []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecScheduling (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) serviceAccount []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecServiceAccount (Optional) tags []string (Optional) tagsFingerprint string (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecDisk (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec) Field Type Description autoDelete bool (Optional) boot bool (Optional) deviceName string (Optional) diskEncryptionKey []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecDiskDiskEncryptionKey (Optional) diskName string (Optional) diskSizeGb int (Optional) diskType string (Optional) interface string (Optional) mode string (Optional) source string (Optional) sourceImage string (Optional) type string (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecDiskDiskEncryptionKey (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecDisk) Field Type Description kmsKeySelfLink string (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecGuestAccelerator (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec) Field Type Description count int type string ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterface (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec) Field Type Description accessConfig []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterfaceAccessConfig (Optional) address string (Optional) Deprecated aliasIPRange []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterfaceAliasIPRange (Optional) network string (Optional) networkIP string (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) subnetworkProject string (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterfaceAccessConfig (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterface) Field Type Description assignedNATIP string (Optional) Deprecated natIP string (Optional) networkTier string (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterfaceAliasIPRange (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterface) Field Type Description ipCIDRRange string subnetworkRangeName string (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecScheduling (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec) Field Type Description automaticRestart bool (Optional) onHostMaintenance string (Optional) preemptible bool (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecServiceAccount (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec) Field Type Description email string (Optional) scopes []string ComputeInstanceTemplateStatus (Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplate) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInterconnectAttachment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinterconnectattachment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinterconnectattachment/</guid><description>ComputeInterconnectAttachment Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInterconnectAttachment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpec status ComputeInterconnectAttachmentStatus ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpec (Appears on:ComputeInterconnectAttachment, ComputeInterconnectAttachmentStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cloudRouterIPAddress string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) customerRouterIPAddress string (Optional) description string (Optional) googleReferenceID string (Optional) interconnect string name string privateInterconnectInfo []ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpecPrivateInterconnectInfo (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string selfLink string (Optional) ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpecPrivateInterconnectInfo (Appears on:ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpec) Field Type Description tag8021q int (Optional) ComputeInterconnectAttachmentStatus (Appears on:ComputeInterconnectAttachment) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeNetwork</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetwork/</guid><description>ComputeNetwork Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNetwork metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNetworkSpec status ComputeNetworkStatus ComputeNetworkSpec (Appears on:ComputeNetwork, ComputeNetworkStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoCreateSubnetworks bool (Optional) description string (Optional) gatewayIpv4 string (Optional) ipv4Range string (Optional) Deprecated name string project string (Optional) routingMode string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeNetworkStatus (Appears on:ComputeNetwork) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeNetworkPeering</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkpeering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkpeering/</guid><description>ComputeNetworkPeering Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNetworkPeering metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNetworkPeeringSpec status ComputeNetworkPeeringStatus ComputeNetworkPeeringSpec (Appears on:ComputeNetworkPeering, ComputeNetworkPeeringStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoCreateRoutes bool (Optional) name string network string peerNetwork string state string (Optional) stateDetails string (Optional) ComputeNetworkPeeringStatus (Appears on:ComputeNetworkPeering) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeProjectMetadata</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadata/</guid><description>ComputeProjectMetadata Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeProjectMetadata metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeProjectMetadataSpec status ComputeProjectMetadataStatus ComputeProjectMetadataSpec (Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadata, ComputeProjectMetadataStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string metadata map[string]string project string (Optional) ComputeProjectMetadataStatus (Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadata) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeProjectMetadataItem</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadataitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadataitem/</guid><description>ComputeProjectMetadataItem Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeProjectMetadataItem metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeProjectMetadataItemSpec status ComputeProjectMetadataItemStatus ComputeProjectMetadataItemSpec (Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadataItem, ComputeProjectMetadataItemStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string key string project string (Optional) value string ComputeProjectMetadataItemStatus (Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadataItem) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionAutoscaler</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionautoscaler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionautoscaler/</guid><description>ComputeRegionAutoscaler Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionAutoscaler metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpec status ComputeRegionAutoscalerStatus ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpec (Appears on:ComputeRegionAutoscaler, ComputeRegionAutoscalerStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoscalingPolicy []ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) target string ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy (Appears on:ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpec) Field Type Description cooldownPeriod int (Optional) cpuUtilization []ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyCpuUtilization (Optional) loadBalancingUtilization []ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyLoadBalancingUtilization (Optional) maxReplicas int metric []ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyMetric (Optional) minReplicas int ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicyCpuUtilization (Appears on:ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy) Field Type Description target encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionBackendService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionbackendservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionbackendservice/</guid><description>ComputeRegionBackendService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionBackendService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpec status ComputeRegionBackendServiceStatus ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpec (Appears on:ComputeRegionBackendService, ComputeRegionBackendServiceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backend []ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpecBackend (Optional) connectionDrainingTimeoutSec int (Optional) description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) healthChecks []string name string project string (Optional) protocol string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sessionAffinity string (Optional) timeoutSec int (Optional) ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpecBackend (Appears on:ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpec) Field Type Description description string (Optional) group string (Optional) ComputeRegionBackendServiceStatus (Appears on:ComputeRegionBackendService) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionDisk</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregiondisk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregiondisk/</guid><description>ComputeRegionDisk Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionDisk metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionDiskSpec status ComputeRegionDiskStatus ComputeRegionDiskSpec (Appears on:ComputeRegionDisk, ComputeRegionDiskStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) diskEncryptionKey []ComputeRegionDiskSpecDiskEncryptionKey (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lastAttachTimestamp string (Optional) lastDetachTimestamp string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) replicaZones []string selfLink string (Optional) size int (Optional) snapshot string (Optional) sourceSnapshotEncryptionKey []ComputeRegionDiskSpecSourceSnapshotEncryptionKey (Optional) sourceSnapshotID string (Optional) type string (Optional) users []string (Optional) ComputeRegionDiskSpecDiskEncryptionKey (Appears on:ComputeRegionDiskSpec) Field Type Description rawKey string (Optional) sha256 string (Optional) ComputeRegionDiskSpecSourceSnapshotEncryptionKey (Appears on:ComputeRegionDiskSpec) Field Type Description rawKey string (Optional) sha256 string (Optional) ComputeRegionDiskStatus (Appears on:ComputeRegionDisk) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregioninstancegroupmanager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregioninstancegroupmanager/</guid><description>ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec status ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerStatus ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec (Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager, ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoHealingPolicies []ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecAutoHealingPolicies (Optional) Deprecated baseInstanceName string description string (Optional) distributionPolicyZones []string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) instanceGroup string (Optional) instanceTemplate string (Optional) name string namedPort []ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort (Optional) project string (Optional) region string rollingUpdatePolicy []ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecRollingUpdatePolicy (Optional) Deprecated selfLink string (Optional) targetPools []string (Optional) targetSize int (Optional) updateStrategy string (Optional) Deprecated version []ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersion (Optional) Deprecated waitForInstances bool (Optional) ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecAutoHealingPolicies (Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description healthCheck string initialDelaySec int ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort (Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description name string port int ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecRollingUpdatePolicy (Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description maxSurgeFixed int (Optional) maxSurgePercent int (Optional) maxUnavailableFixed int (Optional) maxUnavailablePercent int (Optional) minReadySec int (Optional) minimalAction string type string ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersion (Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec) Field Type Description instanceTemplate string name string targetSize []ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersionTargetSize (Optional) ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersionTargetSize (Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecVersion) Field Type Description fixed int (Optional) percent int (Optional) ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerStatus (Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRoute</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeroute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeroute/</guid><description>ComputeRoute Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRoute metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouteSpec status ComputeRouteStatus ComputeRouteSpec (Appears on:ComputeRoute, ComputeRouteStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) destRange string name string network string nextHopGateway string (Optional) nextHopInstance string (Optional) nextHopInstanceZone string (Optional) nextHopIP string (Optional) nextHopNetwork string (Optional) nextHopVPNTunnel string (Optional) priority int (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) tags []string (Optional) ComputeRouteStatus (Appears on:ComputeRoute) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouter</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouter/</guid><description>ComputeRouter Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouter metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterSpec status ComputeRouterStatus ComputeRouterSpec (Appears on:ComputeRouter, ComputeRouterStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bgp []ComputeRouterSpecBgp (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string network string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeRouterSpecBgp (Appears on:ComputeRouterSpec) Field Type Description advertiseMode string (Optional) advertisedGroups []string (Optional) advertisedIPRanges []ComputeRouterSpecBgpAdvertisedIPRanges (Optional) asn int ComputeRouterSpecBgpAdvertisedIPRanges (Appears on:ComputeRouterSpecBgp) Field Type Description description string (Optional) range string (Optional) ComputeRouterStatus (Appears on:ComputeRouter) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouterInterface</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterinterface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterinterface/</guid><description>ComputeRouterInterface Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouterInterface metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterInterfaceSpec status ComputeRouterInterfaceStatus ComputeRouterInterfaceSpec (Appears on:ComputeRouterInterface, ComputeRouterInterfaceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string ipRange string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string vpnTunnel string ComputeRouterInterfaceStatus (Appears on:ComputeRouterInterface) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouterNAT</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouternat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouternat/</guid><description>ComputeRouterNAT Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouterNAT metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterNATSpec status ComputeRouterNATStatus ComputeRouterNATSpec (Appears on:ComputeRouterNAT, ComputeRouterNATStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string icmpIdleTimeoutSec int (Optional) minPortsPerVm int (Optional) name string natIPAllocateOption string natIPS []string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string sourceSubnetworkIPRangesToNAT string (Optional) subnetwork []ComputeRouterNATSpecSubnetwork (Optional) tcpEstablishedIdleTimeoutSec int (Optional) tcpTransitoryIdleTimeoutSec int (Optional) udpIdleTimeoutSec int (Optional) ComputeRouterNATSpecSubnetwork (Appears on:ComputeRouterNATSpec) Field Type Description name string secondaryIPRangeNames []string (Optional) sourceIPRangesToNAT []string (Optional) ComputeRouterNATStatus (Appears on:ComputeRouterNAT) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouterPeer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterpeer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterpeer/</guid><description>ComputeRouterPeer Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouterPeer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterPeerSpec status ComputeRouterPeerStatus ComputeRouterPeerSpec (Appears on:ComputeRouterPeer, ComputeRouterPeerStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string advertisedRoutePriority int (Optional) interface string ipAddress string (Optional) name string peerAsn int peerIPAddress string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string ComputeRouterPeerStatus (Appears on:ComputeRouterPeer) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSecurityPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesecuritypolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesecuritypolicy/</guid><description>ComputeSecurityPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSecurityPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSecurityPolicySpec status ComputeSecurityPolicyStatus ComputeSecurityPolicySpec (Appears on:ComputeSecurityPolicy, ComputeSecurityPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) rule []ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRule (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRule (Appears on:ComputeSecurityPolicySpec) Field Type Description action string description string (Optional) match []ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRuleMatch preview bool (Optional) priority int ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRuleMatch (Appears on:ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRule) Field Type Description config []ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRuleMatchConfig versionedExpr string ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRuleMatchConfig (Appears on:ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRuleMatch) Field Type Description srcIPRanges []string ComputeSecurityPolicyStatus (Appears on:ComputeSecurityPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSharedVpcHostProject</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpchostproject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpchostproject/</guid><description>ComputeSharedVpcHostProject Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSharedVpcHostProject metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectSpec status ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectStatus ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectSpec (Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcHostProject, ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string project string ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectStatus (Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcHostProject) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpcserviceproject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpcserviceproject/</guid><description>ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectSpec status ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectStatus ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectSpec (Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject, ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string hostProject string serviceProject string ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectStatus (Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSnapshot</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesnapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesnapshot/</guid><description>ComputeSnapshot Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSnapshot metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSnapshotSpec status ComputeSnapshotStatus ComputeSnapshotSpec (Appears on:ComputeSnapshot, ComputeSnapshotStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSSLCertificate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslcertificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslcertificate/</guid><description>ComputeSSLCertificate Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSSLCertificate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSSLCertificateSpec status ComputeSSLCertificateStatus ComputeSSLCertificateSpec (Appears on:ComputeSSLCertificate, ComputeSSLCertificateStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSSLPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslpolicy/</guid><description>ComputeSSLPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSSLPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSSLPolicySpec status ComputeSSLPolicyStatus ComputeSSLPolicySpec (Appears on:ComputeSSLPolicy, ComputeSSLPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) customFeatures []string (Optional) description string (Optional) enabledFeatures []string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) minTLSVersion string (Optional) name string profile string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeSSLPolicyStatus (Appears on:ComputeSSLPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetwork</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetwork/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetwork Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetwork metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkSpec status ComputeSubnetworkStatus ComputeSubnetworkSpec (Appears on:ComputeSubnetwork, ComputeSubnetworkStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) enableFlowLogs bool (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) gatewayAddress string (Optional) ipCIDRRange string name string network string privateIPGoogleAccess bool (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) secondaryIPRange []ComputeSubnetworkSpecSecondaryIPRange (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeSubnetworkSpecSecondaryIPRange (Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkSpec) Field Type Description ipCIDRRange string rangeName string ComputeSubnetworkStatus (Appears on:ComputeSubnetwork) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiambinding/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingSpec status ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingStatus ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingSpec (Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding, ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) Deprecated region string (Optional) Deprecated role string subnetwork string Deprecated ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingStatus (Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetworkIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiammember/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetworkIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetworkIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberSpec status ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberStatus ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberSpec (Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamMember, ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) Deprecated region string (Optional) Deprecated role string subnetwork string Deprecated ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberStatus (Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiampolicy/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicySpec status ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicyStatus ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicySpec (Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy, ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) Deprecated region string (Optional) Deprecated subnetwork string Deprecated ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetHTTPProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetHTTPProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetHTTPProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetHTTPProxySpec status ComputeTargetHTTPProxyStatus ComputeTargetHTTPProxySpec (Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPProxy, ComputeTargetHTTPProxyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyID int (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) urlMap string ComputeTargetHTTPProxyStatus (Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPProxy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpsproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpsproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetHTTPSProxySpec status ComputeTargetHTTPSProxyStatus ComputeTargetHTTPSProxySpec (Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy, ComputeTargetHTTPSProxyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyID int (Optional) quicOverride string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sslCertificates []string sslPolicy string (Optional) urlMap string ComputeTargetHTTPSProxyStatus (Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetPool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetpool/</guid><description>ComputeTargetPool Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetPool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetPoolSpec status ComputeTargetPoolStatus ComputeTargetPoolSpec (Appears on:ComputeTargetPool, ComputeTargetPoolStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backupPool string (Optional) description string (Optional) failoverRatio encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetSSLProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetsslproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetsslproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetSSLProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetSSLProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetSSLProxySpec status ComputeTargetSSLProxyStatus ComputeTargetSSLProxySpec (Appears on:ComputeTargetSSLProxy, ComputeTargetSSLProxyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendService string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) proxyID int (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sslCertificates []string sslPolicy string (Optional) ComputeTargetSSLProxyStatus (Appears on:ComputeTargetSSLProxy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetTcpProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargettcpproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargettcpproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetTcpProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetTcpProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetTcpProxySpec status ComputeTargetTcpProxyStatus ComputeTargetTcpProxySpec (Appears on:ComputeTargetTcpProxy, ComputeTargetTcpProxyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendService string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) proxyID int (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeTargetTcpProxyStatus (Appears on:ComputeTargetTcpProxy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeURLMap</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeurlmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeurlmap/</guid><description>ComputeURLMap Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeURLMap metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeURLMapSpec status ComputeURLMapStatus ComputeURLMapSpec (Appears on:ComputeURLMap, ComputeURLMapStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string defaultService string description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) hostRule []ComputeURLMapSpecHostRule (Optional) mapID string (Optional) name string pathMatcher []ComputeURLMapSpecPathMatcher (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) test []ComputeURLMapSpecTest (Optional) ComputeURLMapSpecHostRule (Appears on:ComputeURLMapSpec) Field Type Description description string (Optional) hosts []string pathMatcher string ComputeURLMapSpecPathMatcher (Appears on:ComputeURLMapSpec) Field Type Description defaultService string description string (Optional) name string pathRule []ComputeURLMapSpecPathMatcherPathRule (Optional) ComputeURLMapSpecPathMatcherPathRule (Appears on:ComputeURLMapSpecPathMatcher) Field Type Description paths []string service string ComputeURLMapSpecTest (Appears on:ComputeURLMapSpec) Field Type Description description string (Optional) host string path string service string ComputeURLMapStatus (Appears on:ComputeURLMap) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeVPNGateway</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpngateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpngateway/</guid><description>ComputeVPNGateway Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeVPNGateway metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeVPNGatewaySpec status ComputeVPNGatewayStatus ComputeVPNGatewaySpec (Appears on:ComputeVPNGateway, ComputeVPNGatewayStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string network string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeVPNGatewayStatus (Appears on:ComputeVPNGateway) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ComputeVPNTunnel</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpntunnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpntunnel/</guid><description>ComputeVPNTunnel Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeVPNTunnel metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeVPNTunnelSpec status ComputeVPNTunnelStatus ComputeVPNTunnelSpec (Appears on:ComputeVPNTunnel, ComputeVPNTunnelStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ContainerAnalysisNote</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/containeranalysisnote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/containeranalysisnote/</guid><description>ContainerAnalysisNote Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerAnalysisNote metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerAnalysisNoteSpec status ContainerAnalysisNoteStatus ContainerAnalysisNoteSpec (Appears on:ContainerAnalysisNote, ContainerAnalysisNoteStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string attestationAuthority []ContainerAnalysisNoteSpecAttestationAuthority name string project string (Optional) ContainerAnalysisNoteSpecAttestationAuthority (Appears on:ContainerAnalysisNoteSpec) Field Type Description hint []ContainerAnalysisNoteSpecAttestationAuthorityHint ContainerAnalysisNoteSpecAttestationAuthorityHint (Appears on:ContainerAnalysisNoteSpecAttestationAuthority) Field Type Description humanReadableName string ContainerAnalysisNoteStatus (Appears on:ContainerAnalysisNote) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ContainerCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/containercluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/containercluster/</guid><description>ContainerCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerClusterSpec status ContainerClusterStatus ContainerClusterSpec (Appears on:ContainerCluster, ContainerClusterStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ContainerNodePool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/containernodepool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/containernodepool/</guid><description>ContainerNodePool Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerNodePool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerNodePoolSpec status ContainerNodePoolStatus ContainerNodePoolSpec (Appears on:ContainerNodePool, ContainerNodePoolStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoscaling []ContainerNodePoolSpecAutoscaling (Optional) cluster string initialNodeCount int (Optional) instanceGroupUrls []string (Optional) management []ContainerNodePoolSpecManagement (Optional) maxPodsPerNode int (Optional) Deprecated name string (Optional) namePrefix string (Optional) Deprecated nodeConfig []ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfig (Optional) nodeCount int (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) version string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ContainerNodePoolSpecAutoscaling (Appears on:ContainerNodePoolSpec) Field Type Description maxNodeCount int minNodeCount int ContainerNodePoolSpecManagement (Appears on:ContainerNodePoolSpec) Field Type Description autoRepair bool (Optional) autoUpgrade bool (Optional) ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfig (Appears on:ContainerNodePoolSpec) Field Type Description diskSizeGb int (Optional) diskType string (Optional) guestAccelerator []ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfigGuestAccelerator (Optional) imageType string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) localSsdCount int (Optional) machineType string (Optional) metadata map[string]string (Optional) minCPUPlatform string (Optional) oauthScopes []string (Optional) preemptible bool (Optional) serviceAccount string (Optional) tags []string (Optional) taint []ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfigTaint (Optional) Deprecated workloadMetadataConfig []ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfigWorkloadMetadataConfig (Optional) Deprecated ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfigGuestAccelerator (Appears on:ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfig) Field Type Description count int type string ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfigTaint (Appears on:ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfig) Field Type Description effect string key string value string ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfigWorkloadMetadataConfig (Appears on:ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfig) Field Type Description nodeMetadata string ContainerNodePoolStatus (Appears on:ContainerNodePool) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>DataflowJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataflowjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataflowjob/</guid><description>DataflowJob Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataflowJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataflowJobSpec status DataflowJobStatus DataflowJobSpec (Appears on:DataflowJob, DataflowJobStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string maxWorkers int (Optional) name string onDelete string (Optional) parameters map[string]string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) state string (Optional) tempGcsLocation string templateGcsPath string zone string (Optional) DataflowJobStatus (Appears on:DataflowJob) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>DataprocCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataproccluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataproccluster/</guid><description>DataprocCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocClusterSpec status DataprocClusterStatus DataprocClusterSpec (Appears on:DataprocCluster, DataprocClusterStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string clusterConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpec) Field Type Description bucket string (Optional) deleteAutogenBucket bool (Optional) Deprecated gceClusterConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigGceClusterConfig (Optional) initializationAction []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigInitializationAction (Optional) masterConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigMasterConfig (Optional) preemptibleWorkerConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigPreemptibleWorkerConfig (Optional) softwareConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigSoftwareConfig (Optional) stagingBucket string (Optional) workerConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigWorkerConfig (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigGceClusterConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig) Field Type Description internalIPOnly bool (Optional) metadata map[string]string (Optional) network string (Optional) serviceAccount string (Optional) serviceAccountScopes []string (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) tags []string (Optional) zone string (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigInitializationAction (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig) Field Type Description script string timeoutSec int (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigMasterConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig) Field Type Description diskConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigMasterConfigDiskConfig (Optional) instanceNames []string (Optional) machineType string (Optional) numInstances int (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigMasterConfigDiskConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigMasterConfig) Field Type Description bootDiskSizeGb int (Optional) bootDiskType string (Optional) numLocalSsds int (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigPreemptibleWorkerConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig) Field Type Description diskConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigPreemptibleWorkerConfigDiskConfig (Optional) instanceNames []string (Optional) numInstances int (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigPreemptibleWorkerConfigDiskConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigPreemptibleWorkerConfig) Field Type Description bootDiskSizeGb int (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigSoftwareConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig) Field Type Description imageVersion string (Optional) overrideProperties map[string]string (Optional) properties map[string]string (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigWorkerConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig) Field Type Description diskConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigWorkerConfigDiskConfig (Optional) instanceNames []string (Optional) machineType string (Optional) numInstances int (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigWorkerConfigDiskConfig (Appears on:DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfigWorkerConfig) Field Type Description bootDiskSizeGb int (Optional) bootDiskType string (Optional) numLocalSsds int (Optional) DataprocClusterStatus (Appears on:DataprocCluster) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>DataprocJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjob/</guid><description>DataprocJob Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocJobSpec status DataprocJobStatus DataprocJobSpec (Appears on:DataprocJob, DataprocJobStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string driverControlsFilesURI string (Optional) Output-only.</description></item><item><title>DnsManagedZone</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsmanagedzone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsmanagedzone/</guid><description>DnsManagedZone Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsManagedZone metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsManagedZoneSpec status DnsManagedZoneStatus DnsManagedZoneSpec (Appears on:DnsManagedZone, DnsManagedZoneStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) dnsName string labels map[string]string (Optional) name string nameServers []string (Optional) project string (Optional) DnsManagedZoneStatus (Appears on:DnsManagedZone) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>DnsRecordSet</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsrecordset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsrecordset/</guid><description>DnsRecordSet Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsRecordSet metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsRecordSetSpec status DnsRecordSetStatus DnsRecordSetSpec (Appears on:DnsRecordSet, DnsRecordSetStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string managedZone string name string project string (Optional) rrdatas []string ttl int type string DnsRecordSetStatus (Appears on:DnsRecordSet) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>EndpointsService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/endpointsservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/endpointsservice/</guid><description>EndpointsService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EndpointsService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EndpointsServiceSpec status EndpointsServiceStatus EndpointsServiceSpec (Appears on:EndpointsService, EndpointsServiceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apis []EndpointsServiceSpecApis (Optional) configID string (Optional) dnsAddress string (Optional) endpoints []EndpointsServiceSpecEndpoints (Optional) grpcConfig string (Optional) openapiConfig string (Optional) project string (Optional) protocOutput string (Optional) Deprecated protocOutputBase64 string (Optional) serviceName string EndpointsServiceSpecApis (Appears on:EndpointsServiceSpec) Field Type Description methods []EndpointsServiceSpecApisMethods (Optional) name string (Optional) syntax string (Optional) version string (Optional) EndpointsServiceSpecApisMethods (Appears on:EndpointsServiceSpecApis) Field Type Description name string (Optional) requestType string (Optional) responseType string (Optional) syntax string (Optional) EndpointsServiceSpecEndpoints (Appears on:EndpointsServiceSpec) Field Type Description address string (Optional) name string (Optional) EndpointsServiceStatus (Appears on:EndpointsService) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>FilestoreInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/filestoreinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/filestoreinstance/</guid><description>FilestoreInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FilestoreInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FilestoreInstanceSpec status FilestoreInstanceStatus FilestoreInstanceSpec (Appears on:FilestoreInstance, FilestoreInstanceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTime string (Optional) description string (Optional) etag string (Optional) fileShares []FilestoreInstanceSpecFileShares labels map[string]string (Optional) name string networks []FilestoreInstanceSpecNetworks project string (Optional) tier string zone string FilestoreInstanceSpecFileShares (Appears on:FilestoreInstanceSpec) Field Type Description capacityGb int name string FilestoreInstanceSpecNetworks (Appears on:FilestoreInstanceSpec) Field Type Description ipAddresses []string (Optional) modes []string network string reservedIPRange string (Optional) FilestoreInstanceStatus (Appears on:FilestoreInstance) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>Folder</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folder/</guid><description>Folder Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Folder metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderSpec status FolderStatus FolderSpec (Appears on:Folder, FolderStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTime string (Optional) displayName string lifecycleState string (Optional) name string (Optional) parent string FolderStatus (Appears on:Folder) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>FolderIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiambinding/</guid><description>FolderIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderIamBindingSpec status FolderIamBindingStatus FolderIamBindingSpec (Appears on:FolderIamBinding, FolderIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) folder string members []string role string FolderIamBindingStatus (Appears on:FolderIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>FolderIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiammember/</guid><description>FolderIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderIamMemberSpec status FolderIamMemberStatus FolderIamMemberSpec (Appears on:FolderIamMember, FolderIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) folder string member string role string FolderIamMemberStatus (Appears on:FolderIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>FolderIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiampolicy/</guid><description>FolderIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderIamPolicySpec status FolderIamPolicyStatus FolderIamPolicySpec (Appears on:FolderIamPolicy, FolderIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) folder string policyData string FolderIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:FolderIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>FolderOrganizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderorganizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderorganizationpolicy/</guid><description>FolderOrganizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderOrganizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderOrganizationPolicySpec status FolderOrganizationPolicyStatus FolderOrganizationPolicySpec (Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicy, FolderOrganizationPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string booleanPolicy []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Optional) constraint string etag string (Optional) folder string listPolicy []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Optional) restorePolicy []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Optional) updateTime string (Optional) version int (Optional) FolderOrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description enforced bool FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description allow []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyAllow (Optional) deny []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyDeny (Optional) suggestedValue string (Optional) FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyAllow (Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy) Field Type Description all bool (Optional) values []string (Optional) FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyDeny (Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy) Field Type Description all bool (Optional) values []string (Optional) FolderOrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description default bool FolderOrganizationPolicyStatus (Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>KmsCryptoKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokey/</guid><description>KmsCryptoKey Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsCryptoKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsCryptoKeySpec status KmsCryptoKeyStatus KmsCryptoKeySpec (Appears on:KmsCryptoKey, KmsCryptoKeyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string keyRing string name string rotationPeriod string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) KmsCryptoKeyStatus (Appears on:KmsCryptoKey) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiambinding/</guid><description>KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingSpec status KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingStatus KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingSpec (Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding, KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cryptoKeyID string etag string (Optional) members []string role string KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingStatus (Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>KmsCryptoKeyIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiammember/</guid><description>KmsCryptoKeyIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsCryptoKeyIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberSpec status KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberStatus KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberSpec (Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamMember, KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cryptoKeyID string etag string (Optional) member string role string KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberStatus (Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRing</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyring/</guid><description>KmsKeyRing Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRing metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingSpec status KmsKeyRingStatus KmsKeyRingSpec (Appears on:KmsKeyRing, KmsKeyRingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) KmsKeyRingStatus (Appears on:KmsKeyRing) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRingIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiambinding/</guid><description>KmsKeyRingIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRingIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingIamBindingSpec status KmsKeyRingIamBindingStatus KmsKeyRingIamBindingSpec (Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamBinding, KmsKeyRingIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) keyRingID string members []string role string KmsKeyRingIamBindingStatus (Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRingIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiammember/</guid><description>KmsKeyRingIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRingIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingIamMemberSpec status KmsKeyRingIamMemberStatus KmsKeyRingIamMemberSpec (Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamMember, KmsKeyRingIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) keyRingID string member string role string KmsKeyRingIamMemberStatus (Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRingIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiampolicy/</guid><description>KmsKeyRingIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRingIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingIamPolicySpec status KmsKeyRingIamPolicyStatus KmsKeyRingIamPolicySpec (Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamPolicy, KmsKeyRingIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) keyRingID string policyData string KmsKeyRingIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingBillingAccountExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingBillingAccountExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingBillingAccountExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingBillingAccountExclusionSpec status LoggingBillingAccountExclusionStatus LoggingBillingAccountExclusionSpec (Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountExclusion, LoggingBillingAccountExclusionStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccount string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string name string LoggingBillingAccountExclusionStatus (Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountExclusion) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingBillingAccountSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountsink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountsink/</guid><description>LoggingBillingAccountSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingBillingAccountSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingBillingAccountSinkSpec status LoggingBillingAccountSinkStatus LoggingBillingAccountSinkSpec (Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountSink, LoggingBillingAccountSinkStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccount string destination string filter string (Optional) name string writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingBillingAccountSinkStatus (Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountSink) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingFolderExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfolderexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfolderexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingFolderExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingFolderExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingFolderExclusionSpec status LoggingFolderExclusionStatus LoggingFolderExclusionSpec (Appears on:LoggingFolderExclusion, LoggingFolderExclusionStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string folder string name string LoggingFolderExclusionStatus (Appears on:LoggingFolderExclusion) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingFolderSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfoldersink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfoldersink/</guid><description>LoggingFolderSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingFolderSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingFolderSinkSpec status LoggingFolderSinkStatus LoggingFolderSinkSpec (Appears on:LoggingFolderSink, LoggingFolderSinkStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string destination string filter string (Optional) folder string includeChildren bool (Optional) name string writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingFolderSinkStatus (Appears on:LoggingFolderSink) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingOrganizationExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingOrganizationExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingOrganizationExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingOrganizationExclusionSpec status LoggingOrganizationExclusionStatus LoggingOrganizationExclusionSpec (Appears on:LoggingOrganizationExclusion, LoggingOrganizationExclusionStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string name string orgID string LoggingOrganizationExclusionStatus (Appears on:LoggingOrganizationExclusion) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingOrganizationSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationsink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationsink/</guid><description>LoggingOrganizationSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingOrganizationSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingOrganizationSinkSpec status LoggingOrganizationSinkStatus LoggingOrganizationSinkSpec (Appears on:LoggingOrganizationSink, LoggingOrganizationSinkStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string destination string filter string (Optional) includeChildren bool (Optional) name string orgID string writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingOrganizationSinkStatus (Appears on:LoggingOrganizationSink) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingProjectExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingProjectExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingProjectExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingProjectExclusionSpec status LoggingProjectExclusionStatus LoggingProjectExclusionSpec (Appears on:LoggingProjectExclusion, LoggingProjectExclusionStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string name string project string (Optional) LoggingProjectExclusionStatus (Appears on:LoggingProjectExclusion) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>LoggingProjectSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectsink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectsink/</guid><description>LoggingProjectSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingProjectSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingProjectSinkSpec status LoggingProjectSinkStatus LoggingProjectSinkSpec (Appears on:LoggingProjectSink, LoggingProjectSinkStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string destination string filter string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) uniqueWriterIdentity bool (Optional) writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingProjectSinkStatus (Appears on:LoggingProjectSink) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>MonitoringAlertPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringalertpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringalertpolicy/</guid><description>MonitoringAlertPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringAlertPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringAlertPolicySpec status MonitoringAlertPolicyStatus MonitoringAlertPolicySpec (Appears on:MonitoringAlertPolicy, MonitoringAlertPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string combiner string conditions []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditions creationRecord []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecCreationRecord (Optional) displayName string enabled bool labels []string (Optional) name string (Optional) notificationChannels []string (Optional) project string (Optional) MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditions (Appears on:MonitoringAlertPolicySpec) Field Type Description conditionAbsent []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsent (Optional) conditionThreshold []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionThreshold (Optional) displayName string name string (Optional) MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsent (Appears on:MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditions) Field Type Description aggregations []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsentAggregations (Optional) duration string filter string (Optional) trigger []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsentTrigger (Optional) MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsentAggregations (Appears on:MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsent) Field Type Description alignmentPeriod string (Optional) crossSeriesReducer string (Optional) groupByFields []string (Optional) perSeriesAligner string (Optional) MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsentTrigger (Appears on:MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditionsConditionAbsent) Field Type Description count int (Optional) percent encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>MonitoringGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringgroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringgroup/</guid><description>MonitoringGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringGroupSpec status MonitoringGroupStatus MonitoringGroupSpec (Appears on:MonitoringGroup, MonitoringGroupStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string displayName string filter string isCluster bool (Optional) name string (Optional) parentName string (Optional) project string (Optional) MonitoringGroupStatus (Appears on:MonitoringGroup) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>MonitoringNotificationChannel</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringnotificationchannel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringnotificationchannel/</guid><description>MonitoringNotificationChannel Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringNotificationChannel metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringNotificationChannelSpec status MonitoringNotificationChannelStatus MonitoringNotificationChannelSpec (Appears on:MonitoringNotificationChannel, MonitoringNotificationChannelStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) displayName string enabled bool (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string (Optional) project string (Optional) type string userLabels map[string]string (Optional) verificationStatus string (Optional) MonitoringNotificationChannelStatus (Appears on:MonitoringNotificationChannel) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringuptimecheckconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringuptimecheckconfig/</guid><description>MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigSpec status MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigStatus MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigSpec (Appears on:MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig, MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiambinding/</guid><description>OrganizationIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamBindingSpec status OrganizationIamBindingStatus OrganizationIamBindingSpec (Appears on:OrganizationIamBinding, OrganizationIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string orgID string role string OrganizationIamBindingStatus (Appears on:OrganizationIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamCustomRole</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiamcustomrole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiamcustomrole/</guid><description>OrganizationIamCustomRole Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamCustomRole metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamCustomRoleSpec status OrganizationIamCustomRoleStatus OrganizationIamCustomRoleSpec (Appears on:OrganizationIamCustomRole, OrganizationIamCustomRoleStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string deleted bool (Optional) Deprecated description string (Optional) orgID string permissions []string roleID string stage string (Optional) title string OrganizationIamCustomRoleStatus (Appears on:OrganizationIamCustomRole) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiammember/</guid><description>OrganizationIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamMemberSpec status OrganizationIamMemberStatus OrganizationIamMemberSpec (Appears on:OrganizationIamMember, OrganizationIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string orgID string role string OrganizationIamMemberStatus (Appears on:OrganizationIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiampolicy/</guid><description>OrganizationIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamPolicySpec status OrganizationIamPolicyStatus OrganizationIamPolicySpec (Appears on:OrganizationIamPolicy, OrganizationIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) orgID string policyData string OrganizationIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:OrganizationIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>OrganizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationpolicy/</guid><description>OrganizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationPolicySpec status OrganizationPolicyStatus OrganizationPolicySpec (Appears on:OrganizationPolicy, OrganizationPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string booleanPolicy []OrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Optional) constraint string etag string (Optional) listPolicy []OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Optional) orgID string restorePolicy []OrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Optional) updateTime string (Optional) version int (Optional) OrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Appears on:OrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description enforced bool OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Appears on:OrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description allow []OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyAllow (Optional) deny []OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyDeny (Optional) suggestedValue string (Optional) OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyAllow (Appears on:OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy) Field Type Description all bool (Optional) values []string (Optional) OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyDeny (Appears on:OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy) Field Type Description all bool (Optional) values []string (Optional) OrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Appears on:OrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description default bool OrganizationPolicyStatus (Appears on:OrganizationPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>Project</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/project/</guid><description>Project Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Project metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectSpec status ProjectStatus ProjectSpec (Appears on:Project, ProjectStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appEngine []ProjectSpecAppEngine (Optional) Deprecated autoCreateNetwork bool (Optional) billingAccount string (Optional) folderID string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string number string (Optional) orgID string (Optional) projectID string skipDelete bool (Optional) ProjectSpecAppEngine (Appears on:ProjectSpec) Field Type Description authDomain string (Optional) codeBucket string (Optional) defaultBucket string (Optional) defaultHostname string (Optional) featureSettings []ProjectSpecAppEngineFeatureSettings (Optional) gcrDomain string (Optional) locationID string (Optional) name string (Optional) servingStatus string (Optional) urlDispatchRule []ProjectSpecAppEngineUrlDispatchRule (Optional) ProjectSpecAppEngineFeatureSettings (Appears on:ProjectSpecAppEngine) Field Type Description splitHealthChecks bool (Optional) ProjectSpecAppEngineUrlDispatchRule (Appears on:ProjectSpecAppEngine) Field Type Description domain string (Optional) path string (Optional) service string (Optional) ProjectStatus (Appears on:Project) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiambinding/</guid><description>ProjectIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamBindingSpec status ProjectIamBindingStatus ProjectIamBindingSpec (Appears on:ProjectIamBinding, ProjectIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string ProjectIamBindingStatus (Appears on:ProjectIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamCustomRole</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiamcustomrole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiamcustomrole/</guid><description>ProjectIamCustomRole Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamCustomRole metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamCustomRoleSpec status ProjectIamCustomRoleStatus ProjectIamCustomRoleSpec (Appears on:ProjectIamCustomRole, ProjectIamCustomRoleStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string deleted bool (Optional) Deprecated description string (Optional) permissions []string project string (Optional) roleID string stage string (Optional) title string ProjectIamCustomRoleStatus (Appears on:ProjectIamCustomRole) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiammember/</guid><description>ProjectIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamMemberSpec status ProjectIamMemberStatus ProjectIamMemberSpec (Appears on:ProjectIamMember, ProjectIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string ProjectIamMemberStatus (Appears on:ProjectIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiampolicy/</guid><description>ProjectIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamPolicySpec status ProjectIamPolicyStatus ProjectIamPolicySpec (Appears on:ProjectIamPolicy, ProjectIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string authoritative bool (Optional) Deprecated disableProject bool (Optional) Deprecated etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) restorePolicy string (Optional) Deprecated ProjectIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:ProjectIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectOrganizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectorganizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectorganizationpolicy/</guid><description>ProjectOrganizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectOrganizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectOrganizationPolicySpec status ProjectOrganizationPolicyStatus ProjectOrganizationPolicySpec (Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicy, ProjectOrganizationPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string booleanPolicy []ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Optional) constraint string etag string (Optional) listPolicy []ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Optional) project string restorePolicy []ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Optional) updateTime string (Optional) version int (Optional) ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description enforced bool ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description allow []ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyAllow (Optional) deny []ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyDeny (Optional) suggestedValue string (Optional) ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyAllow (Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy) Field Type Description all bool (Optional) values []string (Optional) ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicyDeny (Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy) Field Type Description all bool (Optional) values []string (Optional) ProjectOrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicySpec) Field Type Description default bool ProjectOrganizationPolicyStatus (Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservice/</guid><description>ProjectService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectServiceSpec status ProjectServiceStatus ProjectServiceSpec (Appears on:ProjectService, ProjectServiceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string disableOnDestroy bool (Optional) project string (Optional) service string ProjectServiceStatus (Appears on:ProjectService) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectServices</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservices/</guid><description>ProjectServices Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectServices metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectServicesSpec status ProjectServicesStatus ProjectServicesSpec (Appears on:ProjectServices, ProjectServicesStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string disableOnDestroy bool (Optional) project string (Optional) services []string ProjectServicesStatus (Appears on:ProjectServices) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ProjectUsageExportBucket</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectusageexportbucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectusageexportbucket/</guid><description>ProjectUsageExportBucket Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectUsageExportBucket metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectUsageExportBucketSpec status ProjectUsageExportBucketStatus ProjectUsageExportBucketSpec (Appears on:ProjectUsageExportBucket, ProjectUsageExportBucketStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucketName string prefix string (Optional) project string (Optional) ProjectUsageExportBucketStatus (Appears on:ProjectUsageExportBucket) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscription</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscription/</guid><description>PubsubSubscription Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscription metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionSpec status PubsubSubscriptionStatus PubsubSubscriptionSpec (Appears on:PubsubSubscription, PubsubSubscriptionStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string ackDeadlineSeconds int (Optional) name string path string (Optional) project string (Optional) pushConfig []PubsubSubscriptionSpecPushConfig (Optional) topic string PubsubSubscriptionSpecPushConfig (Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionSpec) Field Type Description attributes map[string]string (Optional) pushEndpoint string PubsubSubscriptionStatus (Appears on:PubsubSubscription) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniambinding/</guid><description>PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingSpec status PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingStatus PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingSpec (Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding, PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string subscription string PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingStatus (Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscriptionIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniammember/</guid><description>PubsubSubscriptionIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscriptionIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberSpec status PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberStatus PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberSpec (Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamMember, PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string subscription string PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberStatus (Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniampolicy/</guid><description>PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicySpec status PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicyStatus PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicySpec (Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy, PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) subscription string PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopic</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopic/</guid><description>PubsubTopic Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopic metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicSpec status PubsubTopicStatus PubsubTopicSpec (Appears on:PubsubTopic, PubsubTopicStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string project string (Optional) PubsubTopicStatus (Appears on:PubsubTopic) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopicIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciambinding/</guid><description>PubsubTopicIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopicIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicIamBindingSpec status PubsubTopicIamBindingStatus PubsubTopicIamBindingSpec (Appears on:PubsubTopicIamBinding, PubsubTopicIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string topic string PubsubTopicIamBindingStatus (Appears on:PubsubTopicIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopicIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciammember/</guid><description>PubsubTopicIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopicIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicIamMemberSpec status PubsubTopicIamMemberStatus PubsubTopicIamMemberSpec (Appears on:PubsubTopicIamMember, PubsubTopicIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string topic string PubsubTopicIamMemberStatus (Appears on:PubsubTopicIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopicIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciampolicy/</guid><description>PubsubTopicIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopicIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicIamPolicySpec status PubsubTopicIamPolicyStatus PubsubTopicIamPolicySpec (Appears on:PubsubTopicIamPolicy, PubsubTopicIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) topic string PubsubTopicIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:PubsubTopicIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>RedisInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/redisinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/redisinstance/</guid><description>RedisInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RedisInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RedisInstanceSpec status RedisInstanceStatus RedisInstanceSpec (Appears on:RedisInstance, RedisInstanceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string alternativeLocationID string (Optional) authorizedNetwork string (Optional) createTime string (Optional) currentLocationID string (Optional) displayName string (Optional) host string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) locationID string (Optional) memorySizeGb int name string port int (Optional) project string (Optional) redisConfigs map[string]string (Optional) redisVersion string (Optional) region string (Optional) reservedIPRange string (Optional) tier string (Optional) RedisInstanceStatus (Appears on:RedisInstance) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ResourceManagerLien</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/resourcemanagerlien/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/resourcemanagerlien/</guid><description>ResourceManagerLien Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ResourceManagerLien metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ResourceManagerLienSpec status ResourceManagerLienStatus ResourceManagerLienSpec (Appears on:ResourceManagerLien, ResourceManagerLienStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTime string (Optional) name string (Optional) origin string parent string reason string restrictions []string ResourceManagerLienStatus (Appears on:ResourceManagerLien) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>RuntimeconfigConfig</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfig/</guid><description>RuntimeconfigConfig Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RuntimeconfigConfig metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RuntimeconfigConfigSpec status RuntimeconfigConfigStatus RuntimeconfigConfigSpec (Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfig, RuntimeconfigConfigStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) RuntimeconfigConfigStatus (Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfig) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>RuntimeconfigVariable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigvariable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigvariable/</guid><description>RuntimeconfigVariable Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RuntimeconfigVariable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RuntimeconfigVariableSpec status RuntimeconfigVariableStatus RuntimeconfigVariableSpec (Appears on:RuntimeconfigVariable, RuntimeconfigVariableStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string parent string project string (Optional) text string (Optional) updateTime string (Optional) value string (Optional) RuntimeconfigVariableStatus (Appears on:RuntimeconfigVariable) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccount/</guid><description>ServiceAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountSpec status ServiceAccountStatus ServiceAccountSpec (Appears on:ServiceAccount, ServiceAccountStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountID string displayName string (Optional) email string (Optional) name string (Optional) policyData string (Optional) Deprecated project string (Optional) uniqueID string (Optional) ServiceAccountStatus (Appears on:ServiceAccount) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiambinding/</guid><description>ServiceAccountIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountIamBindingSpec status ServiceAccountIamBindingStatus ServiceAccountIamBindingSpec (Appears on:ServiceAccountIamBinding, ServiceAccountIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string role string serviceAccountID string ServiceAccountIamBindingStatus (Appears on:ServiceAccountIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiammember/</guid><description>ServiceAccountIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountIamMemberSpec status ServiceAccountIamMemberStatus ServiceAccountIamMemberSpec (Appears on:ServiceAccountIamMember, ServiceAccountIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string role string serviceAccountID string ServiceAccountIamMemberStatus (Appears on:ServiceAccountIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiampolicy/</guid><description>ServiceAccountIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountIamPolicySpec status ServiceAccountIamPolicyStatus ServiceAccountIamPolicySpec (Appears on:ServiceAccountIamPolicy, ServiceAccountIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string serviceAccountID string ServiceAccountIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:ServiceAccountIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountkey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountkey/</guid><description>ServiceAccountKey Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountKeySpec status ServiceAccountKeyStatus ServiceAccountKeySpec (Appears on:ServiceAccountKey, ServiceAccountKeyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SourcerepoRepository</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepository/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepository/</guid><description>SourcerepoRepository Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SourcerepoRepository metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SourcerepoRepositorySpec status SourcerepoRepositoryStatus SourcerepoRepositorySpec (Appears on:SourcerepoRepository, SourcerepoRepositoryStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string project string (Optional) size int (Optional) url string (Optional) SourcerepoRepositoryStatus (Appears on:SourcerepoRepository) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabase/</guid><description>SpannerDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseSpec status SpannerDatabaseStatus SpannerDatabaseSpec (Appears on:SpannerDatabase, SpannerDatabaseStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string ddl []string (Optional) instance string name string project string (Optional) state string (Optional) SpannerDatabaseStatus (Appears on:SpannerDatabase) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabaseIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiambinding/</guid><description>SpannerDatabaseIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabaseIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseIamBindingSpec status SpannerDatabaseIamBindingStatus SpannerDatabaseIamBindingSpec (Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamBinding, SpannerDatabaseIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string database string etag string (Optional) instance string members []string project string (Optional) role string SpannerDatabaseIamBindingStatus (Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabaseIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiammember/</guid><description>SpannerDatabaseIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabaseIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseIamMemberSpec status SpannerDatabaseIamMemberStatus SpannerDatabaseIamMemberSpec (Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamMember, SpannerDatabaseIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string database string etag string (Optional) instance string member string project string (Optional) role string SpannerDatabaseIamMemberStatus (Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiampolicy/</guid><description>SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseIamPolicySpec status SpannerDatabaseIamPolicyStatus SpannerDatabaseIamPolicySpec (Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy, SpannerDatabaseIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string database string etag string (Optional) instance string policyData string project string (Optional) SpannerDatabaseIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstance/</guid><description>SpannerInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceSpec status SpannerInstanceStatus SpannerInstanceSpec (Appears on:SpannerInstance, SpannerInstanceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string config string displayName string labels map[string]string (Optional) name string (Optional) numNodes int (Optional) project string (Optional) state string (Optional) SpannerInstanceStatus (Appears on:SpannerInstance) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstanceIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiambinding/</guid><description>SpannerInstanceIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstanceIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceIamBindingSpec status SpannerInstanceIamBindingStatus SpannerInstanceIamBindingSpec (Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamBinding, SpannerInstanceIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instance string members []string project string (Optional) role string SpannerInstanceIamBindingStatus (Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstanceIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiammember/</guid><description>SpannerInstanceIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstanceIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceIamMemberSpec status SpannerInstanceIamMemberStatus SpannerInstanceIamMemberSpec (Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamMember, SpannerInstanceIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instance string member string project string (Optional) role string SpannerInstanceIamMemberStatus (Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstanceIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiampolicy/</guid><description>SpannerInstanceIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstanceIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceIamPolicySpec status SpannerInstanceIamPolicyStatus SpannerInstanceIamPolicySpec (Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamPolicy, SpannerInstanceIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instance string policyData string project string (Optional) SpannerInstanceIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SqlDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabase/</guid><description>SqlDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlDatabaseSpec status SqlDatabaseStatus SqlDatabaseSpec (Appears on:SqlDatabase, SqlDatabaseStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string charset string (Optional) collation string (Optional) instance string name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) SqlDatabaseStatus (Appears on:SqlDatabase) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>SqlDatabaseInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabaseinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabaseinstance/</guid><description>SqlDatabaseInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlDatabaseInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlDatabaseInstanceSpec status SqlDatabaseInstanceStatus SqlDatabaseInstanceSpec (Appears on:SqlDatabaseInstance, SqlDatabaseInstanceStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlSSLCert</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqlsslcert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqlsslcert/</guid><description>SqlSSLCert Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlSSLCert metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlSSLCertSpec status SqlSSLCertStatus SqlSSLCertSpec (Appears on:SqlSSLCert, SqlSSLCertStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlUser</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqluser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqluser/</guid><description>SqlUser Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlUser metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlUserSpec status SqlUserStatus SqlUserSpec (Appears on:SqlUser, SqlUserStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucket</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucket/</guid><description>StorageBucket Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucket metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketSpec status StorageBucketStatus StorageBucketSpec (Appears on:StorageBucket, StorageBucketStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cors []StorageBucketSpecCors (Optional) encryption []StorageBucketSpecEncryption (Optional) forceDestroy bool (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lifecycleRule []StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRule (Optional) location string (Optional) logging []StorageBucketSpecLogging (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) storageClass string (Optional) url string (Optional) versioning []StorageBucketSpecVersioning (Optional) website []StorageBucketSpecWebsite (Optional) StorageBucketSpecCors (Appears on:StorageBucketSpec) Field Type Description maxAgeSeconds int (Optional) method []string (Optional) origin []string (Optional) responseHeader []string (Optional) StorageBucketSpecEncryption (Appears on:StorageBucketSpec) Field Type Description defaultKmsKeyName string StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRule (Appears on:StorageBucketSpec) Field Type Description action []StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRuleAction condition []StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRuleCondition StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRuleAction (Appears on:StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRule) Field Type Description storageClass string (Optional) type string StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRuleCondition (Appears on:StorageBucketSpecLifecycleRule) Field Type Description age int (Optional) createdBefore string (Optional) isLive bool (Optional) matchesStorageClass []string (Optional) numNewerVersions int (Optional) StorageBucketSpecLogging (Appears on:StorageBucketSpec) Field Type Description logBucket string logObjectPrefix string (Optional) StorageBucketSpecVersioning (Appears on:StorageBucketSpec) Field Type Description enabled bool (Optional) StorageBucketSpecWebsite (Appears on:StorageBucketSpec) Field Type Description mainPageSuffix string (Optional) notFoundPage string (Optional) StorageBucketStatus (Appears on:StorageBucket) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketACL</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketacl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketacl/</guid><description>StorageBucketACL Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketACL metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketACLSpec status StorageBucketACLStatus StorageBucketACLSpec (Appears on:StorageBucketACL, StorageBucketACLStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string defaultACL string (Optional) predefinedACL string (Optional) roleEntity []string (Optional) StorageBucketACLStatus (Appears on:StorageBucketACL) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiambinding/</guid><description>StorageBucketIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketIamBindingSpec status StorageBucketIamBindingStatus StorageBucketIamBindingSpec (Appears on:StorageBucketIamBinding, StorageBucketIamBindingStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string etag string (Optional) members []string role string StorageBucketIamBindingStatus (Appears on:StorageBucketIamBinding) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiammember/</guid><description>StorageBucketIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketIamMemberSpec status StorageBucketIamMemberStatus StorageBucketIamMemberSpec (Appears on:StorageBucketIamMember, StorageBucketIamMemberStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string etag string (Optional) member string role string StorageBucketIamMemberStatus (Appears on:StorageBucketIamMember) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiampolicy/</guid><description>StorageBucketIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketIamPolicySpec status StorageBucketIamPolicyStatus StorageBucketIamPolicySpec (Appears on:StorageBucketIamPolicy, StorageBucketIamPolicyStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string etag string (Optional) policyData string StorageBucketIamPolicyStatus (Appears on:StorageBucketIamPolicy) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketObject</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketobject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketobject/</guid><description>StorageBucketObject Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketObject metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketObjectSpec status StorageBucketObjectStatus StorageBucketObjectSpec (Appears on:StorageBucketObject, StorageBucketObjectStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string cacheControl string (Optional) content string (Optional) contentDisposition string (Optional) contentEncoding string (Optional) contentLanguage string (Optional) contentType string (Optional) crc32c string (Optional) detectMd5hash string (Optional) md5hash string (Optional) name string source string (Optional) storageClass string (Optional) StorageBucketObjectStatus (Appears on:StorageBucketObject) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectaccesscontrol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectaccesscontrol/</guid><description>StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlSpec status StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlStatus StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlSpec (Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl, StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string domain string (Optional) email string (Optional) entity string entityID string (Optional) generation int (Optional) object string (Optional) projectTeam []StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlSpecProjectTeam (Optional) role string StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlSpecProjectTeam (Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlSpec) Field Type Description projectNumber string (Optional) team string (Optional) StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlStatus (Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageDefaultObjectACL</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectacl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectacl/</guid><description>StorageDefaultObjectACL Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageDefaultObjectACL metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageDefaultObjectACLSpec status StorageDefaultObjectACLStatus StorageDefaultObjectACLSpec (Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectACL, StorageDefaultObjectACLStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string roleEntity []string (Optional) StorageDefaultObjectACLStatus (Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectACL) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageNotification</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagenotification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagenotification/</guid><description>StorageNotification Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageNotification metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageNotificationSpec status StorageNotificationStatus StorageNotificationSpec (Appears on:StorageNotification, StorageNotificationStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string customAttributes map[string]string (Optional) eventTypes []string (Optional) objectNamePrefix string (Optional) payloadFormat string selfLink string (Optional) topic string StorageNotificationStatus (Appears on:StorageNotification) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageObjectAccessControl</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectaccesscontrol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectaccesscontrol/</guid><description>StorageObjectAccessControl Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageObjectAccessControl metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageObjectAccessControlSpec status StorageObjectAccessControlStatus StorageObjectAccessControlSpec (Appears on:StorageObjectAccessControl, StorageObjectAccessControlStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string domain string (Optional) email string (Optional) entity string entityID string (Optional) generation int (Optional) object string projectTeam []StorageObjectAccessControlSpecProjectTeam (Optional) role string StorageObjectAccessControlSpecProjectTeam (Appears on:StorageObjectAccessControlSpec) Field Type Description projectNumber string (Optional) team string (Optional) StorageObjectAccessControlStatus (Appears on:StorageObjectAccessControl) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item><item><title>StorageObjectACL</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectacl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectacl/</guid><description>StorageObjectACL Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageObjectACL metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageObjectACLSpec status StorageObjectACLStatus StorageObjectACLSpec (Appears on:StorageObjectACL, StorageObjectACLStatus) Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucket string object string predefinedACL string (Optional) roleEntity []string (Optional) StorageObjectACLStatus (Appears on:StorageObjectACL) Field Type Description observedGeneration int64 (Optional) Resource generation, which is updated on mutation by the API Server.</description></item></channel></rss>