<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | Linode on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | Linode on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Domain</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/domain/</guid><description>Domain Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Domain metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DomainSpec status DomainStatus DomainSpec Appears on:Domain, DomainStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string axfrIPS []string (Optional) The list of IPs that may perform a zone transfer for this Domain.</description></item><item><title>DomainRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/domainrecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/domainrecord/</guid><description>DomainRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DomainRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DomainRecordSpec status DomainRecordStatus DomainRecordSpec Appears on:DomainRecord, DomainRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string domainID int The ID of the Domain to access.</description></item><item><title>Image</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/image/</guid><description>Image Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Image metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ImageSpec status ImageStatus ImageSpec Appears on:Image, ImageStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string created string (Optional) When this Image was created.</description></item><item><title>Instance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/instance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/instance/</guid><description>Instance Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Instance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec InstanceSpec status InstanceStatus InstanceSpec Appears on:Instance, InstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Nodebalancer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/nodebalancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/nodebalancer/</guid><description>Nodebalancer Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Nodebalancer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NodebalancerSpec status NodebalancerStatus NodebalancerSpec Appears on:Nodebalancer, NodebalancerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string clientConnThrottle int (Optional) Throttle connections per second (0-20).</description></item><item><title>NodebalancerConfig</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/nodebalancerconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/nodebalancerconfig/</guid><description>NodebalancerConfig Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NodebalancerConfig metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NodebalancerConfigSpec status NodebalancerConfigStatus NodebalancerConfigSpec Appears on:NodebalancerConfig, NodebalancerConfigStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>NodebalancerNode</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/nodebalancernode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/nodebalancernode/</guid><description>NodebalancerNode Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NodebalancerNode metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NodebalancerNodeSpec status NodebalancerNodeStatus NodebalancerNodeSpec Appears on:NodebalancerNode, NodebalancerNodeStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string address string The private IP Address and port (IP:PORT) where this backend can be reached.</description></item><item><title>Rdns</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/rdns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/rdns/</guid><description>Rdns Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Rdns metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RdnsSpec status RdnsStatus RdnsSpec Appears on:Rdns, RdnsStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string address string The public Linode IPv4 or IPv6 address to operate on.</description></item><item><title>Sshkey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/sshkey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/sshkey/</guid><description>Sshkey Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Sshkey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SshkeySpec status SshkeyStatus SshkeySpec Appears on:Sshkey, SshkeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string created string (Optional) The date this key was added.</description></item><item><title>Stackscript</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/stackscript/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/stackscript/</guid><description>Stackscript Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Stackscript metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StackscriptSpec status StackscriptStatus StackscriptSpec Appears on:Stackscript, StackscriptStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string created string (Optional) The date this StackScript was created.</description></item><item><title>Token</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/token/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/token/</guid><description>Token Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Token metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec TokenSpec status TokenStatus TokenSpec Appears on:Token, TokenStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string created string (Optional) The date and time this token was created.</description></item><item><title>Volume</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/volume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/linode.kubeform.com/volume/</guid><description>Volume Field Type Description apiVersion string linode.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Volume metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VolumeSpec status VolumeStatus VolumeSpec Appears on:Volume, VolumeStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string filesystemPath string (Optional) The full filesystem path for the Volume based on the Volume&amp;rsquo;s label.</description></item></channel></rss>