<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | Google Cloud on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | Google Cloud on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AccessContextManagerAccessLevel</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/accesscontextmanageraccesslevel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/accesscontextmanageraccesslevel/</guid><description>AccessContextManagerAccessLevel Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AccessContextManagerAccessLevel metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AccessContextManagerAccessLevelSpec status AccessContextManagerAccessLevelStatus AccessContextManagerAccessLevelSpec Appears on:AccessContextManagerAccessLevel, AccessContextManagerAccessLevelStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string basic []AccessContextManagerAccessLevelSpecBasic (Optional) description string (Optional) name string parent string title string AccessContextManagerAccessLevelSpecBasic Appears on:AccessContextManagerAccessLevelSpec</description></item><item><title>AccessContextManagerAccessPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/accesscontextmanageraccesspolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/accesscontextmanageraccesspolicy/</guid><description>AccessContextManagerAccessPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AccessContextManagerAccessPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AccessContextManagerAccessPolicySpec status AccessContextManagerAccessPolicyStatus AccessContextManagerAccessPolicySpec Appears on:AccessContextManagerAccessPolicy, AccessContextManagerAccessPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTime string (Optional) name string (Optional) parent string title string updateTime string (Optional) AccessContextManagerAccessPolicyStatus Appears on:AccessContextManagerAccessPolicy</description></item><item><title>AccessContextManagerServicePerimeter</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/accesscontextmanagerserviceperimeter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/accesscontextmanagerserviceperimeter/</guid><description>AccessContextManagerServicePerimeter Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AccessContextManagerServicePerimeter metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AccessContextManagerServicePerimeterSpec status AccessContextManagerServicePerimeterStatus AccessContextManagerServicePerimeterSpec Appears on:AccessContextManagerServicePerimeter, AccessContextManagerServicePerimeterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTime string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string parent string perimeterType string (Optional) status []AccessContextManagerServicePerimeterSpecStatus (Optional) title string updateTime string (Optional) AccessContextManagerServicePerimeterSpecStatus Appears on:AccessContextManagerServicePerimeterSpec</description></item><item><title>AppEngineApplication</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appengineapplication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appengineapplication/</guid><description>AppEngineApplication Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppEngineApplication metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppEngineApplicationSpec status AppEngineApplicationStatus AppEngineApplicationSpec Appears on:AppEngineApplication, AppEngineApplicationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string (Optional) authDomain string (Optional) codeBucket string (Optional) defaultBucket string (Optional) defaultHostname string (Optional) featureSettings []AppEngineApplicationSpecFeatureSettings (Optional) gcrDomain string (Optional) locationID string name string (Optional) project string (Optional) servingStatus string (Optional) urlDispatchRule []AppEngineApplicationSpecUrlDispatchRule (Optional) AppEngineApplicationSpecFeatureSettings Appears on:AppEngineApplicationSpec</description></item><item><title>AppEngineDomainMapping</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appenginedomainmapping/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appenginedomainmapping/</guid><description>AppEngineDomainMapping Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppEngineDomainMapping metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppEngineDomainMappingSpec status AppEngineDomainMappingStatus AppEngineDomainMappingSpec Appears on:AppEngineDomainMapping, AppEngineDomainMappingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string domainName string name string (Optional) overrideStrategy string (Optional) project string (Optional) resourceRecords []AppEngineDomainMappingSpecResourceRecords (Optional) sslSettings []AppEngineDomainMappingSpecSslSettings (Optional) AppEngineDomainMappingSpecResourceRecords Appears on:AppEngineDomainMappingSpec</description></item><item><title>AppEngineFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appenginefirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appenginefirewallrule/</guid><description>AppEngineFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppEngineFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppEngineFirewallRuleSpec status AppEngineFirewallRuleStatus AppEngineFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:AppEngineFirewallRule, AppEngineFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string action string description string (Optional) priority int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) sourceRange string AppEngineFirewallRuleStatus Appears on:AppEngineFirewallRule</description></item><item><title>AppEngineStandardAppVersion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appenginestandardappversion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/appenginestandardappversion/</guid><description>AppEngineStandardAppVersion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppEngineStandardAppVersion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpec status AppEngineStandardAppVersionStatus AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpec Appears on:AppEngineStandardAppVersion, AppEngineStandardAppVersionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string deployment []AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpecDeployment (Optional) entrypoint []AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpecEntrypoint (Optional) envVariables map[string]string (Optional) handlers []AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpecHandlers (Optional) libraries []AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpecLibraries (Optional) name string (Optional) noopOnDestroy bool (Optional) project string (Optional) runtime string runtimeAPIVersion string (Optional) service string (Optional) threadsafe bool (Optional) versionID string (Optional) AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpecDeployment Appears on:AppEngineStandardAppVersionSpec</description></item><item><title>BigqueryDataset</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerydataset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerydataset/</guid><description>BigqueryDataset Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigqueryDataset metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigqueryDatasetSpec status BigqueryDatasetStatus BigqueryDatasetSpec Appears on:BigqueryDataset, BigqueryDatasetStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string access []BigqueryDatasetSpecAccess (Optional) creationTime int64 (Optional) datasetID string defaultEncryptionConfiguration []BigqueryDatasetSpecDefaultEncryptionConfiguration (Optional) defaultPartitionExpirationMs int64 (Optional) defaultTableExpirationMs int64 (Optional) deleteContentsOnDestroy bool (Optional) description string (Optional) etag string (Optional) friendlyName string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lastModifiedTime int64 (Optional) location string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) BigqueryDatasetSpecAccess Appears on:BigqueryDatasetSpec</description></item><item><title>BigqueryDataTransferConfig</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerydatatransferconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerydatatransferconfig/</guid><description>BigqueryDataTransferConfig Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigqueryDataTransferConfig metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigqueryDataTransferConfigSpec status BigqueryDataTransferConfigStatus BigqueryDataTransferConfigSpec Appears on:BigqueryDataTransferConfig, BigqueryDataTransferConfigStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string dataRefreshWindowDays int64 (Optional) dataSourceID string destinationDatasetID string disabled bool (Optional) displayName string location string (Optional) name string (Optional) params map[string]string project string (Optional) schedule string (Optional) BigqueryDataTransferConfigStatus Appears on:BigqueryDataTransferConfig</description></item><item><title>BigqueryTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerytable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigquerytable/</guid><description>BigqueryTable Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigqueryTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigqueryTableSpec status BigqueryTableStatus BigqueryTableSpec Appears on:BigqueryTable, BigqueryTableStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string clustering []string (Optional) creationTime int64 (Optional) datasetID string description string (Optional) etag string (Optional) expirationTime int64 (Optional) externalDataConfiguration []BigqueryTableSpecExternalDataConfiguration (Optional) friendlyName string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lastModifiedTime int64 (Optional) location string (Optional) numBytes int64 (Optional) numLongTermBytes int64 (Optional) numRows int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) schema string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) tableID string timePartitioning []BigqueryTableSpecTimePartitioning (Optional) type string (Optional) view []BigqueryTableSpecView (Optional) BigqueryTableSpecExternalDataConfiguration Appears on:BigqueryTableSpec</description></item><item><title>BigtableAppProfile</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableappprofile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableappprofile/</guid><description>BigtableAppProfile Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableAppProfile metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableAppProfileSpec status BigtableAppProfileStatus BigtableAppProfileSpec Appears on:BigtableAppProfile, BigtableAppProfileStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appProfileID string description string (Optional) ignoreWarnings bool (Optional) instance string (Optional) multiClusterRoutingUseAny bool (Optional) name string (Optional) project string (Optional) singleClusterRouting []BigtableAppProfileSpecSingleClusterRouting (Optional) BigtableAppProfileSpecSingleClusterRouting Appears on:BigtableAppProfileSpec</description></item><item><title>BigtableGcPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtablegcpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtablegcpolicy/</guid><description>BigtableGcPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableGcPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableGcPolicySpec status BigtableGcPolicyStatus BigtableGcPolicySpec Appears on:BigtableGcPolicy, BigtableGcPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string columnFamily string instanceName string maxAge []BigtableGcPolicySpecMaxAge (Optional) maxVersion []BigtableGcPolicySpecMaxVersion (Optional) mode string (Optional) project string (Optional) table string BigtableGcPolicySpecMaxAge Appears on:BigtableGcPolicySpec</description></item><item><title>BigtableInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstance/</guid><description>BigtableInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableInstanceSpec status BigtableInstanceStatus BigtableInstanceSpec Appears on:BigtableInstance, BigtableInstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cluster []BigtableInstanceSpecCluster (Optional) displayName string (Optional) instanceType string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) BigtableInstanceSpecCluster Appears on:BigtableInstanceSpec</description></item><item><title>BigtableInstanceIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstanceiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstanceiambinding/</guid><description>BigtableInstanceIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableInstanceIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableInstanceIamBindingSpec status BigtableInstanceIamBindingStatus BigtableInstanceIamBindingSpec Appears on:BigtableInstanceIamBinding, BigtableInstanceIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instance string members []string project string (Optional) role string BigtableInstanceIamBindingStatus Appears on:BigtableInstanceIamBinding</description></item><item><title>BigtableInstanceIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstanceiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstanceiammember/</guid><description>BigtableInstanceIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableInstanceIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableInstanceIamMemberSpec status BigtableInstanceIamMemberStatus BigtableInstanceIamMemberSpec Appears on:BigtableInstanceIamMember, BigtableInstanceIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instance string member string project string (Optional) role string BigtableInstanceIamMemberStatus Appears on:BigtableInstanceIamMember</description></item><item><title>BigtableInstanceIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstanceiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtableinstanceiampolicy/</guid><description>BigtableInstanceIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableInstanceIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableInstanceIamPolicySpec status BigtableInstanceIamPolicyStatus BigtableInstanceIamPolicySpec Appears on:BigtableInstanceIamPolicy, BigtableInstanceIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instance string policyData string project string (Optional) BigtableInstanceIamPolicyStatus Appears on:BigtableInstanceIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>BigtableTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtabletable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/bigtabletable/</guid><description>BigtableTable Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BigtableTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BigtableTableSpec status BigtableTableStatus BigtableTableSpec Appears on:BigtableTable, BigtableTableStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string columnFamily []BigtableTableSpecColumnFamily (Optional) instanceName string name string project string (Optional) splitKeys []string (Optional) BigtableTableSpecColumnFamily Appears on:BigtableTableSpec</description></item><item><title>BillingAccountIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiambinding/</guid><description>BillingAccountIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BillingAccountIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BillingAccountIamBindingSpec status BillingAccountIamBindingStatus BillingAccountIamBindingSpec Appears on:BillingAccountIamBinding, BillingAccountIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccountID string etag string (Optional) members []string role string BillingAccountIamBindingStatus Appears on:BillingAccountIamBinding</description></item><item><title>BillingAccountIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiammember/</guid><description>BillingAccountIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BillingAccountIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BillingAccountIamMemberSpec status BillingAccountIamMemberStatus BillingAccountIamMemberSpec Appears on:BillingAccountIamMember, BillingAccountIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccountID string etag string (Optional) member string role string BillingAccountIamMemberStatus Appears on:BillingAccountIamMember</description></item><item><title>BillingAccountIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/billingaccountiampolicy/</guid><description>BillingAccountIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BillingAccountIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BillingAccountIamPolicySpec status BillingAccountIamPolicyStatus BillingAccountIamPolicySpec Appears on:BillingAccountIamPolicy, BillingAccountIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccountID string etag string (Optional) policyData string BillingAccountIamPolicyStatus Appears on:BillingAccountIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>BinaryAuthorizationAttestor</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestor/</guid><description>BinaryAuthorizationAttestor Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BinaryAuthorizationAttestor metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpec status BinaryAuthorizationAttestorStatus BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpec Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestor, BinaryAuthorizationAttestorStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string attestationAuthorityNote []BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpecAttestationAuthorityNote description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpecAttestationAuthorityNote Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorSpec</description></item><item><title>BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestoriambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestoriambinding/</guid><description>BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBindingSpec status BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBindingStatus BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBindingSpec Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBinding, BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string attestor string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBindingStatus Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamBinding</description></item><item><title>BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestoriammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestoriammember/</guid><description>BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMemberSpec status BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMemberStatus BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMemberSpec Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMember, BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string attestor string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMemberStatus Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamMember</description></item><item><title>BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestoriampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationattestoriampolicy/</guid><description>BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicySpec status BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicyStatus BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicySpec Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicy, BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string attestor string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicyStatus Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationAttestorIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>BinaryAuthorizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/binaryauthorizationpolicy/</guid><description>BinaryAuthorizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BinaryAuthorizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec status BinaryAuthorizationPolicyStatus BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationPolicy, BinaryAuthorizationPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string admissionWhitelistPatterns []BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecAdmissionWhitelistPatterns (Optional) clusterAdmissionRules []BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecClusterAdmissionRules (Optional) defaultAdmissionRule []BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecDefaultAdmissionRule description string (Optional) globalPolicyEvaluationMode string (Optional) project string (Optional) BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpecAdmissionWhitelistPatterns Appears on:BinaryAuthorizationPolicySpec</description></item><item><title>CloudbuildTrigger</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudbuildtrigger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudbuildtrigger/</guid><description>CloudbuildTrigger Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudbuildTrigger metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudbuildTriggerSpec status CloudbuildTriggerStatus CloudbuildTriggerSpec Appears on:CloudbuildTrigger, CloudbuildTriggerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string build []CloudbuildTriggerSpecBuild (Optional) createTime string (Optional) description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filename string (Optional) ignoredFiles []string (Optional) includedFiles []string (Optional) project string (Optional) substitutions map[string]string (Optional) triggerID string (Optional) triggerTemplate []CloudbuildTriggerSpecTriggerTemplate (Optional) CloudbuildTriggerSpecBuild Appears on:CloudbuildTriggerSpec</description></item><item><title>CloudfunctionsFunction</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunction/</guid><description>CloudfunctionsFunction Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudfunctionsFunction metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudfunctionsFunctionSpec status CloudfunctionsFunctionStatus CloudfunctionsFunctionSpec Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunction, CloudfunctionsFunctionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string availableMemoryMb int64 (Optional) description string (Optional) entryPoint string (Optional) environmentVariables map[string]string (Optional) eventTrigger []CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecEventTrigger (Optional) httpsTriggerURL string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) maxInstances int64 (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) runtime string (Optional) serviceAccountEmail string (Optional) sourceArchiveBucket string (Optional) sourceArchiveObject string (Optional) sourceRepository []CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecSourceRepository (Optional) timeout int64 (Optional) triggerHTTP bool (Optional) vpcConnector string (Optional) CloudfunctionsFunctionSpecEventTrigger Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionSpec</description></item><item><title>CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunctioniambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunctioniambinding/</guid><description>CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBindingSpec status CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBindingStatus CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBindingSpec Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBinding, CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cloudFunction string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBindingStatus Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionIamBinding</description></item><item><title>CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunctioniammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunctioniammember/</guid><description>CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMemberSpec status CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMemberStatus CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMemberSpec Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMember, CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cloudFunction string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMemberStatus Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionIamMember</description></item><item><title>CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunctioniampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudfunctionsfunctioniampolicy/</guid><description>CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicySpec status CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicyStatus CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicySpec Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicy, CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cloudFunction string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicyStatus Appears on:CloudfunctionsFunctionIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>CloudiotRegistry</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudiotregistry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudiotregistry/</guid><description>CloudiotRegistry Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudiotRegistry metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudiotRegistrySpec status CloudiotRegistryStatus CloudiotRegistrySpec Appears on:CloudiotRegistry, CloudiotRegistryStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string credentials []CloudiotRegistrySpecCredentials (Optional) eventNotificationConfig map[string]kubeform.</description></item><item><title>CloudSchedulerJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudschedulerjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/cloudschedulerjob/</guid><description>CloudSchedulerJob Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CloudSchedulerJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CloudSchedulerJobSpec status CloudSchedulerJobStatus CloudSchedulerJobSpec Appears on:CloudSchedulerJob, CloudSchedulerJobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appEngineHTTPTarget []CloudSchedulerJobSpecAppEngineHTTPTarget (Optional) description string (Optional) httpTarget []CloudSchedulerJobSpecHttpTarget (Optional) name string project string (Optional) pubsubTarget []CloudSchedulerJobSpecPubsubTarget (Optional) region string (Optional) retryConfig []CloudSchedulerJobSpecRetryConfig (Optional) schedule string (Optional) timeZone string (Optional) CloudSchedulerJobSpecAppEngineHTTPTarget Appears on:CloudSchedulerJobSpec</description></item><item><title>ComposerEnvironment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/composerenvironment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/composerenvironment/</guid><description>ComposerEnvironment Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComposerEnvironment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComposerEnvironmentSpec status ComposerEnvironmentStatus ComposerEnvironmentSpec Appears on:ComposerEnvironment, ComposerEnvironmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string config []ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfig (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) ComposerEnvironmentSpecConfig Appears on:ComposerEnvironmentSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeAddress</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeaddress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeaddress/</guid><description>ComputeAddress Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeAddress metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeAddressSpec status ComputeAddressStatus ComputeAddressSpec Appears on:ComputeAddress, ComputeAddressStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string address string (Optional) addressType string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string networkTier string (Optional) project string (Optional) purpose string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) users []string (Optional) ComputeAddressStatus Appears on:ComputeAddress</description></item><item><title>ComputeAttachedDisk</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeattacheddisk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeattacheddisk/</guid><description>ComputeAttachedDisk Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeAttachedDisk metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeAttachedDiskSpec status ComputeAttachedDiskStatus ComputeAttachedDiskSpec Appears on:ComputeAttachedDisk, ComputeAttachedDiskStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string deviceName string (Optional) disk string instance string mode string (Optional) project string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeAttachedDiskStatus Appears on:ComputeAttachedDisk</description></item><item><title>ComputeAutoscaler</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeautoscaler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeautoscaler/</guid><description>ComputeAutoscaler Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeAutoscaler metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeAutoscalerSpec status ComputeAutoscalerStatus ComputeAutoscalerSpec Appears on:ComputeAutoscaler, ComputeAutoscalerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoscalingPolicy []ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) target string zone string (Optional) ComputeAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy Appears on:ComputeAutoscalerSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeBackendBucket</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendbucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendbucket/</guid><description>ComputeBackendBucket Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeBackendBucket metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeBackendBucketSpec status ComputeBackendBucketStatus ComputeBackendBucketSpec Appears on:ComputeBackendBucket, ComputeBackendBucketStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucketName string cdnPolicy []ComputeBackendBucketSpecCdnPolicy (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) enableCdn bool (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeBackendBucketSpecCdnPolicy Appears on:ComputeBackendBucketSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendbucketsignedurlkey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendbucketsignedurlkey/</guid><description>ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKey Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKeySpec status ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKeyStatus ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKeySpec Appears on:ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKey, ComputeBackendBucketSignedURLKeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeBackendService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendservice/</guid><description>ComputeBackendService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeBackendService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeBackendServiceSpec status ComputeBackendServiceStatus ComputeBackendServiceSpec Appears on:ComputeBackendService, ComputeBackendServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendservicesignedurlkey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computebackendservicesignedurlkey/</guid><description>ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKey Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKeySpec status ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKeyStatus ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKeySpec Appears on:ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKey, ComputeBackendServiceSignedURLKeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeDisk</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computedisk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computedisk/</guid><description>ComputeDisk Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeDisk metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeDiskSpec status ComputeDiskStatus ComputeDiskSpec Appears on:ComputeDisk, ComputeDiskStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) diskEncryptionKey []ComputeDiskSpecDiskEncryptionKey (Optional) image string (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lastAttachTimestamp string (Optional) lastDetachTimestamp string (Optional) name string physicalBlockSizeBytes int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) size int64 (Optional) snapshot string (Optional) sourceImageEncryptionKey []ComputeDiskSpecSourceImageEncryptionKey (Optional) sourceImageID string (Optional) sourceSnapshotEncryptionKey []ComputeDiskSpecSourceSnapshotEncryptionKey (Optional) sourceSnapshotID string (Optional) type string (Optional) users []string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeDiskSpecDiskEncryptionKey Appears on:ComputeDiskSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computediskresourcepolicyattachment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computediskresourcepolicyattachment/</guid><description>ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachment Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachmentSpec status ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachmentStatus ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachmentSpec Appears on:ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachment, ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string disk string name string project string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachmentStatus Appears on:ComputeDiskResourcePolicyAttachment</description></item><item><title>ComputeFirewall</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computefirewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computefirewall/</guid><description>ComputeFirewall Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeFirewall metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeFirewallSpec status ComputeFirewallStatus ComputeFirewallSpec Appears on:ComputeFirewall, ComputeFirewallStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string allow []ComputeFirewallSpecAllow (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) deny []ComputeFirewallSpecDeny (Optional) description string (Optional) destinationRanges []string (Optional) direction string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) name string network string priority int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sourceRanges []string (Optional) sourceServiceAccounts []string (Optional) sourceTags []string (Optional) targetServiceAccounts []string (Optional) targetTags []string (Optional) ComputeFirewallSpecAllow Appears on:ComputeFirewallSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeForwardingRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeforwardingrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeforwardingrule/</guid><description>ComputeForwardingRule Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeForwardingRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeForwardingRuleSpec status ComputeForwardingRuleStatus ComputeForwardingRuleSpec Appears on:ComputeForwardingRule, ComputeForwardingRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string allPorts bool (Optional) backendService string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) ipAddress string (Optional) ipProtocol string (Optional) ipVersion string (Optional) Deprecated loadBalancingScheme string (Optional) name string network string (Optional) networkTier string (Optional) portRange string (Optional) ports []string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) serviceLabel string (Optional) serviceName string (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) target string (Optional) ComputeForwardingRuleStatus Appears on:ComputeForwardingRule</description></item><item><title>ComputeGlobalAddress</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobaladdress/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobaladdress/</guid><description>ComputeGlobalAddress Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeGlobalAddress metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeGlobalAddressSpec status ComputeGlobalAddressStatus ComputeGlobalAddressSpec Appears on:ComputeGlobalAddress, ComputeGlobalAddressStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string address string (Optional) addressType string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) ipVersion string (Optional) name string network string (Optional) prefixLength int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) purpose string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeGlobalAddressStatus Appears on:ComputeGlobalAddress</description></item><item><title>ComputeGlobalForwardingRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobalforwardingrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeglobalforwardingrule/</guid><description>ComputeGlobalForwardingRule Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeGlobalForwardingRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleSpec status ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleStatus ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleSpec Appears on:ComputeGlobalForwardingRule, ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) ipAddress string (Optional) ipProtocol string (Optional) ipVersion string (Optional) loadBalancingScheme string (Optional) metadataFilters []ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleSpecMetadataFilters (Optional) name string portRange string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) target string ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleSpecMetadataFilters Appears on:ComputeGlobalForwardingRuleSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeHealthCheck</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehealthcheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehealthcheck/</guid><description>ComputeHealthCheck Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeHealthCheck metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeHealthCheckSpec status ComputeHealthCheckStatus ComputeHealthCheckSpec Appears on:ComputeHealthCheck, ComputeHealthCheckStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string checkIntervalSec int64 (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) healthyThreshold int64 (Optional) http2HealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttp2HealthCheck (Optional) httpHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttpHealthCheck (Optional) httpsHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttpsHealthCheck (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sslHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecSslHealthCheck (Optional) tcpHealthCheck []ComputeHealthCheckSpecTcpHealthCheck (Optional) timeoutSec int64 (Optional) type string (Optional) unhealthyThreshold int64 (Optional) ComputeHealthCheckSpecHttp2HealthCheck Appears on:ComputeHealthCheckSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeHTTPHealthCheck</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttphealthcheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttphealthcheck/</guid><description>ComputeHTTPHealthCheck Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeHTTPHealthCheck metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeHTTPHealthCheckSpec status ComputeHTTPHealthCheckStatus ComputeHTTPHealthCheckSpec Appears on:ComputeHTTPHealthCheck, ComputeHTTPHealthCheckStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string checkIntervalSec int64 (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) healthyThreshold int64 (Optional) host string (Optional) name string port int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) requestPath string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) timeoutSec int64 (Optional) unhealthyThreshold int64 (Optional) ComputeHTTPHealthCheckStatus Appears on:ComputeHTTPHealthCheck</description></item><item><title>ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttpshealthcheck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computehttpshealthcheck/</guid><description>ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckSpec status ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckStatus ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckSpec Appears on:ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck, ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string checkIntervalSec int64 (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) healthyThreshold int64 (Optional) host string (Optional) name string port int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) requestPath string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) timeoutSec int64 (Optional) unhealthyThreshold int64 (Optional) ComputeHTTPSHealthCheckStatus Appears on:ComputeHTTPSHealthCheck</description></item><item><title>ComputeImage</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeimage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeimage/</guid><description>ComputeImage Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeImage metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeImageSpec status ComputeImageStatus ComputeImageSpec Appears on:ComputeImage, ComputeImageStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string archiveSizeBytes int64 (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) diskSizeGb int64 (Optional) family string (Optional) guestOsFeatures []ComputeImageSpecGuestOsFeatures (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) licenses []string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) rawDisk []ComputeImageSpecRawDisk (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sourceDisk string (Optional) ComputeImageSpecGuestOsFeatures Appears on:ComputeImageSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstance/</guid><description>ComputeInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceSpec status ComputeInstanceStatus ComputeInstanceSpec Appears on:ComputeInstance, ComputeInstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceFromTemplate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancefromtemplate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancefromtemplate/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceFromTemplate Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceFromTemplate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceFromTemplateSpec status ComputeInstanceFromTemplateStatus ComputeInstanceFromTemplateSpec Appears on:ComputeInstanceFromTemplate, ComputeInstanceFromTemplateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroup/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceGroupSpec status ComputeInstanceGroupStatus ComputeInstanceGroupSpec Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroup, ComputeInstanceGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) instances []string (Optional) name string namedPort []ComputeInstanceGroupSpecNamedPort (Optional) network string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) size int64 (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeInstanceGroupSpecNamedPort Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceGroupManager</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroupmanager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancegroupmanager/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceGroupManager Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceGroupManager metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec status ComputeInstanceGroupManagerStatus ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManager, ComputeInstanceGroupManagerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string baseInstanceName string description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) instanceGroup string (Optional) instanceTemplate string name string namedPort []ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) targetPools []string (Optional) targetSize int64 (Optional) updateStrategy string (Optional) waitForInstances bool (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort Appears on:ComputeInstanceGroupManagerSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstanceiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstanceiambinding/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceIamBindingSpec status ComputeInstanceIamBindingStatus ComputeInstanceIamBindingSpec Appears on:ComputeInstanceIamBinding, ComputeInstanceIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instanceName string members []string project string (Optional) role string zone string (Optional) ComputeInstanceIamBindingStatus Appears on:ComputeInstanceIamBinding</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstanceiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstanceiammember/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceIamMemberSpec status ComputeInstanceIamMemberStatus ComputeInstanceIamMemberSpec Appears on:ComputeInstanceIamMember, ComputeInstanceIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instanceName string member string project string (Optional) role string zone string (Optional) ComputeInstanceIamMemberStatus Appears on:ComputeInstanceIamMember</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstanceiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstanceiampolicy/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceIamPolicySpec status ComputeInstanceIamPolicyStatus ComputeInstanceIamPolicySpec Appears on:ComputeInstanceIamPolicy, ComputeInstanceIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) instanceName string policyData string project string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeInstanceIamPolicyStatus Appears on:ComputeInstanceIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>ComputeInstanceTemplate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancetemplate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinstancetemplate/</guid><description>ComputeInstanceTemplate Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInstanceTemplate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec status ComputeInstanceTemplateStatus ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplate, ComputeInstanceTemplateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string canIPForward bool (Optional) description string (Optional) disk []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecDisk guestAccelerator []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecGuestAccelerator (Optional) instanceDescription string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) machineType string metadata map[string]string (Optional) metadataFingerprint string (Optional) metadataStartupScript string (Optional) minCPUPlatform string (Optional) name string (Optional) namePrefix string (Optional) networkInterface []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecNetworkInterface (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) scheduling []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecScheduling (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) serviceAccount []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecServiceAccount (Optional) shieldedInstanceConfig []ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecShieldedInstanceConfig (Optional) tags []string (Optional) tagsFingerprint string (Optional) ComputeInstanceTemplateSpecDisk Appears on:ComputeInstanceTemplateSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeInterconnectAttachment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinterconnectattachment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeinterconnectattachment/</guid><description>ComputeInterconnectAttachment Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeInterconnectAttachment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpec status ComputeInterconnectAttachmentStatus ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpec Appears on:ComputeInterconnectAttachment, ComputeInterconnectAttachmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string adminEnabled bool (Optional) bandwidth string (Optional) candidateSubnets []string (Optional) cloudRouterIPAddress string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) customerRouterIPAddress string (Optional) description string (Optional) edgeAvailabilityDomain string (Optional) googleReferenceID string (Optional) interconnect string (Optional) name string pairingKey string (Optional) partnerAsn string (Optional) privateInterconnectInfo []ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpecPrivateInterconnectInfo (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string selfLink string (Optional) state string (Optional) type string (Optional) vlanTag8021q int64 (Optional) ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpecPrivateInterconnectInfo Appears on:ComputeInterconnectAttachmentSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeNetwork</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetwork/</guid><description>ComputeNetwork Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNetwork metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNetworkSpec status ComputeNetworkStatus ComputeNetworkSpec Appears on:ComputeNetwork, ComputeNetworkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoCreateSubnetworks bool (Optional) deleteDefaultRoutesOnCreate bool (Optional) description string (Optional) gatewayIpv4 string (Optional) ipv4Range string (Optional) Deprecated name string project string (Optional) routingMode string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeNetworkStatus Appears on:ComputeNetwork</description></item><item><title>ComputeNetworkEndpoint</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkendpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkendpoint/</guid><description>ComputeNetworkEndpoint Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNetworkEndpoint metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNetworkEndpointSpec status ComputeNetworkEndpointStatus ComputeNetworkEndpointSpec Appears on:ComputeNetworkEndpoint, ComputeNetworkEndpointStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string instance string ipAddress string networkEndpointGroup string port int64 project string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeNetworkEndpointStatus Appears on:ComputeNetworkEndpoint</description></item><item><title>ComputeNetworkEndpointGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkendpointgroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkendpointgroup/</guid><description>ComputeNetworkEndpointGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNetworkEndpointGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNetworkEndpointGroupSpec status ComputeNetworkEndpointGroupStatus ComputeNetworkEndpointGroupSpec Appears on:ComputeNetworkEndpointGroup, ComputeNetworkEndpointGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string defaultPort int64 (Optional) description string (Optional) name string network string networkEndpointType string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) size int64 (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeNetworkEndpointGroupStatus Appears on:ComputeNetworkEndpointGroup</description></item><item><title>ComputeNetworkPeering</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkpeering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenetworkpeering/</guid><description>ComputeNetworkPeering Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNetworkPeering metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNetworkPeeringSpec status ComputeNetworkPeeringStatus ComputeNetworkPeeringSpec Appears on:ComputeNetworkPeering, ComputeNetworkPeeringStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoCreateRoutes bool (Optional) Deprecated name string network string peerNetwork string state string (Optional) stateDetails string (Optional) ComputeNetworkPeeringStatus Appears on:ComputeNetworkPeering</description></item><item><title>ComputeNodeGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenodegroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenodegroup/</guid><description>ComputeNodeGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNodeGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNodeGroupSpec status ComputeNodeGroupStatus ComputeNodeGroupSpec Appears on:ComputeNodeGroup, ComputeNodeGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string (Optional) nodeTemplate string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) size int64 zone string (Optional) ComputeNodeGroupStatus Appears on:ComputeNodeGroup</description></item><item><title>ComputeNodeTemplate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenodetemplate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computenodetemplate/</guid><description>ComputeNodeTemplate Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeNodeTemplate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeNodeTemplateSpec status ComputeNodeTemplateStatus ComputeNodeTemplateSpec Appears on:ComputeNodeTemplate, ComputeNodeTemplateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string (Optional) nodeAffinityLabels map[string]string (Optional) nodeType string (Optional) nodeTypeFlexibility []ComputeNodeTemplateSpecNodeTypeFlexibility (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeNodeTemplateSpecNodeTypeFlexibility Appears on:ComputeNodeTemplateSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTier</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectdefaultnetworktier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectdefaultnetworktier/</guid><description>ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTier Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTier metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTierSpec status ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTierStatus ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTierSpec Appears on:ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTier, ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTierStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string networkTier string project string (Optional) ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTierStatus Appears on:ComputeProjectDefaultNetworkTier</description></item><item><title>ComputeProjectMetadata</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadata/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadata/</guid><description>ComputeProjectMetadata Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeProjectMetadata metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeProjectMetadataSpec status ComputeProjectMetadataStatus ComputeProjectMetadataSpec Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadata, ComputeProjectMetadataStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string metadata map[string]string project string (Optional) ComputeProjectMetadataStatus Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadata</description></item><item><title>ComputeProjectMetadataItem</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadataitem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeprojectmetadataitem/</guid><description>ComputeProjectMetadataItem Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeProjectMetadataItem metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeProjectMetadataItemSpec status ComputeProjectMetadataItemStatus ComputeProjectMetadataItemSpec Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadataItem, ComputeProjectMetadataItemStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string key string project string (Optional) value string ComputeProjectMetadataItemStatus Appears on:ComputeProjectMetadataItem</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionAutoscaler</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionautoscaler/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionautoscaler/</guid><description>ComputeRegionAutoscaler Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionAutoscaler metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpec status ComputeRegionAutoscalerStatus ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpec Appears on:ComputeRegionAutoscaler, ComputeRegionAutoscalerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoscalingPolicy []ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) target string ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpecAutoscalingPolicy Appears on:ComputeRegionAutoscalerSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionBackendService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionbackendservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregionbackendservice/</guid><description>ComputeRegionBackendService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionBackendService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpec status ComputeRegionBackendServiceStatus ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpec Appears on:ComputeRegionBackendService, ComputeRegionBackendServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backend []ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpecBackend (Optional) connectionDrainingTimeoutSec int64 (Optional) description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) healthChecks []string loadBalancingScheme string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) protocol string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sessionAffinity string (Optional) timeoutSec int64 (Optional) ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpecBackend Appears on:ComputeRegionBackendServiceSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionDisk</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregiondisk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregiondisk/</guid><description>ComputeRegionDisk Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionDisk metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionDiskSpec status ComputeRegionDiskStatus ComputeRegionDiskSpec Appears on:ComputeRegionDisk, ComputeRegionDiskStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) diskEncryptionKey []ComputeRegionDiskSpecDiskEncryptionKey (Optional) labelFingerprint string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) lastAttachTimestamp string (Optional) lastDetachTimestamp string (Optional) name string physicalBlockSizeBytes int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) replicaZones []string selfLink string (Optional) size int64 (Optional) snapshot string (Optional) sourceSnapshotEncryptionKey []ComputeRegionDiskSpecSourceSnapshotEncryptionKey (Optional) sourceSnapshotID string (Optional) type string (Optional) users []string (Optional) ComputeRegionDiskSpecDiskEncryptionKey Appears on:ComputeRegionDiskSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregioninstancegroupmanager/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeregioninstancegroupmanager/</guid><description>ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec status ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerStatus ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManager, ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string baseInstanceName string description string (Optional) distributionPolicyZones []string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) instanceGroup string (Optional) instanceTemplate string name string namedPort []ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort (Optional) project string (Optional) region string selfLink string (Optional) targetPools []string (Optional) targetSize int64 (Optional) updateStrategy string (Optional) Deprecated waitForInstances bool (Optional) ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpecNamedPort Appears on:ComputeRegionInstanceGroupManagerSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeReservation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computereservation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computereservation/</guid><description>ComputeReservation Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeReservation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeReservationSpec status ComputeReservationStatus ComputeReservationSpec Appears on:ComputeReservation, ComputeReservationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string commitment string (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) specificReservation []ComputeReservationSpecSpecificReservation specificReservationRequired bool (Optional) status string (Optional) zone string ComputeReservationSpecSpecificReservation Appears on:ComputeReservationSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeResourcePolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeresourcepolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeresourcepolicy/</guid><description>ComputeResourcePolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeResourcePolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeResourcePolicySpec status ComputeResourcePolicyStatus ComputeResourcePolicySpec Appears on:ComputeResourcePolicy, ComputeResourcePolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) snapshotSchedulePolicy []ComputeResourcePolicySpecSnapshotSchedulePolicy (Optional) ComputeResourcePolicySpecSnapshotSchedulePolicy Appears on:ComputeResourcePolicySpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeRoute</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeroute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeroute/</guid><description>ComputeRoute Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRoute metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouteSpec status ComputeRouteStatus ComputeRouteSpec Appears on:ComputeRoute, ComputeRouteStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) destRange string name string network string nextHopGateway string (Optional) nextHopInstance string (Optional) nextHopInstanceZone string (Optional) nextHopIP string (Optional) nextHopNetwork string (Optional) nextHopVPNTunnel string (Optional) priority int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) tags []string (Optional) ComputeRouteStatus Appears on:ComputeRoute</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouter</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouter/</guid><description>ComputeRouter Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouter metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterSpec status ComputeRouterStatus ComputeRouterSpec Appears on:ComputeRouter, ComputeRouterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bgp []ComputeRouterSpecBgp (Optional) creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string network string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeRouterSpecBgp Appears on:ComputeRouterSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouterInterface</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterinterface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterinterface/</guid><description>ComputeRouterInterface Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouterInterface metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterInterfaceSpec status ComputeRouterInterfaceStatus ComputeRouterInterfaceSpec Appears on:ComputeRouterInterface, ComputeRouterInterfaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string interconnectAttachment string (Optional) ipRange string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string vpnTunnel string (Optional) ComputeRouterInterfaceStatus Appears on:ComputeRouterInterface</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouterNAT</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouternat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouternat/</guid><description>ComputeRouterNAT Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouterNAT metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterNATSpec status ComputeRouterNATStatus ComputeRouterNATSpec Appears on:ComputeRouterNAT, ComputeRouterNATStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string icmpIdleTimeoutSec int64 (Optional) logConfig []ComputeRouterNATSpecLogConfig (Optional) minPortsPerVm int64 (Optional) name string natIPAllocateOption string natIPS []string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string sourceSubnetworkIPRangesToNAT string subnetwork []ComputeRouterNATSpecSubnetwork (Optional) tcpEstablishedIdleTimeoutSec int64 (Optional) tcpTransitoryIdleTimeoutSec int64 (Optional) udpIdleTimeoutSec int64 (Optional) ComputeRouterNATSpecLogConfig Appears on:ComputeRouterNATSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeRouterPeer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterpeer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computerouterpeer/</guid><description>ComputeRouterPeer Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeRouterPeer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeRouterPeerSpec status ComputeRouterPeerStatus ComputeRouterPeerSpec Appears on:ComputeRouterPeer, ComputeRouterPeerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string advertiseMode string (Optional) advertisedGroups []string (Optional) advertisedIPRanges []ComputeRouterPeerSpecAdvertisedIPRanges (Optional) advertisedRoutePriority int64 (Optional) interface string ipAddress string (Optional) name string peerAsn int64 peerIPAddress string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) router string ComputeRouterPeerSpecAdvertisedIPRanges Appears on:ComputeRouterPeerSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeSecurityPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesecuritypolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesecuritypolicy/</guid><description>ComputeSecurityPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSecurityPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSecurityPolicySpec status ComputeSecurityPolicyStatus ComputeSecurityPolicySpec Appears on:ComputeSecurityPolicy, ComputeSecurityPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) rule []ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRule (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeSecurityPolicySpecRule Appears on:ComputeSecurityPolicySpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeSharedVpcHostProject</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpchostproject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpchostproject/</guid><description>ComputeSharedVpcHostProject Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSharedVpcHostProject metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectSpec status ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectStatus ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectSpec Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcHostProject, ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string project string ComputeSharedVpcHostProjectStatus Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcHostProject</description></item><item><title>ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpcserviceproject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesharedvpcserviceproject/</guid><description>ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectSpec status ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectStatus ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectSpec Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject, ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string hostProject string serviceProject string ComputeSharedVpcServiceProjectStatus Appears on:ComputeSharedVpcServiceProject</description></item><item><title>ComputeSnapshot</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesnapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesnapshot/</guid><description>ComputeSnapshot Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSnapshot metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSnapshotSpec status ComputeSnapshotStatus ComputeSnapshotSpec Appears on:ComputeSnapshot, ComputeSnapshotStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSSLCertificate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslcertificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslcertificate/</guid><description>ComputeSSLCertificate Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSSLCertificate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSSLCertificateSpec status ComputeSSLCertificateStatus ComputeSSLCertificateSpec Appears on:ComputeSSLCertificate, ComputeSSLCertificateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ComputeSSLPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesslpolicy/</guid><description>ComputeSSLPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSSLPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSSLPolicySpec status ComputeSSLPolicyStatus ComputeSSLPolicySpec Appears on:ComputeSSLPolicy, ComputeSSLPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) customFeatures []string (Optional) description string (Optional) enabledFeatures []string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) minTLSVersion string (Optional) name string profile string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeSSLPolicyStatus Appears on:ComputeSSLPolicy</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetwork</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetwork/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetwork Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetwork metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkSpec status ComputeSubnetworkStatus ComputeSubnetworkSpec Appears on:ComputeSubnetwork, ComputeSubnetworkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) enableFlowLogs bool (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) gatewayAddress string (Optional) ipCIDRRange string name string network string privateIPGoogleAccess bool (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) secondaryIPRange []ComputeSubnetworkSpecSecondaryIPRange (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeSubnetworkSpecSecondaryIPRange Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiambinding/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingSpec status ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingStatus ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingSpec Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding, ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string subnetwork string ComputeSubnetworkIamBindingStatus Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamBinding</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetworkIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiammember/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetworkIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetworkIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberSpec status ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberStatus ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberSpec Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamMember, ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string subnetwork string ComputeSubnetworkIamMemberStatus Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamMember</description></item><item><title>ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computesubnetworkiampolicy/</guid><description>ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicySpec status ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicyStatus ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicySpec Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy, ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) subnetwork string ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicyStatus Appears on:ComputeSubnetworkIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetHTTPProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetHTTPProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetHTTPProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetHTTPProxySpec status ComputeTargetHTTPProxyStatus ComputeTargetHTTPProxySpec Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPProxy, ComputeTargetHTTPProxyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyID int64 (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) urlMap string ComputeTargetHTTPProxyStatus Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPProxy</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpsproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargethttpsproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetHTTPSProxySpec status ComputeTargetHTTPSProxyStatus ComputeTargetHTTPSProxySpec Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy, ComputeTargetHTTPSProxyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyID int64 (Optional) quicOverride string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sslCertificates []string sslPolicy string (Optional) urlMap string ComputeTargetHTTPSProxyStatus Appears on:ComputeTargetHTTPSProxy</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetinstance/</guid><description>ComputeTargetInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetInstanceSpec status ComputeTargetInstanceStatus ComputeTargetInstanceSpec Appears on:ComputeTargetInstance, ComputeTargetInstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) instance string name string natPolicy string (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) zone string (Optional) ComputeTargetInstanceStatus Appears on:ComputeTargetInstance</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetPool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetpool/</guid><description>ComputeTargetPool Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetPool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetPoolSpec status ComputeTargetPoolStatus ComputeTargetPoolSpec Appears on:ComputeTargetPool, ComputeTargetPoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backupPool string (Optional) description string (Optional) failoverRatio float64 (Optional) healthChecks []string (Optional) instances []string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sessionAffinity string (Optional) ComputeTargetPoolStatus Appears on:ComputeTargetPool</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetSSLProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetsslproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargetsslproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetSSLProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetSSLProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetSSLProxySpec status ComputeTargetSSLProxyStatus ComputeTargetSSLProxySpec Appears on:ComputeTargetSSLProxy, ComputeTargetSSLProxyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendService string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) proxyID int64 (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) sslCertificates []string sslPolicy string (Optional) ComputeTargetSSLProxyStatus Appears on:ComputeTargetSSLProxy</description></item><item><title>ComputeTargetTcpProxy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargettcpproxy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computetargettcpproxy/</guid><description>ComputeTargetTcpProxy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeTargetTcpProxy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeTargetTcpProxySpec status ComputeTargetTcpProxyStatus ComputeTargetTcpProxySpec Appears on:ComputeTargetTcpProxy, ComputeTargetTcpProxyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendService string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) proxyHeader string (Optional) proxyID int64 (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeTargetTcpProxyStatus Appears on:ComputeTargetTcpProxy</description></item><item><title>ComputeURLMap</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeurlmap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computeurlmap/</guid><description>ComputeURLMap Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeURLMap metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeURLMapSpec status ComputeURLMapStatus ComputeURLMapSpec Appears on:ComputeURLMap, ComputeURLMapStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) defaultService string description string (Optional) fingerprint string (Optional) hostRule []ComputeURLMapSpecHostRule (Optional) mapID int64 (Optional) name string pathMatcher []ComputeURLMapSpecPathMatcher (Optional) project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) test []ComputeURLMapSpecTest (Optional) ComputeURLMapSpecHostRule Appears on:ComputeURLMapSpec</description></item><item><title>ComputeVPNGateway</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpngateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpngateway/</guid><description>ComputeVPNGateway Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeVPNGateway metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeVPNGatewaySpec status ComputeVPNGatewayStatus ComputeVPNGatewaySpec Appears on:ComputeVPNGateway, ComputeVPNGatewayStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string creationTimestamp string (Optional) description string (Optional) gatewayID int64 (Optional) name string network string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) ComputeVPNGatewayStatus Appears on:ComputeVPNGateway</description></item><item><title>ComputeVPNTunnel</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpntunnel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/computevpntunnel/</guid><description>ComputeVPNTunnel Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ComputeVPNTunnel metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ComputeVPNTunnelSpec status ComputeVPNTunnelStatus ComputeVPNTunnelSpec Appears on:ComputeVPNTunnel, ComputeVPNTunnelStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ContainerAnalysisNote</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/containeranalysisnote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/containeranalysisnote/</guid><description>ContainerAnalysisNote Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerAnalysisNote metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerAnalysisNoteSpec status ContainerAnalysisNoteStatus ContainerAnalysisNoteSpec Appears on:ContainerAnalysisNote, ContainerAnalysisNoteStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string attestationAuthority []ContainerAnalysisNoteSpecAttestationAuthority name string project string (Optional) ContainerAnalysisNoteSpecAttestationAuthority Appears on:ContainerAnalysisNoteSpec</description></item><item><title>ContainerCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/containercluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/containercluster/</guid><description>ContainerCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerClusterSpec status ContainerClusterStatus ContainerClusterSpec Appears on:ContainerCluster, ContainerClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ContainerNodePool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/containernodepool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/containernodepool/</guid><description>ContainerNodePool Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerNodePool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerNodePoolSpec status ContainerNodePoolStatus ContainerNodePoolSpec Appears on:ContainerNodePool, ContainerNodePoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoscaling []ContainerNodePoolSpecAutoscaling (Optional) cluster string initialNodeCount int64 (Optional) instanceGroupUrls []string (Optional) location string (Optional) management []ContainerNodePoolSpecManagement (Optional) maxPodsPerNode int64 (Optional) name string (Optional) namePrefix string (Optional) nodeConfig []ContainerNodePoolSpecNodeConfig (Optional) nodeCount int64 (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) Deprecated version string (Optional) zone string (Optional) Deprecated ContainerNodePoolSpecAutoscaling Appears on:ContainerNodePoolSpec</description></item><item><title>DataflowJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataflowjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataflowjob/</guid><description>DataflowJob Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataflowJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataflowJobSpec status DataflowJobStatus DataflowJobSpec Appears on:DataflowJob, DataflowJobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string labels map[string]string (Optional) machineType string (Optional) maxWorkers int64 (Optional) name string network string (Optional) onDelete string (Optional) parameters map[string]string (Optional) project string (Optional) region string (Optional) serviceAccountEmail string (Optional) state string (Optional) subnetwork string (Optional) tempGcsLocation string templateGcsPath string zone string (Optional) DataflowJobStatus Appears on:DataflowJob</description></item><item><title>DataprocCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataproccluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataproccluster/</guid><description>DataprocCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocClusterSpec status DataprocClusterStatus DataprocClusterSpec Appears on:DataprocCluster, DataprocClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string clusterConfig []DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) DataprocClusterSpecClusterConfig Appears on:DataprocClusterSpec</description></item><item><title>DataprocClusterIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocclusteriambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocclusteriambinding/</guid><description>DataprocClusterIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocClusterIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocClusterIamBindingSpec status DataprocClusterIamBindingStatus DataprocClusterIamBindingSpec Appears on:DataprocClusterIamBinding, DataprocClusterIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cluster string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string DataprocClusterIamBindingStatus Appears on:DataprocClusterIamBinding</description></item><item><title>DataprocClusterIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocclusteriammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocclusteriammember/</guid><description>DataprocClusterIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocClusterIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocClusterIamMemberSpec status DataprocClusterIamMemberStatus DataprocClusterIamMemberSpec Appears on:DataprocClusterIamMember, DataprocClusterIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cluster string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string DataprocClusterIamMemberStatus Appears on:DataprocClusterIamMember</description></item><item><title>DataprocClusterIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocclusteriampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocclusteriampolicy/</guid><description>DataprocClusterIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocClusterIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocClusterIamPolicySpec status DataprocClusterIamPolicyStatus DataprocClusterIamPolicySpec Appears on:DataprocClusterIamPolicy, DataprocClusterIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cluster string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) DataprocClusterIamPolicyStatus Appears on:DataprocClusterIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>DataprocJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjob/</guid><description>DataprocJob Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocJobSpec status DataprocJobStatus DataprocJobSpec Appears on:DataprocJob, DataprocJobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string driverControlsFilesURI string (Optional) Output-only.</description></item><item><title>DataprocJobIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjobiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjobiambinding/</guid><description>DataprocJobIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocJobIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocJobIamBindingSpec status DataprocJobIamBindingStatus DataprocJobIamBindingSpec Appears on:DataprocJobIamBinding, DataprocJobIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) jobID string members []string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string DataprocJobIamBindingStatus Appears on:DataprocJobIamBinding</description></item><item><title>DataprocJobIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjobiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjobiammember/</guid><description>DataprocJobIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocJobIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocJobIamMemberSpec status DataprocJobIamMemberStatus DataprocJobIamMemberSpec Appears on:DataprocJobIamMember, DataprocJobIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) jobID string member string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) role string DataprocJobIamMemberStatus Appears on:DataprocJobIamMember</description></item><item><title>DataprocJobIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjobiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dataprocjobiampolicy/</guid><description>DataprocJobIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataprocJobIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataprocJobIamPolicySpec status DataprocJobIamPolicyStatus DataprocJobIamPolicySpec Appears on:DataprocJobIamPolicy, DataprocJobIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) jobID string policyData string project string (Optional) region string (Optional) DataprocJobIamPolicyStatus Appears on:DataprocJobIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>DnsManagedZone</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsmanagedzone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsmanagedzone/</guid><description>DnsManagedZone Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsManagedZone metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsManagedZoneSpec status DnsManagedZoneStatus DnsManagedZoneSpec Appears on:DnsManagedZone, DnsManagedZoneStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) dnsName string dnssecConfig []DnsManagedZoneSpecDnssecConfig (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string nameServers []string (Optional) privateVisibilityConfig []DnsManagedZoneSpecPrivateVisibilityConfig (Optional) project string (Optional) visibility string (Optional) DnsManagedZoneSpecDnssecConfig Appears on:DnsManagedZoneSpec</description></item><item><title>DnsRecordSet</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsrecordset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/dnsrecordset/</guid><description>DnsRecordSet Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsRecordSet metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsRecordSetSpec status DnsRecordSetStatus DnsRecordSetSpec Appears on:DnsRecordSet, DnsRecordSetStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string managedZone string name string project string (Optional) rrdatas []string ttl int64 type string DnsRecordSetStatus Appears on:DnsRecordSet</description></item><item><title>EndpointsService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/endpointsservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/endpointsservice/</guid><description>EndpointsService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EndpointsService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EndpointsServiceSpec status EndpointsServiceStatus EndpointsServiceSpec Appears on:EndpointsService, EndpointsServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apis []EndpointsServiceSpecApis (Optional) configID string (Optional) dnsAddress string (Optional) endpoints []EndpointsServiceSpecEndpoints (Optional) grpcConfig string (Optional) openapiConfig string (Optional) project string (Optional) protocOutputBase64 string (Optional) serviceName string EndpointsServiceSpecApis Appears on:EndpointsServiceSpec</description></item><item><title>FilestoreInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/filestoreinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/filestoreinstance/</guid><description>FilestoreInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FilestoreInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FilestoreInstanceSpec status FilestoreInstanceStatus FilestoreInstanceSpec Appears on:FilestoreInstance, FilestoreInstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTime string (Optional) description string (Optional) etag string (Optional) fileShares []FilestoreInstanceSpecFileShares labels map[string]string (Optional) name string networks []FilestoreInstanceSpecNetworks project string (Optional) tier string zone string FilestoreInstanceSpecFileShares Appears on:FilestoreInstanceSpec</description></item><item><title>FirestoreIndex</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/firestoreindex/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/firestoreindex/</guid><description>FirestoreIndex Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FirestoreIndex metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FirestoreIndexSpec status FirestoreIndexStatus FirestoreIndexSpec Appears on:FirestoreIndex, FirestoreIndexStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string collection string database string (Optional) fields []FirestoreIndexSpecFields name string (Optional) project string (Optional) queryScope string (Optional) FirestoreIndexSpecFields Appears on:FirestoreIndexSpec</description></item><item><title>Folder</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folder/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folder/</guid><description>Folder Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Folder metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderSpec status FolderStatus FolderSpec Appears on:Folder, FolderStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createTime string (Optional) displayName string lifecycleState string (Optional) name string (Optional) parent string FolderStatus Appears on:Folder</description></item><item><title>FolderIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiambinding/</guid><description>FolderIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderIamBindingSpec status FolderIamBindingStatus FolderIamBindingSpec Appears on:FolderIamBinding, FolderIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) folder string members []string role string FolderIamBindingStatus Appears on:FolderIamBinding</description></item><item><title>FolderIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiammember/</guid><description>FolderIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderIamMemberSpec status FolderIamMemberStatus FolderIamMemberSpec Appears on:FolderIamMember, FolderIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) folder string member string role string FolderIamMemberStatus Appears on:FolderIamMember</description></item><item><title>FolderIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderiampolicy/</guid><description>FolderIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderIamPolicySpec status FolderIamPolicyStatus FolderIamPolicySpec Appears on:FolderIamPolicy, FolderIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) folder string policyData string FolderIamPolicyStatus Appears on:FolderIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>FolderOrganizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderorganizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/folderorganizationpolicy/</guid><description>FolderOrganizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FolderOrganizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FolderOrganizationPolicySpec status FolderOrganizationPolicyStatus FolderOrganizationPolicySpec Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicy, FolderOrganizationPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string booleanPolicy []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Optional) constraint string etag string (Optional) folder string listPolicy []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Optional) restorePolicy []FolderOrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Optional) updateTime string (Optional) version int64 (Optional) FolderOrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy Appears on:FolderOrganizationPolicySpec</description></item><item><title>IapAppEngineServiceIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineserviceiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineserviceiambinding/</guid><description>IapAppEngineServiceIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapAppEngineServiceIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapAppEngineServiceIamBindingSpec status IapAppEngineServiceIamBindingStatus IapAppEngineServiceIamBindingSpec Appears on:IapAppEngineServiceIamBinding, IapAppEngineServiceIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string service string IapAppEngineServiceIamBindingStatus Appears on:IapAppEngineServiceIamBinding</description></item><item><title>IapAppEngineServiceIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineserviceiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineserviceiammember/</guid><description>IapAppEngineServiceIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapAppEngineServiceIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapAppEngineServiceIamMemberSpec status IapAppEngineServiceIamMemberStatus IapAppEngineServiceIamMemberSpec Appears on:IapAppEngineServiceIamMember, IapAppEngineServiceIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string service string IapAppEngineServiceIamMemberStatus Appears on:IapAppEngineServiceIamMember</description></item><item><title>IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineserviceiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineserviceiampolicy/</guid><description>IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicySpec status IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicyStatus IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicySpec Appears on:IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicy, IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) service string IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicyStatus Appears on:IapAppEngineServiceIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>IapAppEngineVersionIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineversioniambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineversioniambinding/</guid><description>IapAppEngineVersionIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapAppEngineVersionIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapAppEngineVersionIamBindingSpec status IapAppEngineVersionIamBindingStatus IapAppEngineVersionIamBindingSpec Appears on:IapAppEngineVersionIamBinding, IapAppEngineVersionIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string service string versionID string IapAppEngineVersionIamBindingStatus Appears on:IapAppEngineVersionIamBinding</description></item><item><title>IapAppEngineVersionIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineversioniammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineversioniammember/</guid><description>IapAppEngineVersionIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapAppEngineVersionIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapAppEngineVersionIamMemberSpec status IapAppEngineVersionIamMemberStatus IapAppEngineVersionIamMemberSpec Appears on:IapAppEngineVersionIamMember, IapAppEngineVersionIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string service string versionID string IapAppEngineVersionIamMemberStatus Appears on:IapAppEngineVersionIamMember</description></item><item><title>IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineversioniampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapappengineversioniampolicy/</guid><description>IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicySpec status IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicyStatus IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicySpec Appears on:IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicy, IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) service string versionID string IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicyStatus Appears on:IapAppEngineVersionIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>IapWebBackendServiceIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebbackendserviceiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebbackendserviceiambinding/</guid><description>IapWebBackendServiceIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebBackendServiceIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebBackendServiceIamBindingSpec status IapWebBackendServiceIamBindingStatus IapWebBackendServiceIamBindingSpec Appears on:IapWebBackendServiceIamBinding, IapWebBackendServiceIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string webBackendService string IapWebBackendServiceIamBindingStatus Appears on:IapWebBackendServiceIamBinding</description></item><item><title>IapWebBackendServiceIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebbackendserviceiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebbackendserviceiammember/</guid><description>IapWebBackendServiceIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebBackendServiceIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebBackendServiceIamMemberSpec status IapWebBackendServiceIamMemberStatus IapWebBackendServiceIamMemberSpec Appears on:IapWebBackendServiceIamMember, IapWebBackendServiceIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string webBackendService string IapWebBackendServiceIamMemberStatus Appears on:IapWebBackendServiceIamMember</description></item><item><title>IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebbackendserviceiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebbackendserviceiampolicy/</guid><description>IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicySpec status IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicyStatus IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicySpec Appears on:IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicy, IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) webBackendService string IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicyStatus Appears on:IapWebBackendServiceIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>IapWebIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebiambinding/</guid><description>IapWebIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebIamBindingSpec status IapWebIamBindingStatus IapWebIamBindingSpec Appears on:IapWebIamBinding, IapWebIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string IapWebIamBindingStatus Appears on:IapWebIamBinding</description></item><item><title>IapWebIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebiammember/</guid><description>IapWebIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebIamMemberSpec status IapWebIamMemberStatus IapWebIamMemberSpec Appears on:IapWebIamMember, IapWebIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string IapWebIamMemberStatus Appears on:IapWebIamMember</description></item><item><title>IapWebIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebiampolicy/</guid><description>IapWebIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebIamPolicySpec status IapWebIamPolicyStatus IapWebIamPolicySpec Appears on:IapWebIamPolicy, IapWebIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) IapWebIamPolicyStatus Appears on:IapWebIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypeappengineiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypeappengineiambinding/</guid><description>IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBindingSpec status IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBindingStatus IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBindingSpec Appears on:IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBinding, IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBindingStatus Appears on:IapWebTypeAppEngineIamBinding</description></item><item><title>IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypeappengineiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypeappengineiammember/</guid><description>IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMemberSpec status IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMemberStatus IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMemberSpec Appears on:IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMember, IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMemberStatus Appears on:IapWebTypeAppEngineIamMember</description></item><item><title>IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypeappengineiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypeappengineiampolicy/</guid><description>IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicySpec status IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicyStatus IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicySpec Appears on:IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicy, IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appID string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicyStatus Appears on:IapWebTypeAppEngineIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>IapWebTypeComputeIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypecomputeiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypecomputeiambinding/</guid><description>IapWebTypeComputeIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebTypeComputeIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebTypeComputeIamBindingSpec status IapWebTypeComputeIamBindingStatus IapWebTypeComputeIamBindingSpec Appears on:IapWebTypeComputeIamBinding, IapWebTypeComputeIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string project string (Optional) role string IapWebTypeComputeIamBindingStatus Appears on:IapWebTypeComputeIamBinding</description></item><item><title>IapWebTypeComputeIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypecomputeiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypecomputeiammember/</guid><description>IapWebTypeComputeIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebTypeComputeIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebTypeComputeIamMemberSpec status IapWebTypeComputeIamMemberStatus IapWebTypeComputeIamMemberSpec Appears on:IapWebTypeComputeIamMember, IapWebTypeComputeIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string project string (Optional) role string IapWebTypeComputeIamMemberStatus Appears on:IapWebTypeComputeIamMember</description></item><item><title>IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypecomputeiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/iapwebtypecomputeiampolicy/</guid><description>IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicySpec status IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicyStatus IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicySpec Appears on:IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicy, IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) policyData string project string (Optional) IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicyStatus Appears on:IapWebTypeComputeIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>KmsCryptoKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokey/</guid><description>KmsCryptoKey Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsCryptoKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsCryptoKeySpec status KmsCryptoKeyStatus KmsCryptoKeySpec Appears on:KmsCryptoKey, KmsCryptoKeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string keyRing string labels map[string]string (Optional) name string purpose string (Optional) rotationPeriod string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) versionTemplate []KmsCryptoKeySpecVersionTemplate (Optional) KmsCryptoKeySpecVersionTemplate Appears on:KmsCryptoKeySpec</description></item><item><title>KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiambinding/</guid><description>KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingSpec status KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingStatus KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingSpec Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding, KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cryptoKeyID string etag string (Optional) members []string role string KmsCryptoKeyIamBindingStatus Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamBinding</description></item><item><title>KmsCryptoKeyIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmscryptokeyiammember/</guid><description>KmsCryptoKeyIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsCryptoKeyIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberSpec status KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberStatus KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberSpec Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamMember, KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string cryptoKeyID string etag string (Optional) member string role string KmsCryptoKeyIamMemberStatus Appears on:KmsCryptoKeyIamMember</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRing</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyring/</guid><description>KmsKeyRing Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRing metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingSpec status KmsKeyRingStatus KmsKeyRingSpec Appears on:KmsKeyRing, KmsKeyRingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string project string (Optional) selfLink string (Optional) KmsKeyRingStatus Appears on:KmsKeyRing</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRingIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiambinding/</guid><description>KmsKeyRingIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRingIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingIamBindingSpec status KmsKeyRingIamBindingStatus KmsKeyRingIamBindingSpec Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamBinding, KmsKeyRingIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) keyRingID string members []string role string KmsKeyRingIamBindingStatus Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamBinding</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRingIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiammember/</guid><description>KmsKeyRingIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRingIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingIamMemberSpec status KmsKeyRingIamMemberStatus KmsKeyRingIamMemberSpec Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamMember, KmsKeyRingIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) keyRingID string member string role string KmsKeyRingIamMemberStatus Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamMember</description></item><item><title>KmsKeyRingIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/kmskeyringiampolicy/</guid><description>KmsKeyRingIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KmsKeyRingIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KmsKeyRingIamPolicySpec status KmsKeyRingIamPolicyStatus KmsKeyRingIamPolicySpec Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamPolicy, KmsKeyRingIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) keyRingID string policyData string KmsKeyRingIamPolicyStatus Appears on:KmsKeyRingIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>LoggingBillingAccountExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingBillingAccountExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingBillingAccountExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingBillingAccountExclusionSpec status LoggingBillingAccountExclusionStatus LoggingBillingAccountExclusionSpec Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountExclusion, LoggingBillingAccountExclusionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccount string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string name string LoggingBillingAccountExclusionStatus Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountExclusion</description></item><item><title>LoggingBillingAccountSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountsink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingbillingaccountsink/</guid><description>LoggingBillingAccountSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingBillingAccountSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingBillingAccountSinkSpec status LoggingBillingAccountSinkStatus LoggingBillingAccountSinkSpec Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountSink, LoggingBillingAccountSinkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string billingAccount string destination string filter string (Optional) name string writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingBillingAccountSinkStatus Appears on:LoggingBillingAccountSink</description></item><item><title>LoggingFolderExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfolderexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfolderexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingFolderExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingFolderExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingFolderExclusionSpec status LoggingFolderExclusionStatus LoggingFolderExclusionSpec Appears on:LoggingFolderExclusion, LoggingFolderExclusionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string folder string name string LoggingFolderExclusionStatus Appears on:LoggingFolderExclusion</description></item><item><title>LoggingFolderSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfoldersink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingfoldersink/</guid><description>LoggingFolderSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingFolderSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingFolderSinkSpec status LoggingFolderSinkStatus LoggingFolderSinkSpec Appears on:LoggingFolderSink, LoggingFolderSinkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string destination string filter string (Optional) folder string includeChildren bool (Optional) name string writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingFolderSinkStatus Appears on:LoggingFolderSink</description></item><item><title>LoggingMetric</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingmetric/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingmetric/</guid><description>LoggingMetric Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingMetric metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingMetricSpec status LoggingMetricStatus LoggingMetricSpec Appears on:LoggingMetric, LoggingMetricStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string bucketOptions []LoggingMetricSpecBucketOptions (Optional) description string (Optional) filter string labelExtractors map[string]string (Optional) metricDescriptor []LoggingMetricSpecMetricDescriptor name string project string (Optional) valueExtractor string (Optional) LoggingMetricSpecBucketOptions Appears on:LoggingMetricSpec</description></item><item><title>LoggingOrganizationExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingOrganizationExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingOrganizationExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingOrganizationExclusionSpec status LoggingOrganizationExclusionStatus LoggingOrganizationExclusionSpec Appears on:LoggingOrganizationExclusion, LoggingOrganizationExclusionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string name string orgID string LoggingOrganizationExclusionStatus Appears on:LoggingOrganizationExclusion</description></item><item><title>LoggingOrganizationSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationsink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingorganizationsink/</guid><description>LoggingOrganizationSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingOrganizationSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingOrganizationSinkSpec status LoggingOrganizationSinkStatus LoggingOrganizationSinkSpec Appears on:LoggingOrganizationSink, LoggingOrganizationSinkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string destination string filter string (Optional) includeChildren bool (Optional) name string orgID string writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingOrganizationSinkStatus Appears on:LoggingOrganizationSink</description></item><item><title>LoggingProjectExclusion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectexclusion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectexclusion/</guid><description>LoggingProjectExclusion Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingProjectExclusion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingProjectExclusionSpec status LoggingProjectExclusionStatus LoggingProjectExclusionSpec Appears on:LoggingProjectExclusion, LoggingProjectExclusionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) disabled bool (Optional) filter string name string project string (Optional) LoggingProjectExclusionStatus Appears on:LoggingProjectExclusion</description></item><item><title>LoggingProjectSink</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectsink/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/loggingprojectsink/</guid><description>LoggingProjectSink Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LoggingProjectSink metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoggingProjectSinkSpec status LoggingProjectSinkStatus LoggingProjectSinkSpec Appears on:LoggingProjectSink, LoggingProjectSinkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string destination string filter string (Optional) name string project string (Optional) uniqueWriterIdentity bool (Optional) writerIdentity string (Optional) LoggingProjectSinkStatus Appears on:LoggingProjectSink</description></item><item><title>MlEngineModel</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/mlenginemodel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/mlenginemodel/</guid><description>MlEngineModel Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MlEngineModel metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MlEngineModelSpec status MlEngineModelStatus MlEngineModelSpec Appears on:MlEngineModel, MlEngineModelStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string defaultVersion []MlEngineModelSpecDefaultVersion (Optional) description string (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string onlinePredictionConsoleLogging bool (Optional) onlinePredictionLogging bool (Optional) project string (Optional) regions []string (Optional) MlEngineModelSpecDefaultVersion Appears on:MlEngineModelSpec</description></item><item><title>MonitoringAlertPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringalertpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringalertpolicy/</guid><description>MonitoringAlertPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringAlertPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringAlertPolicySpec status MonitoringAlertPolicyStatus MonitoringAlertPolicySpec Appears on:MonitoringAlertPolicy, MonitoringAlertPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string combiner string conditions []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditions creationRecord []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecCreationRecord (Optional) displayName string documentation []MonitoringAlertPolicySpecDocumentation (Optional) enabled bool (Optional) labels []string (Optional) Deprecated name string (Optional) notificationChannels []string (Optional) project string (Optional) userLabels map[string]string (Optional) MonitoringAlertPolicySpecConditions Appears on:MonitoringAlertPolicySpec</description></item><item><title>MonitoringGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringgroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringgroup/</guid><description>MonitoringGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringGroupSpec status MonitoringGroupStatus MonitoringGroupSpec Appears on:MonitoringGroup, MonitoringGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string displayName string filter string isCluster bool (Optional) name string (Optional) parentName string (Optional) project string (Optional) MonitoringGroupStatus Appears on:MonitoringGroup</description></item><item><title>MonitoringNotificationChannel</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringnotificationchannel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringnotificationchannel/</guid><description>MonitoringNotificationChannel Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringNotificationChannel metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringNotificationChannelSpec status MonitoringNotificationChannelStatus MonitoringNotificationChannelSpec Appears on:MonitoringNotificationChannel, MonitoringNotificationChannelStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) displayName string enabled bool (Optional) labels map[string]string (Optional) name string (Optional) project string (Optional) type string userLabels map[string]string (Optional) verificationStatus string (Optional) MonitoringNotificationChannelStatus Appears on:MonitoringNotificationChannel</description></item><item><title>MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringuptimecheckconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/monitoringuptimecheckconfig/</guid><description>MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigSpec status MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigStatus MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigSpec Appears on:MonitoringUptimeCheckConfig, MonitoringUptimeCheckConfigStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiambinding/</guid><description>OrganizationIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamBindingSpec status OrganizationIamBindingStatus OrganizationIamBindingSpec Appears on:OrganizationIamBinding, OrganizationIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) members []string orgID string role string OrganizationIamBindingStatus Appears on:OrganizationIamBinding</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamCustomRole</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiamcustomrole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiamcustomrole/</guid><description>OrganizationIamCustomRole Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamCustomRole metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamCustomRoleSpec status OrganizationIamCustomRoleStatus OrganizationIamCustomRoleSpec Appears on:OrganizationIamCustomRole, OrganizationIamCustomRoleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string deleted bool (Optional) description string (Optional) orgID string permissions []string roleID string stage string (Optional) title string OrganizationIamCustomRoleStatus Appears on:OrganizationIamCustomRole</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiammember/</guid><description>OrganizationIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamMemberSpec status OrganizationIamMemberStatus OrganizationIamMemberSpec Appears on:OrganizationIamMember, OrganizationIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) member string orgID string role string OrganizationIamMemberStatus Appears on:OrganizationIamMember</description></item><item><title>OrganizationIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationiampolicy/</guid><description>OrganizationIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationIamPolicySpec status OrganizationIamPolicyStatus OrganizationIamPolicySpec Appears on:OrganizationIamPolicy, OrganizationIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string etag string (Optional) orgID string policyData string OrganizationIamPolicyStatus Appears on:OrganizationIamPolicy</description></item><item><title>OrganizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/organizationpolicy/</guid><description>OrganizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string OrganizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec OrganizationPolicySpec status OrganizationPolicyStatus OrganizationPolicySpec Appears on:OrganizationPolicy, OrganizationPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string booleanPolicy []OrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy (Optional) constraint string etag string (Optional) listPolicy []OrganizationPolicySpecListPolicy (Optional) orgID string restorePolicy []OrganizationPolicySpecRestorePolicy (Optional) updateTime string (Optional) version int64 (Optional) OrganizationPolicySpecBooleanPolicy Appears on:OrganizationPolicySpec</description></item><item><title>Project</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/project/</guid><description>Project Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Project metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectSpec status ProjectStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectStatus
ProjectSpec Appears on:Project, ProjectStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamAuditConfig</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiamauditconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiamauditconfig/</guid><description>ProjectIamAuditConfig Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamAuditConfig metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamAuditConfigSpec status ProjectIamAuditConfigStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectIamAuditConfigStatus
ProjectIamAuditConfigSpec Appears on:ProjectIamAuditConfig, ProjectIamAuditConfigStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiambinding/</guid><description>ProjectIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamBindingSpec status ProjectIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectIamBindingStatus
ProjectIamBindingSpec Appears on:ProjectIamBinding, ProjectIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamCustomRole</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiamcustomrole/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiamcustomrole/</guid><description>ProjectIamCustomRole Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamCustomRole metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamCustomRoleSpec status ProjectIamCustomRoleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectIamCustomRoleStatus
ProjectIamCustomRoleSpec Appears on:ProjectIamCustomRole, ProjectIamCustomRoleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiammember/</guid><description>ProjectIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamMemberSpec status ProjectIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectIamMemberStatus
ProjectIamMemberSpec Appears on:ProjectIamMember, ProjectIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectiampolicy/</guid><description>ProjectIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectIamPolicySpec status ProjectIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectIamPolicyStatus
ProjectIamPolicySpec Appears on:ProjectIamPolicy, ProjectIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectOrganizationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectorganizationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectorganizationpolicy/</guid><description>ProjectOrganizationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectOrganizationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectOrganizationPolicySpec status ProjectOrganizationPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicyStatus
ProjectOrganizationPolicySpec Appears on:ProjectOrganizationPolicy, ProjectOrganizationPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservice/</guid><description>ProjectService Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectServiceSpec status ProjectServiceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectServiceStatus
ProjectServiceSpec Appears on:ProjectService, ProjectServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectServiceBatch</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservicebatch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservicebatch/</guid><description>ProjectServiceBatch Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectServiceBatch metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectServiceBatchSpec status ProjectServiceBatchStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectServiceBatchStatus
ProjectServiceBatchSpec Appears on:ProjectServiceBatch, ProjectServiceBatchStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectServices</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectservices/</guid><description>ProjectServices Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectServices metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectServicesSpec status ProjectServicesStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectServicesStatus
ProjectServicesSpec Appears on:ProjectServices, ProjectServicesStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ProjectUsageExportBucket</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectusageexportbucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/projectusageexportbucket/</guid><description>ProjectUsageExportBucket Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ProjectUsageExportBucket metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectUsageExportBucketSpec status ProjectUsageExportBucketStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ProjectUsageExportBucketStatus
ProjectUsageExportBucketSpec Appears on:ProjectUsageExportBucket, ProjectUsageExportBucketStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscription</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscription/</guid><description>PubsubSubscription Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscription metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionSpec status PubsubSubscriptionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionStatus
PubsubSubscriptionSpec Appears on:PubsubSubscription, PubsubSubscriptionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniambinding/</guid><description>PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingSpec status PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingStatus
PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingSpec Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamBinding, PubsubSubscriptionIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscriptionIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniammember/</guid><description>PubsubSubscriptionIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscriptionIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberSpec status PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberStatus
PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberSpec Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamMember, PubsubSubscriptionIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubsubscriptioniampolicy/</guid><description>PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicySpec status PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicyStatus
PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicySpec Appears on:PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicy, PubsubSubscriptionIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopic</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopic/</guid><description>PubsubTopic Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopic metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicSpec status PubsubTopicStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubTopicStatus
PubsubTopicSpec Appears on:PubsubTopic, PubsubTopicStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopicIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciambinding/</guid><description>PubsubTopicIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopicIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicIamBindingSpec status PubsubTopicIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubTopicIamBindingStatus
PubsubTopicIamBindingSpec Appears on:PubsubTopicIamBinding, PubsubTopicIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopicIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciammember/</guid><description>PubsubTopicIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopicIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicIamMemberSpec status PubsubTopicIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubTopicIamMemberStatus
PubsubTopicIamMemberSpec Appears on:PubsubTopicIamMember, PubsubTopicIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PubsubTopicIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/pubsubtopiciampolicy/</guid><description>PubsubTopicIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PubsubTopicIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PubsubTopicIamPolicySpec status PubsubTopicIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PubsubTopicIamPolicyStatus
PubsubTopicIamPolicySpec Appears on:PubsubTopicIamPolicy, PubsubTopicIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RedisInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/redisinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/redisinstance/</guid><description>RedisInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RedisInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RedisInstanceSpec status RedisInstanceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RedisInstanceStatus
RedisInstanceSpec Appears on:RedisInstance, RedisInstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ResourceManagerLien</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/resourcemanagerlien/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/resourcemanagerlien/</guid><description>ResourceManagerLien Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ResourceManagerLien metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ResourceManagerLienSpec status ResourceManagerLienStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ResourceManagerLienStatus
ResourceManagerLienSpec Appears on:ResourceManagerLien, ResourceManagerLienStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RuntimeconfigConfig</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfig/</guid><description>RuntimeconfigConfig Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RuntimeconfigConfig metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RuntimeconfigConfigSpec status RuntimeconfigConfigStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfigStatus
RuntimeconfigConfigSpec Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfig, RuntimeconfigConfigStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RuntimeconfigConfigIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfigiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfigiambinding/</guid><description>RuntimeconfigConfigIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RuntimeconfigConfigIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RuntimeconfigConfigIamBindingSpec status RuntimeconfigConfigIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfigIamBindingStatus
RuntimeconfigConfigIamBindingSpec Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfigIamBinding, RuntimeconfigConfigIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RuntimeconfigConfigIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfigiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfigiammember/</guid><description>RuntimeconfigConfigIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RuntimeconfigConfigIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RuntimeconfigConfigIamMemberSpec status RuntimeconfigConfigIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfigIamMemberStatus
RuntimeconfigConfigIamMemberSpec Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfigIamMember, RuntimeconfigConfigIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfigiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigconfigiampolicy/</guid><description>RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicySpec status RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicyStatus
RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicySpec Appears on:RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicy, RuntimeconfigConfigIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RuntimeconfigVariable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigvariable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/runtimeconfigvariable/</guid><description>RuntimeconfigVariable Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RuntimeconfigVariable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RuntimeconfigVariableSpec status RuntimeconfigVariableStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RuntimeconfigVariableStatus
RuntimeconfigVariableSpec Appears on:RuntimeconfigVariable, RuntimeconfigVariableStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SccSource</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sccsource/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sccsource/</guid><description>SccSource Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SccSource metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SccSourceSpec status SccSourceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SccSourceStatus
SccSourceSpec Appears on:SccSource, SccSourceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccount/</guid><description>ServiceAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountSpec status ServiceAccountStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServiceAccountStatus
ServiceAccountSpec Appears on:ServiceAccount, ServiceAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiambinding/</guid><description>ServiceAccountIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountIamBindingSpec status ServiceAccountIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServiceAccountIamBindingStatus
ServiceAccountIamBindingSpec Appears on:ServiceAccountIamBinding, ServiceAccountIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiammember/</guid><description>ServiceAccountIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountIamMemberSpec status ServiceAccountIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServiceAccountIamMemberStatus
ServiceAccountIamMemberSpec Appears on:ServiceAccountIamMember, ServiceAccountIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountiampolicy/</guid><description>ServiceAccountIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountIamPolicySpec status ServiceAccountIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServiceAccountIamPolicyStatus
ServiceAccountIamPolicySpec Appears on:ServiceAccountIamPolicy, ServiceAccountIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServiceAccountKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountkey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/serviceaccountkey/</guid><description>ServiceAccountKey Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceAccountKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceAccountKeySpec status ServiceAccountKeyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServiceAccountKeyStatus
ServiceAccountKeySpec Appears on:ServiceAccountKey, ServiceAccountKeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServiceNetworkingConnection</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/servicenetworkingconnection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/servicenetworkingconnection/</guid><description>ServiceNetworkingConnection Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceNetworkingConnection metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceNetworkingConnectionSpec status ServiceNetworkingConnectionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServiceNetworkingConnectionStatus
ServiceNetworkingConnectionSpec Appears on:ServiceNetworkingConnection, ServiceNetworkingConnectionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SourcerepoRepository</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepository/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepository/</guid><description>SourcerepoRepository Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SourcerepoRepository metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SourcerepoRepositorySpec status SourcerepoRepositoryStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SourcerepoRepositoryStatus
SourcerepoRepositorySpec Appears on:SourcerepoRepository, SourcerepoRepositoryStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SourcerepoRepositoryIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepositoryiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepositoryiambinding/</guid><description>SourcerepoRepositoryIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SourcerepoRepositoryIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SourcerepoRepositoryIamBindingSpec status SourcerepoRepositoryIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SourcerepoRepositoryIamBindingStatus
SourcerepoRepositoryIamBindingSpec Appears on:SourcerepoRepositoryIamBinding, SourcerepoRepositoryIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SourcerepoRepositoryIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepositoryiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepositoryiammember/</guid><description>SourcerepoRepositoryIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SourcerepoRepositoryIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SourcerepoRepositoryIamMemberSpec status SourcerepoRepositoryIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SourcerepoRepositoryIamMemberStatus
SourcerepoRepositoryIamMemberSpec Appears on:SourcerepoRepositoryIamMember, SourcerepoRepositoryIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepositoryiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sourcereporepositoryiampolicy/</guid><description>SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicySpec status SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicyStatus
SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicySpec Appears on:SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicy, SourcerepoRepositoryIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabase/</guid><description>SpannerDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseSpec status SpannerDatabaseStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerDatabaseStatus
SpannerDatabaseSpec Appears on:SpannerDatabase, SpannerDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabaseIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiambinding/</guid><description>SpannerDatabaseIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabaseIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseIamBindingSpec status SpannerDatabaseIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamBindingStatus
SpannerDatabaseIamBindingSpec Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamBinding, SpannerDatabaseIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabaseIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiammember/</guid><description>SpannerDatabaseIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabaseIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseIamMemberSpec status SpannerDatabaseIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamMemberStatus
SpannerDatabaseIamMemberSpec Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamMember, SpannerDatabaseIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerdatabaseiampolicy/</guid><description>SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerDatabaseIamPolicySpec status SpannerDatabaseIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamPolicyStatus
SpannerDatabaseIamPolicySpec Appears on:SpannerDatabaseIamPolicy, SpannerDatabaseIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstance/</guid><description>SpannerInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceSpec status SpannerInstanceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerInstanceStatus
SpannerInstanceSpec Appears on:SpannerInstance, SpannerInstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstanceIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiambinding/</guid><description>SpannerInstanceIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstanceIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceIamBindingSpec status SpannerInstanceIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamBindingStatus
SpannerInstanceIamBindingSpec Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamBinding, SpannerInstanceIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstanceIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiammember/</guid><description>SpannerInstanceIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstanceIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceIamMemberSpec status SpannerInstanceIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamMemberStatus
SpannerInstanceIamMemberSpec Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamMember, SpannerInstanceIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SpannerInstanceIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/spannerinstanceiampolicy/</guid><description>SpannerInstanceIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpannerInstanceIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpannerInstanceIamPolicySpec status SpannerInstanceIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamPolicyStatus
SpannerInstanceIamPolicySpec Appears on:SpannerInstanceIamPolicy, SpannerInstanceIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabase/</guid><description>SqlDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlDatabaseSpec status SqlDatabaseStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlDatabaseStatus
SqlDatabaseSpec Appears on:SqlDatabase, SqlDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlDatabaseInstance</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabaseinstance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqldatabaseinstance/</guid><description>SqlDatabaseInstance Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlDatabaseInstance metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlDatabaseInstanceSpec status SqlDatabaseInstanceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlDatabaseInstanceStatus
SqlDatabaseInstanceSpec Appears on:SqlDatabaseInstance, SqlDatabaseInstanceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlSSLCert</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqlsslcert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqlsslcert/</guid><description>SqlSSLCert Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlSSLCert metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlSSLCertSpec status SqlSSLCertStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlSSLCertStatus
SqlSSLCertSpec Appears on:SqlSSLCert, SqlSSLCertStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlUser</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqluser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/sqluser/</guid><description>SqlUser Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlUser metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlUserSpec status SqlUserStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlUserStatus
SqlUserSpec Appears on:SqlUser, SqlUserStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucket</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucket/</guid><description>StorageBucket Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucket metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketSpec status StorageBucketStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBucketStatus
StorageBucketSpec Appears on:StorageBucket, StorageBucketStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketAccessControl</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketaccesscontrol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketaccesscontrol/</guid><description>StorageBucketAccessControl Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketAccessControl metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketAccessControlSpec status StorageBucketAccessControlStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBucketAccessControlStatus
StorageBucketAccessControlSpec Appears on:StorageBucketAccessControl, StorageBucketAccessControlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketACL</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketacl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketacl/</guid><description>StorageBucketACL Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketACL metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketACLSpec status StorageBucketACLStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBucketACLStatus
StorageBucketACLSpec Appears on:StorageBucketACL, StorageBucketACLStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketIamBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiambinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiambinding/</guid><description>StorageBucketIamBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketIamBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketIamBindingSpec status StorageBucketIamBindingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBucketIamBindingStatus
StorageBucketIamBindingSpec Appears on:StorageBucketIamBinding, StorageBucketIamBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketIamMember</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiammember/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiammember/</guid><description>StorageBucketIamMember Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketIamMember metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketIamMemberSpec status StorageBucketIamMemberStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBucketIamMemberStatus
StorageBucketIamMemberSpec Appears on:StorageBucketIamMember, StorageBucketIamMemberStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketIamPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiampolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketiampolicy/</guid><description>StorageBucketIamPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketIamPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketIamPolicySpec status StorageBucketIamPolicyStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBucketIamPolicyStatus
StorageBucketIamPolicySpec Appears on:StorageBucketIamPolicy, StorageBucketIamPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBucketObject</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketobject/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagebucketobject/</guid><description>StorageBucketObject Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBucketObject metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBucketObjectSpec status StorageBucketObjectStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBucketObjectStatus
StorageBucketObjectSpec Appears on:StorageBucketObject, StorageBucketObjectStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectaccesscontrol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectaccesscontrol/</guid><description>StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlSpec status StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlStatus
StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlSpec Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectAccessControl, StorageDefaultObjectAccessControlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageDefaultObjectACL</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectacl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagedefaultobjectacl/</guid><description>StorageDefaultObjectACL Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageDefaultObjectACL metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageDefaultObjectACLSpec status StorageDefaultObjectACLStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectACLStatus
StorageDefaultObjectACLSpec Appears on:StorageDefaultObjectACL, StorageDefaultObjectACLStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageNotification</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagenotification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagenotification/</guid><description>StorageNotification Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageNotification metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageNotificationSpec status StorageNotificationStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageNotificationStatus
StorageNotificationSpec Appears on:StorageNotification, StorageNotificationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageObjectAccessControl</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectaccesscontrol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectaccesscontrol/</guid><description>StorageObjectAccessControl Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageObjectAccessControl metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageObjectAccessControlSpec status StorageObjectAccessControlStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageObjectAccessControlStatus
StorageObjectAccessControlSpec Appears on:StorageObjectAccessControl, StorageObjectAccessControlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageObjectACL</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectacl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storageobjectacl/</guid><description>StorageObjectACL Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageObjectACL metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageObjectACLSpec status StorageObjectACLStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageObjectACLStatus
StorageObjectACLSpec Appears on:StorageObjectACL, StorageObjectACLStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageTransferJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagetransferjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/storagetransferjob/</guid><description>StorageTransferJob Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageTransferJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageTransferJobSpec status StorageTransferJobStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageTransferJobStatus
StorageTransferJobSpec Appears on:StorageTransferJob, StorageTransferJobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>TpuNode</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/tpunode/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v2020.10.30/reference/google.kubeform.com/tpunode/</guid><description>TpuNode Field Type Description apiVersion string google.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string TpuNode metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec TpuNodeSpec status TpuNodeStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:TpuNodeStatus
TpuNodeSpec Appears on:TpuNode, TpuNodeStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item></channel></rss>