<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | Azure on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | Azure on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AnalysisServicesServer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/analysisservicesserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/analysisservicesserver/</guid><description>AnalysisServicesServer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AnalysisServicesServer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AnalysisServicesServerSpec status AnalysisServicesServerStatus AnalysisServicesServerSpec Appears on:AnalysisServicesServer, AnalysisServicesServerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string adminUsers []string (Optional) enablePowerBiService bool (Optional) ipv4FirewallRule []AnalysisServicesServerSpecIpv4FirewallRule (Optional) location string name string querypoolConnectionMode string (Optional) resourceGroupName string sku string tags map[string]string (Optional) AnalysisServicesServerSpecIpv4FirewallRule Appears on:AnalysisServicesServerSpec</description></item><item><title>ApiManagement</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagement/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagement/</guid><description>ApiManagement Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagement metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementSpec status ApiManagementStatus ApiManagementSpec Appears on:ApiManagement, ApiManagementStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementAPI</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapi/</guid><description>ApiManagementAPI Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementAPI metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementAPISpec status ApiManagementAPIStatus ApiManagementAPISpec Appears on:ApiManagementAPI, ApiManagementAPIStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string description string (Optional) displayName string import []ApiManagementAPISpecImport (Optional) isCurrent bool (Optional) isOnline bool (Optional) name string path string protocols []string resourceGroupName string revision string serviceURL string (Optional) soapPassThrough bool (Optional) subscriptionKeyParameterNames []ApiManagementAPISpecSubscriptionKeyParameterNames (Optional) version string (Optional) versionSetID string (Optional) ApiManagementAPISpecImport Appears on:ApiManagementAPISpec</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementAPIOperation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapioperation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapioperation/</guid><description>ApiManagementAPIOperation Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementAPIOperation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementAPIOperationSpec status ApiManagementAPIOperationStatus ApiManagementAPIOperationSpec Appears on:ApiManagementAPIOperation, ApiManagementAPIOperationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string apiName string description string (Optional) displayName string method string operationID string request []ApiManagementAPIOperationSpecRequest (Optional) resourceGroupName string response []ApiManagementAPIOperationSpecResponse (Optional) templateParameter []ApiManagementAPIOperationSpecTemplateParameter (Optional) urlTemplate string ApiManagementAPIOperationSpecRequest Appears on:ApiManagementAPIOperationSpec</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapioperationpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapioperationpolicy/</guid><description>ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicySpec status ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicyStatus ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicySpec Appears on:ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicy, ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string apiName string operationID string resourceGroupName string xmlContent string (Optional) xmlLink string (Optional) ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicyStatus Appears on:ApiManagementAPIOperationPolicy</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementAPIPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapipolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapipolicy/</guid><description>ApiManagementAPIPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementAPIPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementAPIPolicySpec status ApiManagementAPIPolicyStatus ApiManagementAPIPolicySpec Appears on:ApiManagementAPIPolicy, ApiManagementAPIPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string apiName string resourceGroupName string xmlContent string (Optional) xmlLink string (Optional) ApiManagementAPIPolicyStatus Appears on:ApiManagementAPIPolicy</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementAPISchema</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapischema/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapischema/</guid><description>ApiManagementAPISchema Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementAPISchema metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementAPISchemaSpec status ApiManagementAPISchemaStatus ApiManagementAPISchemaSpec Appears on:ApiManagementAPISchema, ApiManagementAPISchemaStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string apiName string contentType string resourceGroupName string schemaID string value string ApiManagementAPISchemaStatus Appears on:ApiManagementAPISchema</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementAPIVersionSet</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapiversionset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementapiversionset/</guid><description>ApiManagementAPIVersionSet Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementAPIVersionSet metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementAPIVersionSetSpec status ApiManagementAPIVersionSetStatus ApiManagementAPIVersionSetSpec Appears on:ApiManagementAPIVersionSet, ApiManagementAPIVersionSetStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string description string (Optional) displayName string name string resourceGroupName string versionHeaderName string (Optional) versionQueryName string (Optional) versioningScheme string ApiManagementAPIVersionSetStatus Appears on:ApiManagementAPIVersionSet</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementAuthorizationServer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementauthorizationserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementauthorizationserver/</guid><description>ApiManagementAuthorizationServer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementAuthorizationServer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementAuthorizationServerSpec status ApiManagementAuthorizationServerStatus ApiManagementAuthorizationServerSpec Appears on:ApiManagementAuthorizationServer, ApiManagementAuthorizationServerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementBackend</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementbackend/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementbackend/</guid><description>ApiManagementBackend Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementBackend metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementBackendSpec status ApiManagementBackendStatus ApiManagementBackendSpec Appears on:ApiManagementBackend, ApiManagementBackendStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementCertificate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementcertificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementcertificate/</guid><description>ApiManagementCertificate Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementCertificate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementCertificateSpec status ApiManagementCertificateStatus ApiManagementCertificateSpec Appears on:ApiManagementCertificate, ApiManagementCertificateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementgroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementgroup/</guid><description>ApiManagementGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementGroupSpec status ApiManagementGroupStatus ApiManagementGroupSpec Appears on:ApiManagementGroup, ApiManagementGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string description string (Optional) displayName string externalID string (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string type string (Optional) ApiManagementGroupStatus Appears on:ApiManagementGroup</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementGroupUser</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementgroupuser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementgroupuser/</guid><description>ApiManagementGroupUser Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementGroupUser metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementGroupUserSpec status ApiManagementGroupUserStatus ApiManagementGroupUserSpec Appears on:ApiManagementGroupUser, ApiManagementGroupUserStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string groupName string resourceGroupName string userID string ApiManagementGroupUserStatus Appears on:ApiManagementGroupUser</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementLogger</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementlogger/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementlogger/</guid><description>ApiManagementLogger Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementLogger metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementLoggerSpec status ApiManagementLoggerStatus ApiManagementLoggerSpec Appears on:ApiManagementLogger, ApiManagementLoggerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementOpenidConnectProvider</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementopenidconnectprovider/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementopenidconnectprovider/</guid><description>ApiManagementOpenidConnectProvider Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementOpenidConnectProvider metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementOpenidConnectProviderSpec status ApiManagementOpenidConnectProviderStatus ApiManagementOpenidConnectProviderSpec Appears on:ApiManagementOpenidConnectProvider, ApiManagementOpenidConnectProviderStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementProduct</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproduct/</guid><description>ApiManagementProduct Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementProduct metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementProductSpec status ApiManagementProductStatus ApiManagementProductSpec Appears on:ApiManagementProduct, ApiManagementProductStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string approvalRequired bool (Optional) description string (Optional) displayName string productID string published bool resourceGroupName string subscriptionRequired bool subscriptionsLimit int (Optional) terms string (Optional) ApiManagementProductStatus Appears on:ApiManagementProduct</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementProductAPI</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproductapi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproductapi/</guid><description>ApiManagementProductAPI Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementProductAPI metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementProductAPISpec status ApiManagementProductAPIStatus ApiManagementProductAPISpec Appears on:ApiManagementProductAPI, ApiManagementProductAPIStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string apiName string productID string resourceGroupName string ApiManagementProductAPIStatus Appears on:ApiManagementProductAPI</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementProductGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproductgroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproductgroup/</guid><description>ApiManagementProductGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementProductGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementProductGroupSpec status ApiManagementProductGroupStatus ApiManagementProductGroupSpec Appears on:ApiManagementProductGroup, ApiManagementProductGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string groupName string productID string resourceGroupName string ApiManagementProductGroupStatus Appears on:ApiManagementProductGroup</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementProductPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproductpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproductpolicy/</guid><description>ApiManagementProductPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementProductPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementProductPolicySpec status ApiManagementProductPolicyStatus ApiManagementProductPolicySpec Appears on:ApiManagementProductPolicy, ApiManagementProductPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string productID string resourceGroupName string xmlContent string (Optional) xmlLink string (Optional) ApiManagementProductPolicyStatus Appears on:ApiManagementProductPolicy</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementProperty</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproperty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementproperty/</guid><description>ApiManagementProperty Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementProperty metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementPropertySpec status ApiManagementPropertyStatus ApiManagementPropertySpec Appears on:ApiManagementProperty, ApiManagementPropertyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string apiManagementName string displayName string name string resourceGroupName string secret bool (Optional) tags []string (Optional) value string ApiManagementPropertyStatus Appears on:ApiManagementProperty</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementSubscription</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementsubscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementsubscription/</guid><description>ApiManagementSubscription Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementSubscription metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementSubscriptionSpec status ApiManagementSubscriptionStatus ApiManagementSubscriptionSpec Appears on:ApiManagementSubscription, ApiManagementSubscriptionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApiManagementUser</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementuser/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/apimanagementuser/</guid><description>ApiManagementUser Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApiManagementUser metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApiManagementUserSpec status ApiManagementUserStatus ApiManagementUserSpec Appears on:ApiManagementUser, ApiManagementUserStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApplicationGateway</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationgateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationgateway/</guid><description>ApplicationGateway Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApplicationGateway metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApplicationGatewaySpec status ApplicationGatewayStatus ApplicationGatewaySpec Appears on:ApplicationGateway, ApplicationGatewayStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApplicationInsights</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationinsights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationinsights/</guid><description>ApplicationInsights Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApplicationInsights metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApplicationInsightsSpec status ApplicationInsightsStatus ApplicationInsightsSpec Appears on:ApplicationInsights, ApplicationInsightsStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApplicationInsightsAPIKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationinsightsapikey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationinsightsapikey/</guid><description>ApplicationInsightsAPIKey Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApplicationInsightsAPIKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApplicationInsightsAPIKeySpec status ApplicationInsightsAPIKeyStatus ApplicationInsightsAPIKeySpec Appears on:ApplicationInsightsAPIKey, ApplicationInsightsAPIKeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ApplicationInsightsWebTest</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationinsightswebtest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationinsightswebtest/</guid><description>ApplicationInsightsWebTest Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApplicationInsightsWebTest metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApplicationInsightsWebTestSpec status ApplicationInsightsWebTestStatus ApplicationInsightsWebTestSpec Appears on:ApplicationInsightsWebTest, ApplicationInsightsWebTestStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string applicationInsightsID string configuration string description string (Optional) enabled bool (Optional) frequency int (Optional) geoLocations []string kind string location string name string resourceGroupName string retryEnabled bool (Optional) syntheticMonitorID string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) timeout int (Optional) ApplicationInsightsWebTestStatus Appears on:ApplicationInsightsWebTest</description></item><item><title>ApplicationSecurityGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationsecuritygroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/applicationsecuritygroup/</guid><description>ApplicationSecurityGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ApplicationSecurityGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ApplicationSecurityGroupSpec status ApplicationSecurityGroupStatus ApplicationSecurityGroupSpec Appears on:ApplicationSecurityGroup, ApplicationSecurityGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ApplicationSecurityGroupStatus Appears on:ApplicationSecurityGroup</description></item><item><title>AppService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appservice/</guid><description>AppService Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppServiceSpec status AppServiceStatus AppServiceSpec Appears on:AppService, AppServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>AppServiceActiveSlot</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appserviceactiveslot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appserviceactiveslot/</guid><description>AppServiceActiveSlot Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppServiceActiveSlot metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppServiceActiveSlotSpec status AppServiceActiveSlotStatus AppServiceActiveSlotSpec Appears on:AppServiceActiveSlot, AppServiceActiveSlotStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appServiceName string appServiceSlotName string resourceGroupName string AppServiceActiveSlotStatus Appears on:AppServiceActiveSlot</description></item><item><title>AppServiceCustomHostnameBinding</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appservicecustomhostnamebinding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appservicecustomhostnamebinding/</guid><description>AppServiceCustomHostnameBinding Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppServiceCustomHostnameBinding metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppServiceCustomHostnameBindingSpec status AppServiceCustomHostnameBindingStatus AppServiceCustomHostnameBindingSpec Appears on:AppServiceCustomHostnameBinding, AppServiceCustomHostnameBindingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appServiceName string hostname string resourceGroupName string AppServiceCustomHostnameBindingStatus Appears on:AppServiceCustomHostnameBinding</description></item><item><title>AppServicePlan</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appserviceplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appserviceplan/</guid><description>AppServicePlan Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppServicePlan metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppServicePlanSpec status AppServicePlanStatus AppServicePlanSpec Appears on:AppServicePlan, AppServicePlanStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appServiceEnvironmentID string (Optional) isXenon bool (Optional) kind string (Optional) location string maximumElasticWorkerCount int (Optional) maximumNumberOfWorkers int (Optional) name string perSiteScaling bool (Optional) properties []AppServicePlanSpecProperties (Optional) Deprecated reserved bool (Optional) resourceGroupName string sku []AppServicePlanSpecSku tags map[string]string (Optional) AppServicePlanSpecProperties Appears on:AppServicePlanSpec</description></item><item><title>AppServiceSlot</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appserviceslot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/appserviceslot/</guid><description>AppServiceSlot Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AppServiceSlot metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AppServiceSlotSpec status AppServiceSlotStatus AppServiceSlotSpec Appears on:AppServiceSlot, AppServiceSlotStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>AutomationAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationaccount/</guid><description>AutomationAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationAccountSpec status AutomationAccountStatus AutomationAccountSpec Appears on:AutomationAccount, AutomationAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string dscPrimaryAccessKey string (Optional) dscSecondaryAccessKey string (Optional) dscServerEndpoint string (Optional) location string name string resourceGroupName string sku []AutomationAccountSpecSku (Optional) Deprecated skuName string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) AutomationAccountSpecSku Appears on:AutomationAccountSpec</description></item><item><title>AutomationCredential</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationcredential/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationcredential/</guid><description>AutomationCredential Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationCredential metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationCredentialSpec status AutomationCredentialStatus AutomationCredentialSpec Appears on:AutomationCredential, AutomationCredentialStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>AutomationDscConfiguration</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationdscconfiguration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationdscconfiguration/</guid><description>AutomationDscConfiguration Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationDscConfiguration metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationDscConfigurationSpec status AutomationDscConfigurationStatus AutomationDscConfigurationSpec Appears on:AutomationDscConfiguration, AutomationDscConfigurationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string automationAccountName string contentEmbedded string description string (Optional) location string logVerbose bool (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string state string (Optional) AutomationDscConfigurationStatus Appears on:AutomationDscConfiguration</description></item><item><title>AutomationDscNodeconfiguration</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationdscnodeconfiguration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationdscnodeconfiguration/</guid><description>AutomationDscNodeconfiguration Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationDscNodeconfiguration metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationDscNodeconfigurationSpec status AutomationDscNodeconfigurationStatus AutomationDscNodeconfigurationSpec Appears on:AutomationDscNodeconfiguration, AutomationDscNodeconfigurationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string automationAccountName string configurationName string (Optional) contentEmbedded string name string resourceGroupName string AutomationDscNodeconfigurationStatus Appears on:AutomationDscNodeconfiguration</description></item><item><title>AutomationModule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationmodule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationmodule/</guid><description>AutomationModule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationModule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationModuleSpec status AutomationModuleStatus AutomationModuleSpec Appears on:AutomationModule, AutomationModuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string automationAccountName string moduleLink []AutomationModuleSpecModuleLink name string resourceGroupName string AutomationModuleSpecModuleLink Appears on:AutomationModuleSpec</description></item><item><title>AutomationRunbook</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationrunbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationrunbook/</guid><description>AutomationRunbook Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationRunbook metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationRunbookSpec status AutomationRunbookStatus AutomationRunbookSpec Appears on:AutomationRunbook, AutomationRunbookStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string content string (Optional) description string (Optional) location string logProgress bool logVerbose bool name string publishContentLink []AutomationRunbookSpecPublishContentLink resourceGroupName string runbookType string tags map[string]string (Optional) AutomationRunbookSpecPublishContentLink Appears on:AutomationRunbookSpec</description></item><item><title>AutomationSchedule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationschedule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationschedule/</guid><description>AutomationSchedule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationSchedule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationScheduleSpec status AutomationScheduleStatus AutomationScheduleSpec Appears on:AutomationSchedule, AutomationScheduleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string (Optional) Deprecated automationAccountName string (Optional) description string (Optional) expiryTime string (Optional) frequency string interval int (Optional) monthDays []int64 (Optional) monthlyOccurrence []AutomationScheduleSpecMonthlyOccurrence (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string startTime string (Optional) timezone string (Optional) weekDays []string (Optional) AutomationScheduleSpecMonthlyOccurrence Appears on:AutomationScheduleSpec</description></item><item><title>AutomationVariableBool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariablebool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariablebool/</guid><description>AutomationVariableBool Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationVariableBool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationVariableBoolSpec status AutomationVariableBoolStatus AutomationVariableBoolSpec Appears on:AutomationVariableBool, AutomationVariableBoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string automationAccountName string description string (Optional) encrypted bool (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string value bool (Optional) AutomationVariableBoolStatus Appears on:AutomationVariableBool</description></item><item><title>AutomationVariableDatetime</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariabledatetime/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariabledatetime/</guid><description>AutomationVariableDatetime Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationVariableDatetime metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationVariableDatetimeSpec status AutomationVariableDatetimeStatus AutomationVariableDatetimeSpec Appears on:AutomationVariableDatetime, AutomationVariableDatetimeStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string automationAccountName string description string (Optional) encrypted bool (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string value string (Optional) AutomationVariableDatetimeStatus Appears on:AutomationVariableDatetime</description></item><item><title>AutomationVariableInt</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariableint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariableint/</guid><description>AutomationVariableInt Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationVariableInt metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationVariableIntSpec status AutomationVariableIntStatus AutomationVariableIntSpec Appears on:AutomationVariableInt, AutomationVariableIntStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string automationAccountName string description string (Optional) encrypted bool (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string value int (Optional) AutomationVariableIntStatus Appears on:AutomationVariableInt</description></item><item><title>AutomationVariableString</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariablestring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/automationvariablestring/</guid><description>AutomationVariableString Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutomationVariableString metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutomationVariableStringSpec status AutomationVariableStringStatus AutomationVariableStringSpec Appears on:AutomationVariableString, AutomationVariableStringStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string automationAccountName string description string (Optional) encrypted bool (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string value string (Optional) AutomationVariableStringStatus Appears on:AutomationVariableString</description></item><item><title>AutoscaleSetting</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/autoscalesetting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/autoscalesetting/</guid><description>AutoscaleSetting Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AutoscaleSetting metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AutoscaleSettingSpec status AutoscaleSettingStatus AutoscaleSettingSpec Appears on:AutoscaleSetting, AutoscaleSettingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string enabled bool (Optional) location string name string notification []AutoscaleSettingSpecNotification (Optional) profile []AutoscaleSettingSpecProfile resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) targetResourceID string AutoscaleSettingSpecNotification Appears on:AutoscaleSettingSpec</description></item><item><title>AvailabilitySet</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/availabilityset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/availabilityset/</guid><description>AvailabilitySet Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AvailabilitySet metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AvailabilitySetSpec status AvailabilitySetStatus AvailabilitySetSpec Appears on:AvailabilitySet, AvailabilitySetStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string managed bool (Optional) name string platformFaultDomainCount int (Optional) platformUpdateDomainCount int (Optional) resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) AvailabilitySetStatus Appears on:AvailabilitySet</description></item><item><title>AzureadApplication</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/azureadapplication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/azureadapplication/</guid><description>AzureadApplication Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AzureadApplication metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AzureadApplicationSpec status AzureadApplicationStatus AzureadApplicationSpec Appears on:AzureadApplication, AzureadApplicationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string applicationID string (Optional) availableToOtherTenants bool (Optional) homepage string (Optional) identifierUris []string (Optional) name string oauth2AllowImplicitFlow bool (Optional) replyUrls []string (Optional) AzureadApplicationStatus Appears on:AzureadApplication</description></item><item><title>AzureadServicePrincipal</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/azureadserviceprincipal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/azureadserviceprincipal/</guid><description>AzureadServicePrincipal Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AzureadServicePrincipal metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AzureadServicePrincipalSpec status AzureadServicePrincipalStatus AzureadServicePrincipalSpec Appears on:AzureadServicePrincipal, AzureadServicePrincipalStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string applicationID string displayName string (Optional) AzureadServicePrincipalStatus Appears on:AzureadServicePrincipal</description></item><item><title>AzureadServicePrincipalPassword</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/azureadserviceprincipalpassword/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/azureadserviceprincipalpassword/</guid><description>AzureadServicePrincipalPassword Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string AzureadServicePrincipalPassword metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec AzureadServicePrincipalPasswordSpec status AzureadServicePrincipalPasswordStatus AzureadServicePrincipalPasswordSpec Appears on:AzureadServicePrincipalPassword, AzureadServicePrincipalPasswordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>BatchAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchaccount/</guid><description>BatchAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BatchAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BatchAccountSpec status BatchAccountStatus BatchAccountSpec Appears on:BatchAccount, BatchAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>BatchApplication</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchapplication/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchapplication/</guid><description>BatchApplication Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BatchApplication metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BatchApplicationSpec status BatchApplicationStatus BatchApplicationSpec Appears on:BatchApplication, BatchApplicationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string allowUpdates bool (Optional) defaultVersion string (Optional) displayName string (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string BatchApplicationStatus Appears on:BatchApplication</description></item><item><title>BatchCertificate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchcertificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchcertificate/</guid><description>BatchCertificate Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BatchCertificate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BatchCertificateSpec status BatchCertificateStatus BatchCertificateSpec Appears on:BatchCertificate, BatchCertificateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>BatchPool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/batchpool/</guid><description>BatchPool Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string BatchPool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec BatchPoolSpec status BatchPoolStatus BatchPoolSpec Appears on:BatchPool, BatchPoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string autoScale []BatchPoolSpecAutoScale (Optional) certificate []BatchPoolSpecCertificate (Optional) containerConfiguration []BatchPoolSpecContainerConfiguration (Optional) displayName string (Optional) fixedScale []BatchPoolSpecFixedScale (Optional) maxTasksPerNode int (Optional) name string nodeAgentSkuID string resourceGroupName string startTask []BatchPoolSpecStartTask (Optional) stopPendingResizeOperation bool (Optional) storageImageReference []BatchPoolSpecStorageImageReference vmSize string BatchPoolSpecAutoScale Appears on:BatchPoolSpec</description></item><item><title>CdnEndpoint</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cdnendpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cdnendpoint/</guid><description>CdnEndpoint Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CdnEndpoint metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CdnEndpointSpec status CdnEndpointStatus CdnEndpointSpec Appears on:CdnEndpoint, CdnEndpointStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string contentTypesToCompress []string (Optional) geoFilter []CdnEndpointSpecGeoFilter (Optional) hostName string (Optional) isCompressionEnabled bool (Optional) isHTTPAllowed bool (Optional) isHTTPSAllowed bool (Optional) location string name string optimizationType string (Optional) origin []CdnEndpointSpecOrigin originHostHeader string (Optional) originPath string (Optional) probePath string (Optional) profileName string querystringCachingBehaviour string (Optional) resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) CdnEndpointSpecGeoFilter Appears on:CdnEndpointSpec</description></item><item><title>CdnProfile</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cdnprofile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cdnprofile/</guid><description>CdnProfile Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CdnProfile metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CdnProfileSpec status CdnProfileStatus CdnProfileSpec Appears on:CdnProfile, CdnProfileStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string sku string tags map[string]string (Optional) CdnProfileStatus Appears on:CdnProfile</description></item><item><title>CognitiveAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cognitiveaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cognitiveaccount/</guid><description>CognitiveAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CognitiveAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CognitiveAccountSpec status CognitiveAccountStatus CognitiveAccountSpec Appears on:CognitiveAccount, CognitiveAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ConnectionMonitor</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/connectionmonitor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/connectionmonitor/</guid><description>ConnectionMonitor Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ConnectionMonitor metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ConnectionMonitorSpec status ConnectionMonitorStatus ConnectionMonitorSpec Appears on:ConnectionMonitor, ConnectionMonitorStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoStart bool (Optional) destination []ConnectionMonitorSpecDestination intervalInSeconds int (Optional) location string name string networkWatcherName string resourceGroupName string source []ConnectionMonitorSpecSource tags map[string]string (Optional) ConnectionMonitorSpecDestination Appears on:ConnectionMonitorSpec</description></item><item><title>ContainerGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/containergroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/containergroup/</guid><description>ContainerGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerGroupSpec status ContainerGroupStatus ContainerGroupSpec Appears on:ContainerGroup, ContainerGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ContainerRegistry</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/containerregistry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/containerregistry/</guid><description>ContainerRegistry Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerRegistry metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerRegistrySpec status ContainerRegistryStatus ContainerRegistrySpec Appears on:ContainerRegistry, ContainerRegistryStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ContainerService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/containerservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/containerservice/</guid><description>ContainerService Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ContainerService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ContainerServiceSpec status ContainerServiceStatus ContainerServiceSpec Appears on:ContainerService, ContainerServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>CosmosdbAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbaccount/</guid><description>CosmosdbAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CosmosdbAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CosmosdbAccountSpec status CosmosdbAccountStatus CosmosdbAccountSpec Appears on:CosmosdbAccount, CosmosdbAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>CosmosdbCassandraKeyspace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbcassandrakeyspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbcassandrakeyspace/</guid><description>CosmosdbCassandraKeyspace Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CosmosdbCassandraKeyspace metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CosmosdbCassandraKeyspaceSpec status CosmosdbCassandraKeyspaceStatus CosmosdbCassandraKeyspaceSpec Appears on:CosmosdbCassandraKeyspace, CosmosdbCassandraKeyspaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string name string resourceGroupName string CosmosdbCassandraKeyspaceStatus Appears on:CosmosdbCassandraKeyspace</description></item><item><title>CosmosdbMongoCollection</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbmongocollection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbmongocollection/</guid><description>CosmosdbMongoCollection Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CosmosdbMongoCollection metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CosmosdbMongoCollectionSpec status CosmosdbMongoCollectionStatus CosmosdbMongoCollectionSpec Appears on:CosmosdbMongoCollection, CosmosdbMongoCollectionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string databaseName string defaultTtlSeconds int (Optional) indexes []CosmosdbMongoCollectionSpecIndexes (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string shardKey string (Optional) CosmosdbMongoCollectionSpecIndexes Appears on:CosmosdbMongoCollectionSpec</description></item><item><title>CosmosdbMongoDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbmongodatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbmongodatabase/</guid><description>CosmosdbMongoDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CosmosdbMongoDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CosmosdbMongoDatabaseSpec status CosmosdbMongoDatabaseStatus CosmosdbMongoDatabaseSpec Appears on:CosmosdbMongoDatabase, CosmosdbMongoDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string name string resourceGroupName string CosmosdbMongoDatabaseStatus Appears on:CosmosdbMongoDatabase</description></item><item><title>CosmosdbSQLDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbsqldatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbsqldatabase/</guid><description>CosmosdbSQLDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CosmosdbSQLDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CosmosdbSQLDatabaseSpec status CosmosdbSQLDatabaseStatus CosmosdbSQLDatabaseSpec Appears on:CosmosdbSQLDatabase, CosmosdbSQLDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string name string resourceGroupName string CosmosdbSQLDatabaseStatus Appears on:CosmosdbSQLDatabase</description></item><item><title>CosmosdbTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbtable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/cosmosdbtable/</guid><description>CosmosdbTable Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string CosmosdbTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CosmosdbTableSpec status CosmosdbTableStatus CosmosdbTableSpec Appears on:CosmosdbTable, CosmosdbTableStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string name string resourceGroupName string CosmosdbTableStatus Appears on:CosmosdbTable</description></item><item><title>DatabricksWorkspace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/databricksworkspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/databricksworkspace/</guid><description>DatabricksWorkspace Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DatabricksWorkspace metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DatabricksWorkspaceSpec status DatabricksWorkspaceStatus DatabricksWorkspaceSpec Appears on:DatabricksWorkspace, DatabricksWorkspaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string managedResourceGroupID string (Optional) managedResourceGroupName string (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string sku string tags map[string]string (Optional) DatabricksWorkspaceStatus Appears on:DatabricksWorkspace</description></item><item><title>DataFactory</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactory/</guid><description>DataFactory Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactory metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactorySpec status DataFactoryStatus DataFactorySpec Appears on:DataFactory, DataFactoryStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string githubConfiguration []DataFactorySpecGithubConfiguration (Optional) identity []DataFactorySpecIdentity (Optional) location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) vstsConfiguration []DataFactorySpecVstsConfiguration (Optional) DataFactorySpecGithubConfiguration Appears on:DataFactorySpec</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryDatasetMysql</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorydatasetmysql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorydatasetmysql/</guid><description>DataFactoryDatasetMysql Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryDatasetMysql metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryDatasetMysqlSpec status DataFactoryDatasetMysqlStatus DataFactoryDatasetMysqlSpec Appears on:DataFactoryDatasetMysql, DataFactoryDatasetMysqlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string additionalProperties map[string]string (Optional) annotations []string (Optional) dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) folder string (Optional) linkedServiceName string name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string schemaColumn []DataFactoryDatasetMysqlSpecSchemaColumn (Optional) tableName string (Optional) DataFactoryDatasetMysqlSpecSchemaColumn Appears on:DataFactoryDatasetMysqlSpec</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryDatasetPostgresql</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorydatasetpostgresql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorydatasetpostgresql/</guid><description>DataFactoryDatasetPostgresql Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryDatasetPostgresql metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryDatasetPostgresqlSpec status DataFactoryDatasetPostgresqlStatus DataFactoryDatasetPostgresqlSpec Appears on:DataFactoryDatasetPostgresql, DataFactoryDatasetPostgresqlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string additionalProperties map[string]string (Optional) annotations []string (Optional) dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) folder string (Optional) linkedServiceName string name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string schemaColumn []DataFactoryDatasetPostgresqlSpecSchemaColumn (Optional) tableName string (Optional) DataFactoryDatasetPostgresqlSpecSchemaColumn Appears on:DataFactoryDatasetPostgresqlSpec</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorydatasetsqlservertable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorydatasetsqlservertable/</guid><description>DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTable Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTableSpec status DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTableStatus DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTableSpec Appears on:DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTable, DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTableStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string additionalProperties map[string]string (Optional) annotations []string (Optional) dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) folder string (Optional) linkedServiceName string name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string schemaColumn []DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTableSpecSchemaColumn (Optional) tableName string (Optional) DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTableSpecSchemaColumn Appears on:DataFactoryDatasetSQLServerTableSpec</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicedatalakestoragegen2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicedatalakestoragegen2/</guid><description>DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2 Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2 metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2Spec status DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2Status DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2Spec Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2, DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2Status
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string additionalProperties map[string]string (Optional) annotations []string (Optional) dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) integrationRuntimeName string (Optional) name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string servicePrincipalID string servicePrincipalKey string tenant string url string DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2Status Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServiceDataLakeStorageGen2</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysql</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicemysql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicemysql/</guid><description>DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysql Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysql metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysqlSpec status DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysqlStatus DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysqlSpec Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysql, DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysqlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string additionalProperties map[string]string (Optional) annotations []string (Optional) connectionString string dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) integrationRuntimeName string (Optional) name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysqlStatus Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServiceMysql</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresql</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicepostgresql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicepostgresql/</guid><description>DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresql Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresql metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresqlSpec status DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresqlStatus DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresqlSpec Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresql, DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresqlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string additionalProperties map[string]string (Optional) annotations []string (Optional) connectionString string dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) integrationRuntimeName string (Optional) name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresqlStatus Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServicePostgresql</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicesqlserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorylinkedservicesqlserver/</guid><description>DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServerSpec status DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServerStatus DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServerSpec Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServer, DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string additionalProperties map[string]string (Optional) annotations []string (Optional) connectionString string dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) integrationRuntimeName string (Optional) name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServerStatus Appears on:DataFactoryLinkedServiceSQLServer</description></item><item><title>DataFactoryPipeline</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorypipeline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datafactorypipeline/</guid><description>DataFactoryPipeline Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataFactoryPipeline metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataFactoryPipelineSpec status DataFactoryPipelineStatus DataFactoryPipelineSpec Appears on:DataFactoryPipeline, DataFactoryPipelineStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string annotations []string (Optional) dataFactoryName string description string (Optional) name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string variables map[string]string (Optional) DataFactoryPipelineStatus Appears on:DataFactoryPipeline</description></item><item><title>DataLakeAnalyticsAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakeanalyticsaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakeanalyticsaccount/</guid><description>DataLakeAnalyticsAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataLakeAnalyticsAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataLakeAnalyticsAccountSpec status DataLakeAnalyticsAccountStatus DataLakeAnalyticsAccountSpec Appears on:DataLakeAnalyticsAccount, DataLakeAnalyticsAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string defaultStoreAccountName string location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) tier string (Optional) DataLakeAnalyticsAccountStatus Appears on:DataLakeAnalyticsAccount</description></item><item><title>DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakeanalyticsfirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakeanalyticsfirewallrule/</guid><description>DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRuleSpec status DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRuleStatus DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRule, DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string endIPAddress string name string resourceGroupName string startIPAddress string DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRuleStatus Appears on:DataLakeAnalyticsFirewallRule</description></item><item><title>DataLakeStore</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakestore/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakestore/</guid><description>DataLakeStore Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataLakeStore metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataLakeStoreSpec status DataLakeStoreStatus DataLakeStoreSpec Appears on:DataLakeStore, DataLakeStoreStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string encryptionState string (Optional) encryptionType string (Optional) endpoint string (Optional) firewallAllowAzureIPS string (Optional) firewallState string (Optional) location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) tier string (Optional) DataLakeStoreStatus Appears on:DataLakeStore</description></item><item><title>DataLakeStoreFile</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakestorefile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakestorefile/</guid><description>DataLakeStoreFile Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataLakeStoreFile metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataLakeStoreFileSpec status DataLakeStoreFileStatus DataLakeStoreFileSpec Appears on:DataLakeStoreFile, DataLakeStoreFileStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string localFilePath string remoteFilePath string DataLakeStoreFileStatus Appears on:DataLakeStoreFile</description></item><item><title>DataLakeStoreFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakestorefirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/datalakestorefirewallrule/</guid><description>DataLakeStoreFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DataLakeStoreFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DataLakeStoreFirewallRuleSpec status DataLakeStoreFirewallRuleStatus DataLakeStoreFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:DataLakeStoreFirewallRule, DataLakeStoreFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accountName string endIPAddress string name string resourceGroupName string startIPAddress string DataLakeStoreFirewallRuleStatus Appears on:DataLakeStoreFirewallRule</description></item><item><title>DdosProtectionPlan</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/ddosprotectionplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/ddosprotectionplan/</guid><description>DdosProtectionPlan Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DdosProtectionPlan metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DdosProtectionPlanSpec status DdosProtectionPlanStatus DdosProtectionPlanSpec Appears on:DdosProtectionPlan, DdosProtectionPlanStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) virtualNetworkIDS []string (Optional) DdosProtectionPlanStatus Appears on:DdosProtectionPlan</description></item><item><title>DevspaceController</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devspacecontroller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devspacecontroller/</guid><description>DevspaceController Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DevspaceController metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DevspaceControllerSpec status DevspaceControllerStatus DevspaceControllerSpec Appears on:DevspaceController, DevspaceControllerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>DevTestLab</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestlab/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestlab/</guid><description>DevTestLab Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DevTestLab metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DevTestLabSpec status DevTestLabStatus DevTestLabSpec Appears on:DevTestLab, DevTestLabStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string artifactsStorageAccountID string (Optional) defaultPremiumStorageAccountID string (Optional) defaultStorageAccountID string (Optional) keyVaultID string (Optional) location string name string premiumDataDiskStorageAccountID string (Optional) resourceGroupName string storageType string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) uniqueIdentifier string (Optional) DevTestLabStatus Appears on:DevTestLab</description></item><item><title>DevTestLinuxVirtualMachine</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestlinuxvirtualmachine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestlinuxvirtualmachine/</guid><description>DevTestLinuxVirtualMachine Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DevTestLinuxVirtualMachine metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DevTestLinuxVirtualMachineSpec status DevTestLinuxVirtualMachineStatus DevTestLinuxVirtualMachineSpec Appears on:DevTestLinuxVirtualMachine, DevTestLinuxVirtualMachineStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>DevTestPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestpolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestpolicy/</guid><description>DevTestPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DevTestPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DevTestPolicySpec status DevTestPolicyStatus DevTestPolicySpec Appears on:DevTestPolicy, DevTestPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) evaluatorType string factData string (Optional) labName string name string policySetName string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) threshold string DevTestPolicyStatus Appears on:DevTestPolicy</description></item><item><title>DevTestVirtualNetwork</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestvirtualnetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestvirtualnetwork/</guid><description>DevTestVirtualNetwork Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DevTestVirtualNetwork metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DevTestVirtualNetworkSpec status DevTestVirtualNetworkStatus DevTestVirtualNetworkSpec Appears on:DevTestVirtualNetwork, DevTestVirtualNetworkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) labName string name string resourceGroupName string subnet []DevTestVirtualNetworkSpecSubnet (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) uniqueIdentifier string (Optional) DevTestVirtualNetworkSpecSubnet Appears on:DevTestVirtualNetworkSpec</description></item><item><title>DevTestWindowsVirtualMachine</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestwindowsvirtualmachine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/devtestwindowsvirtualmachine/</guid><description>DevTestWindowsVirtualMachine Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DevTestWindowsVirtualMachine metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineSpec status DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineStatus DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineSpec Appears on:DevTestWindowsVirtualMachine, DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string allowClaim bool (Optional) disallowPublicIPAddress bool (Optional) fqdn string (Optional) galleryImageReference []DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineSpecGalleryImageReference inboundNATRule []DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineSpecInboundNATRule (Optional) labName string labSubnetName string labVirtualNetworkID string location string name string notes string (Optional) password string resourceGroupName string size string storageType string tags map[string]string (Optional) uniqueIdentifier string (Optional) username string DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineSpecGalleryImageReference Appears on:DevTestWindowsVirtualMachineSpec</description></item><item><title>DnsAaaaRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsaaaarecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsaaaarecord/</guid><description>DnsAaaaRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsAaaaRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsAaaaRecordSpec status DnsAaaaRecordStatus DnsAaaaRecordSpec Appears on:DnsAaaaRecord, DnsAaaaRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string records []string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsAaaaRecordStatus Appears on:DnsAaaaRecord</description></item><item><title>DnsARecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsarecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsarecord/</guid><description>DnsARecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsARecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsARecordSpec status DnsARecordStatus DnsARecordSpec Appears on:DnsARecord, DnsARecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string records []string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsARecordStatus Appears on:DnsARecord</description></item><item><title>DnsCaaRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnscaarecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnscaarecord/</guid><description>DnsCaaRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsCaaRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsCaaRecordSpec status DnsCaaRecordStatus DnsCaaRecordSpec Appears on:DnsCaaRecord, DnsCaaRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string record []DnsCaaRecordSpecRecord resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsCaaRecordSpecRecord Appears on:DnsCaaRecordSpec</description></item><item><title>DnsCnameRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnscnamerecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnscnamerecord/</guid><description>DnsCnameRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsCnameRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsCnameRecordSpec status DnsCnameRecordStatus DnsCnameRecordSpec Appears on:DnsCnameRecord, DnsCnameRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string record string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsCnameRecordStatus Appears on:DnsCnameRecord</description></item><item><title>DnsMxRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsmxrecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsmxrecord/</guid><description>DnsMxRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsMxRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsMxRecordSpec status DnsMxRecordStatus DnsMxRecordSpec Appears on:DnsMxRecord, DnsMxRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string record []DnsMxRecordSpecRecord resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsMxRecordSpecRecord Appears on:DnsMxRecordSpec</description></item><item><title>DnsNsRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsnsrecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsnsrecord/</guid><description>DnsNsRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsNsRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsNsRecordSpec status DnsNsRecordStatus DnsNsRecordSpec Appears on:DnsNsRecord, DnsNsRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string record []DnsNsRecordSpecRecord (Optional) Deprecated records []string (Optional) resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsNsRecordSpecRecord Appears on:DnsNsRecordSpec</description></item><item><title>DnsPtrRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsptrrecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnsptrrecord/</guid><description>DnsPtrRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsPtrRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsPtrRecordSpec status DnsPtrRecordStatus DnsPtrRecordSpec Appears on:DnsPtrRecord, DnsPtrRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string records []string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsPtrRecordStatus Appears on:DnsPtrRecord</description></item><item><title>DnsSrvRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnssrvrecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnssrvrecord/</guid><description>DnsSrvRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsSrvRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsSrvRecordSpec status DnsSrvRecordStatus DnsSrvRecordSpec Appears on:DnsSrvRecord, DnsSrvRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string record []DnsSrvRecordSpecRecord resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsSrvRecordSpecRecord Appears on:DnsSrvRecordSpec</description></item><item><title>DnsTxtRecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnstxtrecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnstxtrecord/</guid><description>DnsTxtRecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsTxtRecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsTxtRecordSpec status DnsTxtRecordStatus DnsTxtRecordSpec Appears on:DnsTxtRecord, DnsTxtRecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string record []DnsTxtRecordSpecRecord resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) ttl int zoneName string DnsTxtRecordSpecRecord Appears on:DnsTxtRecordSpec</description></item><item><title>DnsZone</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnszone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/dnszone/</guid><description>DnsZone Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DnsZone metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DnsZoneSpec status DnsZoneStatus DnsZoneSpec Appears on:DnsZone, DnsZoneStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string maxNumberOfRecordSets int (Optional) name string nameServers []string (Optional) numberOfRecordSets int (Optional) registrationVirtualNetworkIDS []string (Optional) resolutionVirtualNetworkIDS []string (Optional) resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) zoneType string (Optional) DnsZoneStatus Appears on:DnsZone</description></item><item><title>EventgridDomain</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventgriddomain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventgriddomain/</guid><description>EventgridDomain Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EventgridDomain metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventgridDomainSpec status EventgridDomainStatus EventgridDomainSpec Appears on:EventgridDomain, EventgridDomainStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string endpoint string (Optional) inputMappingDefaultValues []EventgridDomainSpecInputMappingDefaultValues (Optional) inputMappingFields []EventgridDomainSpecInputMappingFields (Optional) inputSchema string (Optional) location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) EventgridDomainSpecInputMappingDefaultValues Appears on:EventgridDomainSpec</description></item><item><title>EventgridEventSubscription</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventgrideventsubscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventgrideventsubscription/</guid><description>EventgridEventSubscription Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EventgridEventSubscription metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventgridEventSubscriptionSpec status EventgridEventSubscriptionStatus EventgridEventSubscriptionSpec Appears on:EventgridEventSubscription, EventgridEventSubscriptionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string eventDeliverySchema string (Optional) eventhubEndpoint []EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecEventhubEndpoint (Optional) hybridConnectionEndpoint []EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecHybridConnectionEndpoint (Optional) includedEventTypes []string (Optional) labels []string (Optional) name string retryPolicy []EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecRetryPolicy (Optional) scope string storageBlobDeadLetterDestination []EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecStorageBlobDeadLetterDestination (Optional) storageQueueEndpoint []EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecStorageQueueEndpoint (Optional) subjectFilter []EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecSubjectFilter (Optional) topicName string (Optional) webhookEndpoint []EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecWebhookEndpoint (Optional) EventgridEventSubscriptionSpecEventhubEndpoint Appears on:EventgridEventSubscriptionSpec</description></item><item><title>EventgridTopic</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventgridtopic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventgridtopic/</guid><description>EventgridTopic Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EventgridTopic metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventgridTopicSpec status EventgridTopicStatus EventgridTopicSpec Appears on:EventgridTopic, EventgridTopicStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Eventhub</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhub/</guid><description>Eventhub Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Eventhub metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventhubSpec status EventhubStatus EventhubSpec Appears on:Eventhub, EventhubStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string captureDescription []EventhubSpecCaptureDescription (Optional) location string (Optional) Deprecated messageRetention int name string namespaceName string partitionCount int partitionIDS []string (Optional) resourceGroupName string EventhubSpecCaptureDescription Appears on:EventhubSpec</description></item><item><title>EventhubAuthorizationRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubauthorizationrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubauthorizationrule/</guid><description>EventhubAuthorizationRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EventhubAuthorizationRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventhubAuthorizationRuleSpec status EventhubAuthorizationRuleStatus EventhubAuthorizationRuleSpec Appears on:EventhubAuthorizationRule, EventhubAuthorizationRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>EventhubConsumerGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubconsumergroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubconsumergroup/</guid><description>EventhubConsumerGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EventhubConsumerGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventhubConsumerGroupSpec status EventhubConsumerGroupStatus EventhubConsumerGroupSpec Appears on:EventhubConsumerGroup, EventhubConsumerGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string eventhubName string location string (Optional) Deprecated name string namespaceName string resourceGroupName string userMetadata string (Optional) EventhubConsumerGroupStatus Appears on:EventhubConsumerGroup</description></item><item><title>EventhubNamespace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubnamespace_/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubnamespace_/</guid><description>EventhubNamespace_ Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EventhubNamespace_ metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventhubNamespace_Spec status EventhubNamespace_Status EventhubNamespace_Spec Appears on:EventhubNamespace_, EventhubNamespace_Status
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubnamespaceauthorizationrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/eventhubnamespaceauthorizationrule/</guid><description>EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRuleSpec status EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRuleStatus EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRuleSpec Appears on:EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRule, EventhubNamespaceAuthorizationRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ExpressRouteCircuit</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/expressroutecircuit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/expressroutecircuit/</guid><description>ExpressRouteCircuit Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ExpressRouteCircuit metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ExpressRouteCircuitSpec status ExpressRouteCircuitStatus ExpressRouteCircuitSpec Appears on:ExpressRouteCircuit, ExpressRouteCircuitStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorization</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/expressroutecircuitauthorization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/expressroutecircuitauthorization/</guid><description>ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorization Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorization metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorizationSpec status ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorizationStatus ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorizationSpec Appears on:ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorization, ExpressRouteCircuitAuthorizationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ExpressRouteCircuitPeering</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/expressroutecircuitpeering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/expressroutecircuitpeering/</guid><description>ExpressRouteCircuitPeering Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ExpressRouteCircuitPeering metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ExpressRouteCircuitPeeringSpec status ExpressRouteCircuitPeeringStatus ExpressRouteCircuitPeeringSpec Appears on:ExpressRouteCircuitPeering, ExpressRouteCircuitPeeringStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Firewall</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewall/</guid><description>Firewall Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Firewall metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FirewallSpec status FirewallStatus FirewallSpec Appears on:Firewall, FirewallStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string ipConfiguration []FirewallSpecIpConfiguration location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) FirewallSpecIpConfiguration Appears on:FirewallSpec</description></item><item><title>FirewallApplicationRuleCollection</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewallapplicationrulecollection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewallapplicationrulecollection/</guid><description>FirewallApplicationRuleCollection Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FirewallApplicationRuleCollection metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FirewallApplicationRuleCollectionSpec status FirewallApplicationRuleCollectionStatus FirewallApplicationRuleCollectionSpec Appears on:FirewallApplicationRuleCollection, FirewallApplicationRuleCollectionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string action string azureFirewallName string name string priority int resourceGroupName string rule []FirewallApplicationRuleCollectionSpecRule FirewallApplicationRuleCollectionSpecRule Appears on:FirewallApplicationRuleCollectionSpec</description></item><item><title>FirewallNATRuleCollection</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewallnatrulecollection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewallnatrulecollection/</guid><description>FirewallNATRuleCollection Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FirewallNATRuleCollection metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FirewallNATRuleCollectionSpec status FirewallNATRuleCollectionStatus FirewallNATRuleCollectionSpec Appears on:FirewallNATRuleCollection, FirewallNATRuleCollectionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string action string azureFirewallName string name string priority int resourceGroupName string rule []FirewallNATRuleCollectionSpecRule FirewallNATRuleCollectionSpecRule Appears on:FirewallNATRuleCollectionSpec</description></item><item><title>FirewallNetworkRuleCollection</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewallnetworkrulecollection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/firewallnetworkrulecollection/</guid><description>FirewallNetworkRuleCollection Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FirewallNetworkRuleCollection metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FirewallNetworkRuleCollectionSpec status FirewallNetworkRuleCollectionStatus FirewallNetworkRuleCollectionSpec Appears on:FirewallNetworkRuleCollection, FirewallNetworkRuleCollectionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string action string azureFirewallName string name string priority int resourceGroupName string rule []FirewallNetworkRuleCollectionSpecRule FirewallNetworkRuleCollectionSpecRule Appears on:FirewallNetworkRuleCollectionSpec</description></item><item><title>FunctionApp</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/functionapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/functionapp/</guid><description>FunctionApp Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FunctionApp metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FunctionAppSpec status FunctionAppStatus FunctionAppSpec Appears on:FunctionApp, FunctionAppStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightHadoopCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsighthadoopcluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsighthadoopcluster/</guid><description>HdinsightHadoopCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightHadoopCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightHadoopClusterSpec status HdinsightHadoopClusterStatus HdinsightHadoopClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightHadoopCluster, HdinsightHadoopClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightHbaseCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsighthbasecluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsighthbasecluster/</guid><description>HdinsightHbaseCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightHbaseCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightHbaseClusterSpec status HdinsightHbaseClusterStatus HdinsightHbaseClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightHbaseCluster, HdinsightHbaseClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightInteractiveQueryCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightinteractivequerycluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightinteractivequerycluster/</guid><description>HdinsightInteractiveQueryCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightInteractiveQueryCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightInteractiveQueryClusterSpec status HdinsightInteractiveQueryClusterStatus HdinsightInteractiveQueryClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightInteractiveQueryCluster, HdinsightInteractiveQueryClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightKafkaCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightkafkacluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightkafkacluster/</guid><description>HdinsightKafkaCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightKafkaCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightKafkaClusterSpec status HdinsightKafkaClusterStatus HdinsightKafkaClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightKafkaCluster, HdinsightKafkaClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightMlServicesCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightmlservicescluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightmlservicescluster/</guid><description>HdinsightMlServicesCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightMlServicesCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightMlServicesClusterSpec status HdinsightMlServicesClusterStatus HdinsightMlServicesClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightMlServicesCluster, HdinsightMlServicesClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightRserverCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightrservercluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightrservercluster/</guid><description>HdinsightRserverCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightRserverCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightRserverClusterSpec status HdinsightRserverClusterStatus HdinsightRserverClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightRserverCluster, HdinsightRserverClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightSparkCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightsparkcluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightsparkcluster/</guid><description>HdinsightSparkCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightSparkCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightSparkClusterSpec status HdinsightSparkClusterStatus HdinsightSparkClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightSparkCluster, HdinsightSparkClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>HdinsightStormCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightstormcluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/hdinsightstormcluster/</guid><description>HdinsightStormCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string HdinsightStormCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec HdinsightStormClusterSpec status HdinsightStormClusterStatus HdinsightStormClusterSpec Appears on:HdinsightStormCluster, HdinsightStormClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Image</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/image/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/image/</guid><description>Image Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Image metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ImageSpec status ImageStatus ImageSpec Appears on:Image, ImageStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string dataDisk []ImageSpecDataDisk (Optional) location string name string osDisk []ImageSpecOsDisk (Optional) resourceGroupName string sourceVirtualMachineID string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) zoneResilient bool (Optional) ImageSpecDataDisk Appears on:ImageSpec</description></item><item><title>IotDps</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iotdps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iotdps/</guid><description>IotDps Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IotDps metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IotDpsSpec status IotDpsStatus IotDpsSpec Appears on:IotDps, IotDpsStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string sku []IotDpsSpecSku tags map[string]string (Optional) IotDpsSpecSku Appears on:IotDpsSpec</description></item><item><title>IotDpsCertificate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iotdpscertificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iotdpscertificate/</guid><description>IotDpsCertificate Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IotDpsCertificate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IotDpsCertificateSpec status IotDpsCertificateStatus IotDpsCertificateSpec Appears on:IotDpsCertificate, IotDpsCertificateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Iothub</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iothub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iothub/</guid><description>Iothub Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Iothub metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IothubSpec status IothubStatus IothubSpec Appears on:Iothub, IothubStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>IothubConsumerGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iothubconsumergroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iothubconsumergroup/</guid><description>IothubConsumerGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IothubConsumerGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IothubConsumerGroupSpec status IothubConsumerGroupStatus IothubConsumerGroupSpec Appears on:IothubConsumerGroup, IothubConsumerGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string eventhubEndpointName string iothubName string name string resourceGroupName string IothubConsumerGroupStatus Appears on:IothubConsumerGroup</description></item><item><title>IothubSharedAccessPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iothubsharedaccesspolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/iothubsharedaccesspolicy/</guid><description>IothubSharedAccessPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string IothubSharedAccessPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec IothubSharedAccessPolicySpec status IothubSharedAccessPolicyStatus IothubSharedAccessPolicySpec Appears on:IothubSharedAccessPolicy, IothubSharedAccessPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>KeyVault</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvault/</guid><description>KeyVault Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KeyVault metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KeyVaultSpec status KeyVaultStatus KeyVaultSpec Appears on:KeyVault, KeyVaultStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accessPolicy []KeyVaultSpecAccessPolicy (Optional) enabledForDeployment bool (Optional) enabledForDiskEncryption bool (Optional) enabledForTemplateDeployment bool (Optional) location string name string networkAcls []KeyVaultSpecNetworkAcls (Optional) resourceGroupName string sku []KeyVaultSpecSku (Optional) Deprecated skuName string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) tenantID string vaultURI string (Optional) KeyVaultSpecAccessPolicy Appears on:KeyVaultSpec</description></item><item><title>KeyVaultAccessPolicy</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultaccesspolicy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultaccesspolicy/</guid><description>KeyVaultAccessPolicy Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KeyVaultAccessPolicy metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KeyVaultAccessPolicySpec status KeyVaultAccessPolicyStatus KeyVaultAccessPolicySpec Appears on:KeyVaultAccessPolicy, KeyVaultAccessPolicyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string applicationID string (Optional) certificatePermissions []string (Optional) keyPermissions []string (Optional) keyVaultID string (Optional) objectID string resourceGroupName string (Optional) Deprecated secretPermissions []string (Optional) storagePermissions []string (Optional) tenantID string vaultName string (Optional) Deprecated KeyVaultAccessPolicyStatus Appears on:KeyVaultAccessPolicy</description></item><item><title>KeyVaultCertificate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultcertificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultcertificate/</guid><description>KeyVaultCertificate Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KeyVaultCertificate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KeyVaultCertificateSpec status KeyVaultCertificateStatus KeyVaultCertificateSpec Appears on:KeyVaultCertificate, KeyVaultCertificateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>KeyVaultKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultkey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultkey/</guid><description>KeyVaultKey Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KeyVaultKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KeyVaultKeySpec status KeyVaultKeyStatus KeyVaultKeySpec Appears on:KeyVaultKey, KeyVaultKeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string curve string (Optional) e string (Optional) keyOpts []string keySize int (Optional) keyType string keyVaultID string (Optional) n string (Optional) name string tags map[string]string (Optional) vaultURI string (Optional) Deprecated version string (Optional) x string (Optional) y string (Optional) KeyVaultKeyStatus Appears on:KeyVaultKey</description></item><item><title>KeyVaultSecret</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultsecret/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/keyvaultsecret/</guid><description>KeyVaultSecret Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KeyVaultSecret metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KeyVaultSecretSpec status KeyVaultSecretStatus KeyVaultSecretSpec Appears on:KeyVaultSecret, KeyVaultSecretStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>KubernetesCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/kubernetescluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/kubernetescluster/</guid><description>KubernetesCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KubernetesCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KubernetesClusterSpec status KubernetesClusterStatus KubernetesClusterSpec Appears on:KubernetesCluster, KubernetesClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Lb</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lb/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lb/</guid><description>Lb Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Lb metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LbSpec status LbStatus LbSpec Appears on:Lb, LbStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string frontendIPConfiguration []LbSpecFrontendIPConfiguration (Optional) location string name string privateIPAddress string (Optional) privateIPAddresses []string (Optional) resourceGroupName string sku string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) LbSpecFrontendIPConfiguration Appears on:LbSpec</description></item><item><title>LbBackendAddressPool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbbackendaddresspool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbbackendaddresspool/</guid><description>LbBackendAddressPool Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LbBackendAddressPool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LbBackendAddressPoolSpec status LbBackendAddressPoolStatus LbBackendAddressPoolSpec Appears on:LbBackendAddressPool, LbBackendAddressPoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendIPConfigurations []string (Optional) loadBalancingRules []string (Optional) loadbalancerID string location string (Optional) Deprecated name string resourceGroupName string LbBackendAddressPoolStatus Appears on:LbBackendAddressPool</description></item><item><title>LbNATPool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbnatpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbnatpool/</guid><description>LbNATPool Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LbNATPool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LbNATPoolSpec status LbNATPoolStatus LbNATPoolSpec Appears on:LbNATPool, LbNATPoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendPort int frontendIPConfigurationID string (Optional) frontendIPConfigurationName string frontendPortEnd int frontendPortStart int loadbalancerID string location string (Optional) Deprecated name string protocol string resourceGroupName string LbNATPoolStatus Appears on:LbNATPool</description></item><item><title>LbNATRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbnatrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbnatrule/</guid><description>LbNATRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LbNATRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LbNATRuleSpec status LbNATRuleStatus LbNATRuleSpec Appears on:LbNATRule, LbNATRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendIPConfigurationID string (Optional) backendPort int enableFloatingIP bool (Optional) frontendIPConfigurationID string (Optional) frontendIPConfigurationName string frontendPort int loadbalancerID string location string (Optional) Deprecated name string protocol string resourceGroupName string LbNATRuleStatus Appears on:LbNATRule</description></item><item><title>LbOutboundRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lboutboundrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lboutboundrule/</guid><description>LbOutboundRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LbOutboundRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LbOutboundRuleSpec status LbOutboundRuleStatus LbOutboundRuleSpec Appears on:LbOutboundRule, LbOutboundRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string allocatedOutboundPorts int (Optional) backendAddressPoolID string enableTcpReset bool (Optional) frontendIPConfiguration []LbOutboundRuleSpecFrontendIPConfiguration (Optional) idleTimeoutInMinutes int (Optional) loadbalancerID string name string protocol string resourceGroupName string LbOutboundRuleSpecFrontendIPConfiguration Appears on:LbOutboundRuleSpec</description></item><item><title>LbProbe</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbprobe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbprobe/</guid><description>LbProbe Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LbProbe metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LbProbeSpec status LbProbeStatus LbProbeSpec Appears on:LbProbe, LbProbeStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string intervalInSeconds int (Optional) loadBalancerRules []string (Optional) loadbalancerID string location string (Optional) Deprecated name string numberOfProbes int (Optional) port int protocol string (Optional) requestPath string (Optional) resourceGroupName string LbProbeStatus Appears on:LbProbe</description></item><item><title>LbRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/lbrule/</guid><description>LbRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LbRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LbRuleSpec status LbRuleStatus LbRuleSpec Appears on:LbRule, LbRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendAddressPoolID string (Optional) backendPort int disableOutboundSnat bool (Optional) enableFloatingIP bool (Optional) frontendIPConfigurationID string (Optional) frontendIPConfigurationName string frontendPort int idleTimeoutInMinutes int (Optional) loadDistribution string (Optional) loadbalancerID string location string (Optional) Deprecated name string probeID string (Optional) protocol string resourceGroupName string LbRuleStatus Appears on:LbRule</description></item><item><title>LocalNetworkGateway</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/localnetworkgateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/localnetworkgateway/</guid><description>LocalNetworkGateway Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LocalNetworkGateway metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LocalNetworkGatewaySpec status LocalNetworkGatewayStatus LocalNetworkGatewaySpec Appears on:LocalNetworkGateway, LocalNetworkGatewayStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string addressSpace []string bgpSettings []LocalNetworkGatewaySpecBgpSettings (Optional) gatewayAddress string location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) LocalNetworkGatewaySpecBgpSettings Appears on:LocalNetworkGatewaySpec</description></item><item><title>LogAnalyticsLinkedService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticslinkedservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticslinkedservice/</guid><description>LogAnalyticsLinkedService Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogAnalyticsLinkedService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogAnalyticsLinkedServiceSpec status LogAnalyticsLinkedServiceStatus LogAnalyticsLinkedServiceSpec Appears on:LogAnalyticsLinkedService, LogAnalyticsLinkedServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string linkedServiceName string (Optional) linkedServiceProperties []LogAnalyticsLinkedServiceSpecLinkedServiceProperties (Optional) name string (Optional) resourceGroupName string resourceID string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) workspaceName string LogAnalyticsLinkedServiceSpecLinkedServiceProperties Appears on:LogAnalyticsLinkedServiceSpec</description></item><item><title>LogAnalyticsSolution</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticssolution/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticssolution/</guid><description>LogAnalyticsSolution Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogAnalyticsSolution metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogAnalyticsSolutionSpec status LogAnalyticsSolutionStatus LogAnalyticsSolutionSpec Appears on:LogAnalyticsSolution, LogAnalyticsSolutionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string plan []LogAnalyticsSolutionSpecPlan resourceGroupName string solutionName string workspaceName string workspaceResourceID string LogAnalyticsSolutionSpecPlan Appears on:LogAnalyticsSolutionSpec</description></item><item><title>LogAnalyticsWorkspace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticsworkspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticsworkspace/</guid><description>LogAnalyticsWorkspace Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogAnalyticsWorkspace metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogAnalyticsWorkspaceSpec status LogAnalyticsWorkspaceStatus LogAnalyticsWorkspaceSpec Appears on:LogAnalyticsWorkspace, LogAnalyticsWorkspaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticsworkspacelinkedservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/loganalyticsworkspacelinkedservice/</guid><description>LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedService Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedServiceSpec status LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedServiceStatus LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedServiceSpec Appears on:LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedService, LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string linkedServiceName string (Optional) linkedServiceProperties []LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedServiceSpecLinkedServiceProperties (Optional) name string (Optional) resourceGroupName string resourceID string (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) workspaceName string LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedServiceSpecLinkedServiceProperties Appears on:LogAnalyticsWorkspaceLinkedServiceSpec</description></item><item><title>LogicAppActionCustom</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicappactioncustom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicappactioncustom/</guid><description>LogicAppActionCustom Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogicAppActionCustom metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogicAppActionCustomSpec status LogicAppActionCustomStatus LogicAppActionCustomSpec Appears on:LogicAppActionCustom, LogicAppActionCustomStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string body string logicAppID string name string LogicAppActionCustomStatus Appears on:LogicAppActionCustom</description></item><item><title>LogicAppActionHTTP</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicappactionhttp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicappactionhttp/</guid><description>LogicAppActionHTTP Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogicAppActionHTTP metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogicAppActionHTTPSpec status LogicAppActionHTTPStatus LogicAppActionHTTPSpec Appears on:LogicAppActionHTTP, LogicAppActionHTTPStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string body string (Optional) headers map[string]string (Optional) logicAppID string method string name string uri string LogicAppActionHTTPStatus Appears on:LogicAppActionHTTP</description></item><item><title>LogicAppTriggerCustom</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicapptriggercustom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicapptriggercustom/</guid><description>LogicAppTriggerCustom Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogicAppTriggerCustom metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogicAppTriggerCustomSpec status LogicAppTriggerCustomStatus LogicAppTriggerCustomSpec Appears on:LogicAppTriggerCustom, LogicAppTriggerCustomStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string body string logicAppID string name string LogicAppTriggerCustomStatus Appears on:LogicAppTriggerCustom</description></item><item><title>LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequest</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicapptriggerhttprequest/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicapptriggerhttprequest/</guid><description>LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequest Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequest metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequestSpec status LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequestStatus LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequestSpec Appears on:LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequest, LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequestStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string logicAppID string method string (Optional) name string relativePath string (Optional) schema string LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequestStatus Appears on:LogicAppTriggerHTTPRequest</description></item><item><title>LogicAppTriggerRecurrence</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicapptriggerrecurrence/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicapptriggerrecurrence/</guid><description>LogicAppTriggerRecurrence Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogicAppTriggerRecurrence metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogicAppTriggerRecurrenceSpec status LogicAppTriggerRecurrenceStatus LogicAppTriggerRecurrenceSpec Appears on:LogicAppTriggerRecurrence, LogicAppTriggerRecurrenceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string frequency string interval int logicAppID string name string LogicAppTriggerRecurrenceStatus Appears on:LogicAppTriggerRecurrence</description></item><item><title>LogicAppWorkflow</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicappworkflow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/logicappworkflow/</guid><description>LogicAppWorkflow Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string LogicAppWorkflow metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LogicAppWorkflowSpec status LogicAppWorkflowStatus LogicAppWorkflowSpec Appears on:LogicAppWorkflow, LogicAppWorkflowStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string accessEndpoint string (Optional) location string name string parameters map[string]string (Optional) resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) workflowSchema string (Optional) workflowVersion string (Optional) LogicAppWorkflowStatus Appears on:LogicAppWorkflow</description></item><item><title>ManagedDisk</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/manageddisk/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/manageddisk/</guid><description>ManagedDisk Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ManagedDisk metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ManagedDiskSpec status ManagedDiskStatus ManagedDiskSpec Appears on:ManagedDisk, ManagedDiskStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createOption string diskSizeGb int (Optional) encryptionSettings []ManagedDiskSpecEncryptionSettings (Optional) imageReferenceID string (Optional) location string name string osType string (Optional) resourceGroupName string sourceResourceID string (Optional) sourceURI string (Optional) storageAccountType string tags map[string]string (Optional) zones []string (Optional) ManagedDiskSpecEncryptionSettings Appears on:ManagedDiskSpec</description></item><item><title>ManagementGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/managementgroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/managementgroup/</guid><description>ManagementGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ManagementGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ManagementGroupSpec status ManagementGroupStatus ManagementGroupSpec Appears on:ManagementGroup, ManagementGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string displayName string (Optional) groupID string (Optional) parentManagementGroupID string (Optional) subscriptionIDS []string (Optional) ManagementGroupStatus Appears on:ManagementGroup</description></item><item><title>ManagementLock</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/managementlock/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/managementlock/</guid><description>ManagementLock Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ManagementLock metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ManagementLockSpec status ManagementLockStatus ManagementLockSpec Appears on:ManagementLock, ManagementLockStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string lockLevel string name string notes string (Optional) scope string ManagementLockStatus Appears on:ManagementLock</description></item><item><title>MapsAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mapsaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mapsaccount/</guid><description>MapsAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MapsAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MapsAccountSpec status MapsAccountStatus MapsAccountSpec Appears on:MapsAccount, MapsAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>MariadbDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mariadbdatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mariadbdatabase/</guid><description>MariadbDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MariadbDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MariadbDatabaseSpec status MariadbDatabaseStatus MariadbDatabaseSpec Appears on:MariadbDatabase, MariadbDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string charset string collation string name string resourceGroupName string serverName string MariadbDatabaseStatus Appears on:MariadbDatabase</description></item><item><title>MariadbFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mariadbfirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mariadbfirewallrule/</guid><description>MariadbFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MariadbFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MariadbFirewallRuleSpec status MariadbFirewallRuleStatus MariadbFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:MariadbFirewallRule, MariadbFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string endIPAddress string name string resourceGroupName string serverName string startIPAddress string MariadbFirewallRuleStatus Appears on:MariadbFirewallRule</description></item><item><title>MariadbServer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mariadbserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mariadbserver/</guid><description>MariadbServer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MariadbServer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MariadbServerSpec status MariadbServerStatus MariadbServerSpec Appears on:MariadbServer, MariadbServerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>MediaServicesAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mediaservicesaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mediaservicesaccount/</guid><description>MediaServicesAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MediaServicesAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MediaServicesAccountSpec status MediaServicesAccountStatus MediaServicesAccountSpec Appears on:MediaServicesAccount, MediaServicesAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string storageAccount []MediaServicesAccountSpecStorageAccount MediaServicesAccountSpecStorageAccount Appears on:MediaServicesAccountSpec</description></item><item><title>MetricAlertrule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/metricalertrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/metricalertrule/</guid><description>MetricAlertrule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MetricAlertrule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MetricAlertruleSpec status MetricAlertruleStatus MetricAlertruleSpec Appears on:MetricAlertrule, MetricAlertruleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string aggregation string description string (Optional) emailAction []MetricAlertruleSpecEmailAction (Optional) enabled bool (Optional) location string metricName string name string operator string period string resourceGroupName string resourceID string tags map[string]string (Optional) threshold encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>MonitorActionGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitoractiongroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitoractiongroup/</guid><description>MonitorActionGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitorActionGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitorActionGroupSpec status MonitorActionGroupStatus MonitorActionGroupSpec Appears on:MonitorActionGroup, MonitorActionGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string emailReceiver []MonitorActionGroupSpecEmailReceiver (Optional) enabled bool (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string shortName string smsReceiver []MonitorActionGroupSpecSmsReceiver (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) webhookReceiver []MonitorActionGroupSpecWebhookReceiver (Optional) MonitorActionGroupSpecEmailReceiver Appears on:MonitorActionGroupSpec</description></item><item><title>MonitorActivityLogAlert</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitoractivitylogalert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitoractivitylogalert/</guid><description>MonitorActivityLogAlert Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitorActivityLogAlert metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitorActivityLogAlertSpec status MonitorActivityLogAlertStatus MonitorActivityLogAlertSpec Appears on:MonitorActivityLogAlert, MonitorActivityLogAlertStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string action []MonitorActivityLogAlertSpecAction (Optional) criteria []MonitorActivityLogAlertSpecCriteria description string (Optional) enabled bool (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string scopes []string tags map[string]string (Optional) MonitorActivityLogAlertSpecAction Appears on:MonitorActivityLogAlertSpec</description></item><item><title>MonitorAutoscaleSetting</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitorautoscalesetting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitorautoscalesetting/</guid><description>MonitorAutoscaleSetting Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitorAutoscaleSetting metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitorAutoscaleSettingSpec status MonitorAutoscaleSettingStatus MonitorAutoscaleSettingSpec Appears on:MonitorAutoscaleSetting, MonitorAutoscaleSettingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string enabled bool (Optional) location string name string notification []MonitorAutoscaleSettingSpecNotification (Optional) profile []MonitorAutoscaleSettingSpecProfile resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) targetResourceID string MonitorAutoscaleSettingSpecNotification Appears on:MonitorAutoscaleSettingSpec</description></item><item><title>MonitorDiagnosticSetting</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitordiagnosticsetting/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitordiagnosticsetting/</guid><description>MonitorDiagnosticSetting Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitorDiagnosticSetting metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitorDiagnosticSettingSpec status MonitorDiagnosticSettingStatus MonitorDiagnosticSettingSpec Appears on:MonitorDiagnosticSetting, MonitorDiagnosticSettingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string eventhubAuthorizationRuleID string (Optional) eventhubName string (Optional) log []MonitorDiagnosticSettingSpecLog (Optional) logAnalyticsWorkspaceID string (Optional) metric []MonitorDiagnosticSettingSpecMetric (Optional) name string storageAccountID string (Optional) targetResourceID string MonitorDiagnosticSettingSpecLog Appears on:MonitorDiagnosticSettingSpec</description></item><item><title>MonitorLogProfile</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitorlogprofile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitorlogprofile/</guid><description>MonitorLogProfile Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitorLogProfile metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitorLogProfileSpec status MonitorLogProfileStatus MonitorLogProfileSpec Appears on:MonitorLogProfile, MonitorLogProfileStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string categories []string locations []string name string retentionPolicy []MonitorLogProfileSpecRetentionPolicy servicebusRuleID string (Optional) storageAccountID string (Optional) MonitorLogProfileSpecRetentionPolicy Appears on:MonitorLogProfileSpec</description></item><item><title>MonitorMetricAlert</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitormetricalert/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitormetricalert/</guid><description>MonitorMetricAlert Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitorMetricAlert metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitorMetricAlertSpec status MonitorMetricAlertStatus MonitorMetricAlertSpec Appears on:MonitorMetricAlert, MonitorMetricAlertStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string action []MonitorMetricAlertSpecAction (Optional) autoMitigate bool (Optional) criteria []MonitorMetricAlertSpecCriteria description string (Optional) enabled bool (Optional) frequency string (Optional) name string resourceGroupName string scopes []string severity int (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) windowSize string (Optional) MonitorMetricAlertSpecAction Appears on:MonitorMetricAlertSpec</description></item><item><title>MonitorMetricAlertrule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitormetricalertrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/monitormetricalertrule/</guid><description>MonitorMetricAlertrule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MonitorMetricAlertrule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MonitorMetricAlertruleSpec status MonitorMetricAlertruleStatus MonitorMetricAlertruleSpec Appears on:MonitorMetricAlertrule, MonitorMetricAlertruleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string aggregation string description string (Optional) emailAction []MonitorMetricAlertruleSpecEmailAction (Optional) enabled bool (Optional) location string metricName string name string operator string period string resourceGroupName string resourceID string tags map[string]string (Optional) threshold encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>MssqlElasticpool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mssqlelasticpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mssqlelasticpool/</guid><description>MssqlElasticpool Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MssqlElasticpool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MssqlElasticpoolSpec status MssqlElasticpoolStatus MssqlElasticpoolSpec Appears on:MssqlElasticpool, MssqlElasticpoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string elasticPoolProperties []MssqlElasticpoolSpecElasticPoolProperties (Optional) Deprecated location string maxSizeBytes int (Optional) maxSizeGb encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>MysqlConfiguration</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlconfiguration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlconfiguration/</guid><description>MysqlConfiguration Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MysqlConfiguration metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MysqlConfigurationSpec status MysqlConfigurationStatus MysqlConfigurationSpec Appears on:MysqlConfiguration, MysqlConfigurationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string resourceGroupName string serverName string value string MysqlConfigurationStatus Appears on:MysqlConfiguration</description></item><item><title>MysqlDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqldatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqldatabase/</guid><description>MysqlDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MysqlDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MysqlDatabaseSpec status MysqlDatabaseStatus MysqlDatabaseSpec Appears on:MysqlDatabase, MysqlDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string charset string collation string name string resourceGroupName string serverName string MysqlDatabaseStatus Appears on:MysqlDatabase</description></item><item><title>MysqlFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlfirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlfirewallrule/</guid><description>MysqlFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MysqlFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MysqlFirewallRuleSpec status MysqlFirewallRuleStatus MysqlFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:MysqlFirewallRule, MysqlFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string endIPAddress string name string resourceGroupName string serverName string startIPAddress string MysqlFirewallRuleStatus Appears on:MysqlFirewallRule</description></item><item><title>MysqlServer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlserver/</guid><description>MysqlServer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MysqlServer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MysqlServerSpec status MysqlServerStatus MysqlServerSpec Appears on:MysqlServer, MysqlServerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>MysqlVirtualNetworkRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlvirtualnetworkrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/mysqlvirtualnetworkrule/</guid><description>MysqlVirtualNetworkRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string MysqlVirtualNetworkRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec MysqlVirtualNetworkRuleSpec status MysqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus MysqlVirtualNetworkRuleSpec Appears on:MysqlVirtualNetworkRule, MysqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string resourceGroupName string serverName string subnetID string MysqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus Appears on:MysqlVirtualNetworkRule</description></item><item><title>NetworkConnectionMonitor</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkconnectionmonitor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkconnectionmonitor/</guid><description>NetworkConnectionMonitor Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkConnectionMonitor metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkConnectionMonitorSpec status NetworkConnectionMonitorStatus NetworkConnectionMonitorSpec Appears on:NetworkConnectionMonitor, NetworkConnectionMonitorStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string autoStart bool (Optional) destination []NetworkConnectionMonitorSpecDestination intervalInSeconds int (Optional) location string name string networkWatcherName string resourceGroupName string source []NetworkConnectionMonitorSpecSource tags map[string]string (Optional) NetworkConnectionMonitorSpecDestination Appears on:NetworkConnectionMonitorSpec</description></item><item><title>NetworkDdosProtectionPlan</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkddosprotectionplan/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkddosprotectionplan/</guid><description>NetworkDdosProtectionPlan Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkDdosProtectionPlan metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkDdosProtectionPlanSpec status NetworkDdosProtectionPlanStatus NetworkDdosProtectionPlanSpec Appears on:NetworkDdosProtectionPlan, NetworkDdosProtectionPlanStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) virtualNetworkIDS []string (Optional) NetworkDdosProtectionPlanStatus Appears on:NetworkDdosProtectionPlan</description></item><item><title>NetworkInterface</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterface/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterface/</guid><description>NetworkInterface Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkInterface metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkInterfaceSpec status NetworkInterfaceStatus NetworkInterfaceSpec Appears on:NetworkInterface, NetworkInterfaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string appliedDNSServers []string (Optional) dnsServers []string (Optional) enableAcceleratedNetworking bool (Optional) enableIPForwarding bool (Optional) internalDNSNameLabel string (Optional) internalFqdn string (Optional) Deprecated ipConfiguration []NetworkInterfaceSpecIpConfiguration location string macAddress string (Optional) name string networkSecurityGroupID string (Optional) privateIPAddress string (Optional) privateIPAddresses []string (Optional) resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) virtualMachineID string (Optional) NetworkInterfaceSpecIpConfiguration Appears on:NetworkInterfaceSpec</description></item><item><title>NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfaceapplicationgatewaybackendaddresspoolassociation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfaceapplicationgatewaybackendaddresspoolassociation/</guid><description>NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociation Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociationSpec status NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociationStatus NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociationSpec Appears on:NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociation, NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendAddressPoolID string ipConfigurationName string networkInterfaceID string NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociationStatus Appears on:NetworkInterfaceApplicationGatewayBackendAddressPoolAssociation</description></item><item><title>NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfaceapplicationsecuritygroupassociation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfaceapplicationsecuritygroupassociation/</guid><description>NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociation Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociationSpec status NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociationStatus NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociationSpec Appears on:NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociation, NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string applicationSecurityGroupID string ipConfigurationName string networkInterfaceID string NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociationStatus Appears on:NetworkInterfaceApplicationSecurityGroupAssociation</description></item><item><title>NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfacebackendaddresspoolassociation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfacebackendaddresspoolassociation/</guid><description>NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociation Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociationSpec status NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociationStatus NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociationSpec Appears on:NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociation, NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backendAddressPoolID string ipConfigurationName string networkInterfaceID string NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociationStatus Appears on:NetworkInterfaceBackendAddressPoolAssociation</description></item><item><title>NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfacenatruleassociation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkinterfacenatruleassociation/</guid><description>NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociation Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociationSpec status NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociationStatus NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociationSpec Appears on:NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociation, NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string ipConfigurationName string natRuleID string networkInterfaceID string NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociationStatus Appears on:NetworkInterfaceNATRuleAssociation</description></item><item><title>NetworkPacketCapture</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkpacketcapture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkpacketcapture/</guid><description>NetworkPacketCapture Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkPacketCapture metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkPacketCaptureSpec status NetworkPacketCaptureStatus NetworkPacketCaptureSpec Appears on:NetworkPacketCapture, NetworkPacketCaptureStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string filter []NetworkPacketCaptureSpecFilter (Optional) maximumBytesPerPacket int (Optional) maximumBytesPerSession int (Optional) maximumCaptureDuration int (Optional) name string networkWatcherName string resourceGroupName string storageLocation []NetworkPacketCaptureSpecStorageLocation targetResourceID string NetworkPacketCaptureSpecFilter Appears on:NetworkPacketCaptureSpec</description></item><item><title>NetworkProfile</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkprofile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkprofile/</guid><description>NetworkProfile Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkProfile metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkProfileSpec status NetworkProfileStatus NetworkProfileSpec Appears on:NetworkProfile, NetworkProfileStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string containerNetworkInterface []NetworkProfileSpecContainerNetworkInterface containerNetworkInterfaceIDS []string (Optional) location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) NetworkProfileSpecContainerNetworkInterface Appears on:NetworkProfileSpec</description></item><item><title>NetworkSecurityGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networksecuritygroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networksecuritygroup/</guid><description>NetworkSecurityGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkSecurityGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkSecurityGroupSpec status NetworkSecurityGroupStatus NetworkSecurityGroupSpec Appears on:NetworkSecurityGroup, NetworkSecurityGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string securityRule []NetworkSecurityGroupSpecSecurityRule (Optional) tags map[string]string (Optional) NetworkSecurityGroupSpecSecurityRule Appears on:NetworkSecurityGroupSpec</description></item><item><title>NetworkSecurityRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networksecurityrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networksecurityrule/</guid><description>NetworkSecurityRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkSecurityRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkSecurityRuleSpec status NetworkSecurityRuleStatus NetworkSecurityRuleSpec Appears on:NetworkSecurityRule, NetworkSecurityRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string access string description string (Optional) destinationAddressPrefix string (Optional) destinationAddressPrefixes []string (Optional) destinationApplicationSecurityGroupIDS []string (Optional) destinationPortRange string (Optional) destinationPortRanges []string (Optional) direction string name string networkSecurityGroupName string priority int protocol string resourceGroupName string sourceAddressPrefix string (Optional) sourceAddressPrefixes []string (Optional) sourceApplicationSecurityGroupIDS []string (Optional) sourcePortRange string (Optional) sourcePortRanges []string (Optional) NetworkSecurityRuleStatus Appears on:NetworkSecurityRule</description></item><item><title>NetworkWatcher</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkwatcher/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/networkwatcher/</guid><description>NetworkWatcher Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NetworkWatcher metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NetworkWatcherSpec status NetworkWatcherStatus NetworkWatcherSpec Appears on:NetworkWatcher, NetworkWatcherStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string location string name string resourceGroupName string tags map[string]string (Optional) NetworkWatcherStatus Appears on:NetworkWatcher</description></item><item><title>NotificationHub</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/notificationhub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/notificationhub/</guid><description>NotificationHub Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NotificationHub metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NotificationHubSpec status NotificationHubStatus NotificationHubSpec Appears on:NotificationHub, NotificationHubStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>NotificationHubAuthorizationRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/notificationhubauthorizationrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/notificationhubauthorizationrule/</guid><description>NotificationHubAuthorizationRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NotificationHubAuthorizationRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NotificationHubAuthorizationRuleSpec status NotificationHubAuthorizationRuleStatus NotificationHubAuthorizationRuleSpec Appears on:NotificationHubAuthorizationRule, NotificationHubAuthorizationRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string listen bool (Optional) manage bool (Optional) name string namespaceName string notificationHubName string primaryAccessKey string (Optional) resourceGroupName string secondaryAccessKey string (Optional) send bool (Optional) NotificationHubAuthorizationRuleStatus Appears on:NotificationHubAuthorizationRule</description></item><item><title>NotificationHubNamespace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/notificationhubnamespace_/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/notificationhubnamespace_/</guid><description>NotificationHubNamespace_ Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string NotificationHubNamespace_ metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec NotificationHubNamespace_Spec status NotificationHubNamespace_Status NotificationHubNamespace_Spec Appears on:NotificationHubNamespace_, NotificationHubNamespace_Status
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string enabled bool (Optional) location string name string namespaceType string resourceGroupName string servicebusEndpoint string (Optional) sku []NotificationHubNamespace_SpecSku (Optional) Deprecated skuName string (Optional) NotificationHubNamespace_SpecSku Appears on:NotificationHubNamespace_Spec</description></item><item><title>PacketCapture</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/packetcapture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/packetcapture/</guid><description>PacketCapture Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PacketCapture metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PacketCaptureSpec status PacketCaptureStatus PacketCaptureSpec Appears on:PacketCapture, PacketCaptureStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string filter []PacketCaptureSpecFilter (Optional) maximumBytesPerPacket int (Optional) maximumBytesPerSession int (Optional) maximumCaptureDuration int (Optional) name string networkWatcherName string resourceGroupName string storageLocation []PacketCaptureSpecStorageLocation targetResourceID string PacketCaptureSpecFilter Appears on:PacketCaptureSpec</description></item><item><title>PolicyAssignment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/policyassignment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/policyassignment/</guid><description>PolicyAssignment Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PolicyAssignment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PolicyAssignmentSpec status PolicyAssignmentStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PolicyAssignmentStatus
PolicyAssignmentSpec Appears on:PolicyAssignment, PolicyAssignmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PolicyDefinition</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/policydefinition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/policydefinition/</guid><description>PolicyDefinition Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PolicyDefinition metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PolicyDefinitionSpec status PolicyDefinitionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PolicyDefinitionStatus
PolicyDefinitionSpec Appears on:PolicyDefinition, PolicyDefinitionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PolicySetDefinition</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/policysetdefinition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/policysetdefinition/</guid><description>PolicySetDefinition Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PolicySetDefinition metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PolicySetDefinitionSpec status PolicySetDefinitionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PolicySetDefinitionStatus
PolicySetDefinitionSpec Appears on:PolicySetDefinition, PolicySetDefinitionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PostgresqlConfiguration</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlconfiguration/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlconfiguration/</guid><description>PostgresqlConfiguration Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PostgresqlConfiguration metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PostgresqlConfigurationSpec status PostgresqlConfigurationStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PostgresqlConfigurationStatus
PostgresqlConfigurationSpec Appears on:PostgresqlConfiguration, PostgresqlConfigurationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PostgresqlDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqldatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqldatabase/</guid><description>PostgresqlDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PostgresqlDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PostgresqlDatabaseSpec status PostgresqlDatabaseStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PostgresqlDatabaseStatus
PostgresqlDatabaseSpec Appears on:PostgresqlDatabase, PostgresqlDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PostgresqlFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlfirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlfirewallrule/</guid><description>PostgresqlFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PostgresqlFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PostgresqlFirewallRuleSpec status PostgresqlFirewallRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PostgresqlFirewallRuleStatus
PostgresqlFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:PostgresqlFirewallRule, PostgresqlFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PostgresqlServer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlserver/</guid><description>PostgresqlServer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PostgresqlServer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PostgresqlServerSpec status PostgresqlServerStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PostgresqlServerStatus
PostgresqlServerSpec Appears on:PostgresqlServer, PostgresqlServerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlvirtualnetworkrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/postgresqlvirtualnetworkrule/</guid><description>PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRuleSpec status PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus
PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRuleSpec Appears on:PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRule, PostgresqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PrivateDNSARecord</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/privatednsarecord/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/privatednsarecord/</guid><description>PrivateDNSARecord Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PrivateDNSARecord metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PrivateDNSARecordSpec status PrivateDNSARecordStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PrivateDNSARecordStatus
PrivateDNSARecordSpec Appears on:PrivateDNSARecord, PrivateDNSARecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PrivateDNSZone</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/privatednszone/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/privatednszone/</guid><description>PrivateDNSZone Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PrivateDNSZone metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PrivateDNSZoneSpec status PrivateDNSZoneStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PrivateDNSZoneStatus
PrivateDNSZoneSpec Appears on:PrivateDNSZone, PrivateDNSZoneStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PublicIP</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/publicip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/publicip/</guid><description>PublicIP Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PublicIP metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PublicIPSpec status PublicIPStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PublicIPStatus
PublicIPSpec Appears on:PublicIP, PublicIPStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>PublicIPPrefix</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/publicipprefix/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/publicipprefix/</guid><description>PublicIPPrefix Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string PublicIPPrefix metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec PublicIPPrefixSpec status PublicIPPrefixStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:PublicIPPrefixStatus
PublicIPPrefixSpec Appears on:PublicIPPrefix, PublicIPPrefixStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RecoveryServicesProtectedVm</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/recoveryservicesprotectedvm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/recoveryservicesprotectedvm/</guid><description>RecoveryServicesProtectedVm Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RecoveryServicesProtectedVm metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RecoveryServicesProtectedVmSpec status RecoveryServicesProtectedVmStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RecoveryServicesProtectedVmStatus
RecoveryServicesProtectedVmSpec Appears on:RecoveryServicesProtectedVm, RecoveryServicesProtectedVmStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVm</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/recoveryservicesprotectionpolicyvm/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/recoveryservicesprotectionpolicyvm/</guid><description>RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVm Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVm metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVmSpec status RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVmStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVmStatus
RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVmSpec Appears on:RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVm, RecoveryServicesProtectionPolicyVmStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RecoveryServicesVault</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/recoveryservicesvault/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/recoveryservicesvault/</guid><description>RecoveryServicesVault Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RecoveryServicesVault metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RecoveryServicesVaultSpec status RecoveryServicesVaultStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RecoveryServicesVaultStatus
RecoveryServicesVaultSpec Appears on:RecoveryServicesVault, RecoveryServicesVaultStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RedisCache</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/rediscache/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/rediscache/</guid><description>RedisCache Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RedisCache metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RedisCacheSpec status RedisCacheStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RedisCacheStatus
RedisCacheSpec Appears on:RedisCache, RedisCacheStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RedisFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/redisfirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/redisfirewallrule/</guid><description>RedisFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RedisFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RedisFirewallRuleSpec status RedisFirewallRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RedisFirewallRuleStatus
RedisFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:RedisFirewallRule, RedisFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RelayNamespace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/relaynamespace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/relaynamespace/</guid><description>RelayNamespace Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RelayNamespace metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RelayNamespaceSpec status RelayNamespaceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RelayNamespaceStatus
RelayNamespaceSpec Appears on:RelayNamespace, RelayNamespaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ResourceGroup</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/resourcegroup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/resourcegroup/</guid><description>ResourceGroup Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ResourceGroup metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ResourceGroupSpec status ResourceGroupStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ResourceGroupStatus
ResourceGroupSpec Appears on:ResourceGroup, ResourceGroupStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RoleAssignment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/roleassignment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/roleassignment/</guid><description>RoleAssignment Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RoleAssignment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RoleAssignmentSpec status RoleAssignmentStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RoleAssignmentStatus
RoleAssignmentSpec Appears on:RoleAssignment, RoleAssignmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RoleDefinition</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/roledefinition/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/roledefinition/</guid><description>RoleDefinition Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RoleDefinition metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RoleDefinitionSpec status RoleDefinitionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RoleDefinitionStatus
RoleDefinitionSpec Appears on:RoleDefinition, RoleDefinitionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Route</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/route/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/route/</guid><description>Route Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Route metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RouteSpec status RouteStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RouteStatus
RouteSpec Appears on:Route, RouteStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>RouteTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/routetable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/routetable/</guid><description>RouteTable Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string RouteTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RouteTableSpec status RouteTableStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:RouteTableStatus
RouteTableSpec Appears on:RouteTable, RouteTableStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SchedulerJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/schedulerjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/schedulerjob/</guid><description>SchedulerJob Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SchedulerJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SchedulerJobSpec status SchedulerJobStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SchedulerJobStatus
SchedulerJobSpec Appears on:SchedulerJob, SchedulerJobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SchedulerJobCollection</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/schedulerjobcollection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/schedulerjobcollection/</guid><description>SchedulerJobCollection Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SchedulerJobCollection metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SchedulerJobCollectionSpec status SchedulerJobCollectionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SchedulerJobCollectionStatus
SchedulerJobCollectionSpec Appears on:SchedulerJobCollection, SchedulerJobCollectionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SearchService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/searchservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/searchservice/</guid><description>SearchService Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SearchService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SearchServiceSpec status SearchServiceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SearchServiceStatus
SearchServiceSpec Appears on:SearchService, SearchServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SecurityCenterContact</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/securitycentercontact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/securitycentercontact/</guid><description>SecurityCenterContact Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SecurityCenterContact metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SecurityCenterContactSpec status SecurityCenterContactStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SecurityCenterContactStatus
SecurityCenterContactSpec Appears on:SecurityCenterContact, SecurityCenterContactStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricing</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/securitycentersubscriptionpricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/securitycentersubscriptionpricing/</guid><description>SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricing Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricing metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricingSpec status SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricingStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricingStatus
SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricingSpec Appears on:SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricing, SecurityCenterSubscriptionPricingStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SecurityCenterWorkspace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/securitycenterworkspace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/securitycenterworkspace/</guid><description>SecurityCenterWorkspace Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SecurityCenterWorkspace metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SecurityCenterWorkspaceSpec status SecurityCenterWorkspaceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SecurityCenterWorkspaceStatus
SecurityCenterWorkspaceSpec Appears on:SecurityCenterWorkspace, SecurityCenterWorkspaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusNamespace</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusnamespace/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusnamespace/</guid><description>ServicebusNamespace Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusNamespace metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusNamespaceSpec status ServicebusNamespaceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusNamespaceStatus
ServicebusNamespaceSpec Appears on:ServicebusNamespace, ServicebusNamespaceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusnamespaceauthorizationrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusnamespaceauthorizationrule/</guid><description>ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRuleSpec status ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRuleStatus
ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRuleSpec Appears on:ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRule, ServicebusNamespaceAuthorizationRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusQueue</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusqueue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusqueue/</guid><description>ServicebusQueue Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusQueue metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusQueueSpec status ServicebusQueueStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusQueueStatus
ServicebusQueueSpec Appears on:ServicebusQueue, ServicebusQueueStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusqueueauthorizationrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebusqueueauthorizationrule/</guid><description>ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRuleSpec status ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRuleStatus
ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRuleSpec Appears on:ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRule, ServicebusQueueAuthorizationRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusSubscription</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebussubscription/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebussubscription/</guid><description>ServicebusSubscription Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusSubscription metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusSubscriptionSpec status ServicebusSubscriptionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusSubscriptionStatus
ServicebusSubscriptionSpec Appears on:ServicebusSubscription, ServicebusSubscriptionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusSubscriptionRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebussubscriptionrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebussubscriptionrule/</guid><description>ServicebusSubscriptionRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusSubscriptionRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusSubscriptionRuleSpec status ServicebusSubscriptionRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusSubscriptionRuleStatus
ServicebusSubscriptionRuleSpec Appears on:ServicebusSubscriptionRule, ServicebusSubscriptionRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusTopic</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebustopic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebustopic/</guid><description>ServicebusTopic Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusTopic metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusTopicSpec status ServicebusTopicStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusTopicStatus
ServicebusTopicSpec Appears on:ServicebusTopic, ServicebusTopicStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebustopicauthorizationrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicebustopicauthorizationrule/</guid><description>ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRuleSpec status ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRuleStatus
ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRuleSpec Appears on:ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRule, ServicebusTopicAuthorizationRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>ServiceFabricCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicefabriccluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/servicefabriccluster/</guid><description>ServiceFabricCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string ServiceFabricCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ServiceFabricClusterSpec status ServiceFabricClusterStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:ServiceFabricClusterStatus
ServiceFabricClusterSpec Appears on:ServiceFabricCluster, ServiceFabricClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SharedImage</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sharedimage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sharedimage/</guid><description>SharedImage Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SharedImage metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SharedImageSpec status SharedImageStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SharedImageStatus
SharedImageSpec Appears on:SharedImage, SharedImageStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SharedImageGallery</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sharedimagegallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sharedimagegallery/</guid><description>SharedImageGallery Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SharedImageGallery metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SharedImageGallerySpec status SharedImageGalleryStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SharedImageGalleryStatus
SharedImageGallerySpec Appears on:SharedImageGallery, SharedImageGalleryStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SharedImageVersion</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sharedimageversion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sharedimageversion/</guid><description>SharedImageVersion Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SharedImageVersion metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SharedImageVersionSpec status SharedImageVersionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SharedImageVersionStatus
SharedImageVersionSpec Appears on:SharedImageVersion, SharedImageVersionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SignalrService</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/signalrservice/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/signalrservice/</guid><description>SignalrService Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SignalrService metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SignalrServiceSpec status SignalrServiceStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SignalrServiceStatus
SignalrServiceSpec Appears on:SignalrService, SignalrServiceStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Snapshot</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/snapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/snapshot/</guid><description>Snapshot Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Snapshot metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SnapshotSpec status SnapshotStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SnapshotStatus
SnapshotSpec Appears on:Snapshot, SnapshotStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlActiveDirectoryAdministrator</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlactivedirectoryadministrator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlactivedirectoryadministrator/</guid><description>SqlActiveDirectoryAdministrator Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlActiveDirectoryAdministrator metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlActiveDirectoryAdministratorSpec status SqlActiveDirectoryAdministratorStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlActiveDirectoryAdministratorStatus
SqlActiveDirectoryAdministratorSpec Appears on:SqlActiveDirectoryAdministrator, SqlActiveDirectoryAdministratorStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlDatabase</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqldatabase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqldatabase/</guid><description>SqlDatabase Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlDatabase metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlDatabaseSpec status SqlDatabaseStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlDatabaseStatus
SqlDatabaseSpec Appears on:SqlDatabase, SqlDatabaseStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlElasticpool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlelasticpool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlelasticpool/</guid><description>SqlElasticpool Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlElasticpool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlElasticpoolSpec status SqlElasticpoolStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlElasticpoolStatus
SqlElasticpoolSpec Appears on:SqlElasticpool, SqlElasticpoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlFirewallRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlfirewallrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlfirewallrule/</guid><description>SqlFirewallRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlFirewallRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlFirewallRuleSpec status SqlFirewallRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlFirewallRuleStatus
SqlFirewallRuleSpec Appears on:SqlFirewallRule, SqlFirewallRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlServer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlserver/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlserver/</guid><description>SqlServer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlServer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlServerSpec status SqlServerStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlServerStatus
SqlServerSpec Appears on:SqlServer, SqlServerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SqlVirtualNetworkRule</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlvirtualnetworkrule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/sqlvirtualnetworkrule/</guid><description>SqlVirtualNetworkRule Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SqlVirtualNetworkRule metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SqlVirtualNetworkRuleSpec status SqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus
SqlVirtualNetworkRuleSpec Appears on:SqlVirtualNetworkRule, SqlVirtualNetworkRuleStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageAccount</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storageaccount/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storageaccount/</guid><description>StorageAccount Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageAccount metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageAccountSpec status StorageAccountStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageAccountStatus
StorageAccountSpec Appears on:StorageAccount, StorageAccountStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageBlob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storageblob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storageblob/</guid><description>StorageBlob Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageBlob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageBlobSpec status StorageBlobStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageBlobStatus
StorageBlobSpec Appears on:StorageBlob, StorageBlobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageContainer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagecontainer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagecontainer/</guid><description>StorageContainer Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageContainer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageContainerSpec status StorageContainerStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageContainerStatus
StorageContainerSpec Appears on:StorageContainer, StorageContainerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageQueue</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagequeue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagequeue/</guid><description>StorageQueue Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageQueue metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageQueueSpec status StorageQueueStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageQueueStatus
StorageQueueSpec Appears on:StorageQueue, StorageQueueStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageShare</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storageshare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storageshare/</guid><description>StorageShare Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageShare metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageShareSpec status StorageShareStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageShareStatus
StorageShareSpec Appears on:StorageShare, StorageShareStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageShareDirectory</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagesharedirectory/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagesharedirectory/</guid><description>StorageShareDirectory Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageShareDirectory metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageShareDirectorySpec status StorageShareDirectoryStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageShareDirectoryStatus
StorageShareDirectorySpec Appears on:StorageShareDirectory, StorageShareDirectoryStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageTable</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagetable/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagetable/</guid><description>StorageTable Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageTable metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageTableSpec status StorageTableStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageTableStatus
StorageTableSpec Appears on:StorageTable, StorageTableStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StorageTableEntity</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagetableentity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/storagetableentity/</guid><description>StorageTableEntity Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StorageTableEntity metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StorageTableEntitySpec status StorageTableEntityStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StorageTableEntityStatus
StorageTableEntitySpec Appears on:StorageTableEntity, StorageTableEntityStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdf</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsfunctionjavascriptudf/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsfunctionjavascriptudf/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdf Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdf metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdfSpec status StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdfStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdfStatus
StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdfSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdf, StreamAnalyticsFunctionJavascriptUdfStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsJob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsjob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsjob/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsJob Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsJob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsJobSpec status StreamAnalyticsJobStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsJobStatus
StreamAnalyticsJobSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsJob, StreamAnalyticsJobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsOutputBlob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputblob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputblob/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsOutputBlob Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsOutputBlob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsOutputBlobSpec status StreamAnalyticsOutputBlobStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputBlobStatus
StreamAnalyticsOutputBlobSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputBlob, StreamAnalyticsOutputBlobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhub</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputeventhub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputeventhub/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhub Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhub metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhubSpec status StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhubStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhubStatus
StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhubSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhub, StreamAnalyticsOutputEventhubStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsOutputMssql</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputmssql/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputmssql/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsOutputMssql Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsOutputMssql metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsOutputMssqlSpec status StreamAnalyticsOutputMssqlStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputMssqlStatus
StreamAnalyticsOutputMssqlSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputMssql, StreamAnalyticsOutputMssqlStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueue</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputservicebusqueue/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsoutputservicebusqueue/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueue Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueue metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueueSpec status StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueueStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueueStatus
StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueueSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueue, StreamAnalyticsOutputServicebusQueueStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlob</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsstreaminputblob/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsstreaminputblob/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlob Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlob metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlobSpec status StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlobStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlobStatus
StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlobSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlob, StreamAnalyticsStreamInputBlobStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhub</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsstreaminputeventhub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsstreaminputeventhub/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhub Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhub metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhubSpec status StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhubStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhubStatus
StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhubSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhub, StreamAnalyticsStreamInputEventhubStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothub</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsstreaminputiothub/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/streamanalyticsstreaminputiothub/</guid><description>StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothub Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothub metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothubSpec status StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothubStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothubStatus
StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothubSpec Appears on:StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothub, StreamAnalyticsStreamInputIothubStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>Subnet</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/subnet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/subnet/</guid><description>Subnet Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Subnet metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SubnetSpec status SubnetStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SubnetStatus
SubnetSpec Appears on:Subnet, SubnetStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/subnetnetworksecuritygroupassociation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/subnetnetworksecuritygroupassociation/</guid><description>SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociation Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociationSpec status SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociationStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociationStatus
SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociationSpec Appears on:SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociation, SubnetNetworkSecurityGroupAssociationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>SubnetRouteTableAssociation</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/subnetroutetableassociation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/subnetroutetableassociation/</guid><description>SubnetRouteTableAssociation Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SubnetRouteTableAssociation metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SubnetRouteTableAssociationSpec status SubnetRouteTableAssociationStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:SubnetRouteTableAssociationStatus
SubnetRouteTableAssociationSpec Appears on:SubnetRouteTableAssociation, SubnetRouteTableAssociationStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>TemplateDeployment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/templatedeployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/templatedeployment/</guid><description>TemplateDeployment Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string TemplateDeployment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec TemplateDeploymentSpec status TemplateDeploymentStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:TemplateDeploymentStatus
TemplateDeploymentSpec Appears on:TemplateDeployment, TemplateDeploymentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>TrafficManagerEndpoint</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/trafficmanagerendpoint/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/trafficmanagerendpoint/</guid><description>TrafficManagerEndpoint Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string TrafficManagerEndpoint metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec TrafficManagerEndpointSpec status TrafficManagerEndpointStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:TrafficManagerEndpointStatus
TrafficManagerEndpointSpec Appears on:TrafficManagerEndpoint, TrafficManagerEndpointStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>TrafficManagerProfile</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/trafficmanagerprofile/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/trafficmanagerprofile/</guid><description>TrafficManagerProfile Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string TrafficManagerProfile metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec TrafficManagerProfileSpec status TrafficManagerProfileStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:TrafficManagerProfileStatus
TrafficManagerProfileSpec Appears on:TrafficManagerProfile, TrafficManagerProfileStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>UserAssignedIdentity</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/userassignedidentity/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/userassignedidentity/</guid><description>UserAssignedIdentity Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string UserAssignedIdentity metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec UserAssignedIdentitySpec status UserAssignedIdentityStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:UserAssignedIdentityStatus
UserAssignedIdentitySpec Appears on:UserAssignedIdentity, UserAssignedIdentityStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualMachine</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachine/</guid><description>VirtualMachine Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualMachine metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualMachineSpec status VirtualMachineStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualMachineStatus
VirtualMachineSpec Appears on:VirtualMachine, VirtualMachineStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachinedatadiskattachment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachinedatadiskattachment/</guid><description>VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachment Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachmentSpec status VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachmentStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachmentStatus
VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachmentSpec Appears on:VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachment, VirtualMachineDataDiskAttachmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualMachineExtension</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachineextension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachineextension/</guid><description>VirtualMachineExtension Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualMachineExtension metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualMachineExtensionSpec status VirtualMachineExtensionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualMachineExtensionStatus
VirtualMachineExtensionSpec Appears on:VirtualMachineExtension, VirtualMachineExtensionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualMachineScaleSet</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachinescaleset/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualmachinescaleset/</guid><description>VirtualMachineScaleSet Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualMachineScaleSet metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualMachineScaleSetSpec status VirtualMachineScaleSetStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualMachineScaleSetStatus
VirtualMachineScaleSetSpec Appears on:VirtualMachineScaleSet, VirtualMachineScaleSetStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualNetwork</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetwork/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetwork/</guid><description>VirtualNetwork Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualNetwork metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualNetworkSpec status VirtualNetworkStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualNetworkStatus
VirtualNetworkSpec Appears on:VirtualNetwork, VirtualNetworkStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualNetworkGateway</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetworkgateway/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetworkgateway/</guid><description>VirtualNetworkGateway Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualNetworkGateway metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualNetworkGatewaySpec status VirtualNetworkGatewayStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualNetworkGatewayStatus
VirtualNetworkGatewaySpec Appears on:VirtualNetworkGateway, VirtualNetworkGatewayStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualNetworkGatewayConnection</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetworkgatewayconnection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetworkgatewayconnection/</guid><description>VirtualNetworkGatewayConnection Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualNetworkGatewayConnection metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualNetworkGatewayConnectionSpec status VirtualNetworkGatewayConnectionStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualNetworkGatewayConnectionStatus
VirtualNetworkGatewayConnectionSpec Appears on:VirtualNetworkGatewayConnection, VirtualNetworkGatewayConnectionStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>VirtualNetworkPeering</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetworkpeering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.1.0/reference/azurerm.kubeform.com/virtualnetworkpeering/</guid><description>VirtualNetworkPeering Field Type Description apiVersion string azurerm.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VirtualNetworkPeering metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VirtualNetworkPeeringSpec status VirtualNetworkPeeringStatus Phase(string alias) Appears on:VirtualNetworkPeeringStatus
VirtualNetworkPeeringSpec Appears on:VirtualNetworkPeering, VirtualNetworkPeeringStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item></channel></rss>