<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Reference | DigitalOcean on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/</link><description>Recent content in Reference | DigitalOcean on Provision cloud resources using Kubernetes CRDs &amp; Terraform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cdn</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/cdn/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/cdn/</guid><description>Cdn Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Cdn metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CdnSpec status CdnStatus CdnSpec Appears on:Cdn, CdnStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string certificateID string (Optional) ID of a DigitalOcean managed TLS certificate for use with custom domains createdAt string (Optional) The date and time (ISO8601) of when the CDN endpoint was created.</description></item><item><title>Certificate</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/certificate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/certificate/</guid><description>Certificate Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Certificate metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec CertificateSpec status CertificateStatus CertificateSpec Appears on:Certificate, CertificateStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string secretRef Kubernetes core/v1.</description></item><item><title>DatabaseCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/databasecluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/databasecluster/</guid><description>DatabaseCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DatabaseCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DatabaseClusterSpec status DatabaseClusterStatus DatabaseClusterSpec Appears on:DatabaseCluster, DatabaseClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string database string (Optional) engine string host string (Optional) maintenanceWindow []DatabaseClusterSpecMaintenanceWindow (Optional) name string nodeCount int password string (Optional) port int (Optional) region string size string uri string (Optional) user string (Optional) version string DatabaseClusterSpecMaintenanceWindow Appears on:DatabaseClusterSpec</description></item><item><title>Domain</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/domain/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/domain/</guid><description>Domain Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Domain metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DomainSpec status DomainStatus DomainSpec Appears on:Domain, DomainStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string ipAddress string (Optional) name string urn string (Optional) DomainStatus Appears on:Domain</description></item><item><title>Droplet</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/droplet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/droplet/</guid><description>Droplet Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Droplet metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DropletSpec status DropletStatus DropletSpec Appears on:Droplet, DropletStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string backups bool (Optional) disk int (Optional) image string ipv4Address string (Optional) ipv4AddressPrivate string (Optional) ipv6 bool (Optional) ipv6Address string (Optional) locked bool (Optional) memory int (Optional) monitoring bool (Optional) name string priceHourly encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>DropletSnapshot</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/dropletsnapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/dropletsnapshot/</guid><description>DropletSnapshot Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string DropletSnapshot metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec DropletSnapshotSpec status DropletSnapshotStatus DropletSnapshotSpec Appears on:DropletSnapshot, DropletSnapshotStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createdAt string (Optional) dropletID string minDiskSize int (Optional) name string regions []string (Optional) size encoding/json.</description></item><item><title>Firewall</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/firewall/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/firewall/</guid><description>Firewall Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Firewall metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FirewallSpec status FirewallStatus FirewallSpec Appears on:Firewall, FirewallStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createdAt string (Optional) dropletIDS []int64 (Optional) inboundRule []FirewallSpecInboundRule (Optional) name string outboundRule []FirewallSpecOutboundRule (Optional) pendingChanges []FirewallSpecPendingChanges (Optional) status string (Optional) tags []string (Optional) FirewallSpecInboundRule Appears on:FirewallSpec</description></item><item><title>FloatingIP</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/floatingip/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/floatingip/</guid><description>FloatingIP Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FloatingIP metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FloatingIPSpec status FloatingIPStatus FloatingIPSpec Appears on:FloatingIP, FloatingIPStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string dropletID int (Optional) ipAddress string (Optional) region string urn string (Optional) the uniform resource name for the floating ip FloatingIPStatus Appears on:FloatingIP</description></item><item><title>FloatingIPAssignment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/floatingipassignment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/floatingipassignment/</guid><description>FloatingIPAssignment Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string FloatingIPAssignment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec FloatingIPAssignmentSpec status FloatingIPAssignmentStatus FloatingIPAssignmentSpec Appears on:FloatingIPAssignment, FloatingIPAssignmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string dropletID int ipAddress string FloatingIPAssignmentStatus Appears on:FloatingIPAssignment</description></item><item><title>KubernetesCluster</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/kubernetescluster/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/kubernetescluster/</guid><description>KubernetesCluster Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KubernetesCluster metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KubernetesClusterSpec status KubernetesClusterStatus KubernetesClusterSpec Appears on:KubernetesCluster, KubernetesClusterStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string clusterSubnet string (Optional) createdAt string (Optional) endpoint string (Optional) ipv4Address string (Optional) kubeConfig []KubernetesClusterSpecKubeConfig (Optional) name string nodePool []KubernetesClusterSpecNodePool region string serviceSubnet string (Optional) status string (Optional) tags []string (Optional) updatedAt string (Optional) version string KubernetesClusterSpecKubeConfig Appears on:KubernetesClusterSpec</description></item><item><title>KubernetesNodePool</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/kubernetesnodepool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/kubernetesnodepool/</guid><description>KubernetesNodePool Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string KubernetesNodePool metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec KubernetesNodePoolSpec status KubernetesNodePoolStatus KubernetesNodePoolSpec Appears on:KubernetesNodePool, KubernetesNodePoolStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string clusterID string name string nodeCount int nodes []KubernetesNodePoolSpecNodes (Optional) size string tags []string (Optional) KubernetesNodePoolSpecNodes Appears on:KubernetesNodePoolSpec</description></item><item><title>Loadbalancer</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/loadbalancer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/loadbalancer/</guid><description>Loadbalancer Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Loadbalancer metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec LoadbalancerSpec status LoadbalancerStatus LoadbalancerSpec Appears on:Loadbalancer, LoadbalancerStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string algorithm string (Optional) dropletIDS []int64 (Optional) dropletTag string (Optional) enableProxyProtocol bool (Optional) forwardingRule []LoadbalancerSpecForwardingRule healthcheck []LoadbalancerSpecHealthcheck (Optional) ip string (Optional) name string redirectHTTPToHTTPS bool (Optional) region string status string (Optional) stickySessions []LoadbalancerSpecStickySessions (Optional) urn string (Optional) the uniform resource name for the load balancer LoadbalancerSpecForwardingRule Appears on:LoadbalancerSpec</description></item><item><title>Project</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/project/</guid><description>Project Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Project metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec ProjectSpec status ProjectStatus ProjectSpec Appears on:Project, ProjectStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createdAt string (Optional) the date and time when the project was created, (ISO8601) description string (Optional) the descirption of the project environment string (Optional) the environment of the project&amp;rsquo;s resources name string the human-readable name for the project ownerID int (Optional) the id of the project owner.</description></item><item><title>Record</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/record/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/record/</guid><description>Record Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Record metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec RecordSpec status RecordStatus RecordSpec Appears on:Record, RecordStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string domain string flags int (Optional) fqdn string (Optional) name string port int (Optional) priority int (Optional) tag string (Optional) ttl int (Optional) type string value string weight int (Optional) RecordStatus Appears on:Record</description></item><item><title>SpacesBucket</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/spacesbucket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/spacesbucket/</guid><description>SpacesBucket Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SpacesBucket metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SpacesBucketSpec status SpacesBucketStatus SpacesBucketSpec Appears on:SpacesBucket, SpacesBucketStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string acl string (Optional) Canned ACL applied on bucket creation bucketDomainName string (Optional) The FQDN of the bucket forceDestroy bool (Optional) Unless true, the bucket will only be destroyed if empty name string Bucket name region string (Optional) Bucket region urn string (Optional) the uniform resource name for the bucket SpacesBucketStatus Appears on:SpacesBucket</description></item><item><title>SshKey</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/sshkey/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/sshkey/</guid><description>SshKey Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string SshKey metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec SshKeySpec status SshKeyStatus SshKeySpec Appears on:SshKey, SshKeyStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string fingerprint string (Optional) name string publicKey string SshKeyStatus Appears on:SshKey</description></item><item><title>Tag</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/tag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/tag/</guid><description>Tag Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Tag metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec TagSpec status TagStatus TagSpec Appears on:Tag, TagStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string name string TagStatus Appears on:Tag</description></item><item><title>Volume</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/volume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/volume/</guid><description>Volume Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string Volume metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VolumeSpec status VolumeStatus VolumeSpec Appears on:Volume, VolumeStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string description string (Optional) dropletIDS []int64 (Optional) filesystemLabel string (Optional) filesystemType string (Optional) Deprecated initialFilesystemLabel string (Optional) initialFilesystemType string (Optional) name string region string size int snapshotID string (Optional) urn string (Optional) the uniform resource name for the volume.</description></item><item><title>VolumeAttachment</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/volumeattachment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/volumeattachment/</guid><description>VolumeAttachment Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VolumeAttachment metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VolumeAttachmentSpec status VolumeAttachmentStatus VolumeAttachmentSpec Appears on:VolumeAttachment, VolumeAttachmentStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string dropletID int volumeID string VolumeAttachmentStatus Appears on:VolumeAttachment</description></item><item><title>VolumeSnapshot</title><link>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/volumesnapshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kubeform.com/docs/v0.0.1/reference/digitalocean.kubeform.com/volumesnapshot/</guid><description>VolumeSnapshot Field Type Description apiVersion string digitalocean.kubeform.com/v1alpha1 kind string VolumeSnapshot metadata Kubernetes meta/v1.ObjectMeta Refer to the Kubernetes API documentation for the fields of the metadata field. spec VolumeSnapshotSpec status VolumeSnapshotStatus VolumeSnapshotSpec Appears on:VolumeSnapshot, VolumeSnapshotStatus
Field Type Description providerRef Kubernetes core/v1.LocalObjectReference id string createdAt string (Optional) minDiskSize int (Optional) name string regions []string (Optional) size encoding/json.</description></item></channel></rss>